Chapter 261: Totem Skill 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

As he observed the leader, the two alongside Garen were ushered out of the scene by the paramedics who had rushed over, and onto a white carriage.

Lying on the stretcher, Garen’s sights fell on the chivalry leader’s direction unknowingly, and he his felt an unexpected chill.

The other party also looked back at him, his seemed cold and deep.

"We’ll talk in a moment."

A voice echoed by Garen’s ears.

Garen was shocked, He looked around, but there was clearly nobody who was talking to him. He realized that the chivalry leader seemed to nod at him, and turned away.

On the carriage, A team of people were guiding the carriage to a small hospital in White Garcia. A male doctor wearing glasses performed a brief check-up on Garen. There are no injuries, so he gave a prescription to calm his nerves, and also asked Garen to buy some simple medicine for external wounds and disinfectants. He was promptly released after paying for his services.

After Garen left the pharmacy, he found himself at the hospital corridor, and he saw the chivalry leader waiting for him.

Both men stood at the white corridor, looking at each other.

The chivalry leader’s expressionless face forced out a smile, and he reached out his hands.

"Eisenhart, the local leader of the chivalry unit, patrol unit guard and security officer."

"Garen, Garen Lombard." Garen held his hand and shook it, then released them. "Let’s find a quieter spot."

"Okay." Leader Eisenhart nodded, "Follow me."

He turned around and walked into a small ward, Garren followed suit, hanging up the "Do not disturb" sign and locking the door from the inside.

The ward was a simple affair; beds, tables and chairs, and a vase which carried a dried yellow flower.

The window was opened, and the white curtain waved along with the wind.

Leader Eisenhart walked to the window, turned around and looked at Garen silently.

"Be honest, are those people here for you?"

Garen lowered his gaze and nodded.

"I honestly don’t know, but it is possible."

"The totem users in Lush Forest are a already messy enough affair as it is, why are you poking your nose in here? Don’t you know we are in the midst of unrest here? So many people have died just a few days ago, yet you still don’t have the sense to avoid this place? "The chivalry leader opted to save the niceties and lit himself a cigarette, taking a long puff.

He looked at Garen sideways, his eyes full of deep hatred and fatigue.

"The Lush Forest is in a situation where we find two or more totem users dead every day, it doesn’t matter which side are you from, this is still not the right time to come."

"I actually don’t know anything…." Garen frowned, "I’m just a normal person who just graduated. My house is here, I just want to go home. And this unrest you spoke of, what’s up with that? What’s a totem user? I only know of Luminarists…"

The chivalry leader took another deep puff, the cigarette head lit up with embers.

"A normal person who’d just graduated?" He took a sharp stare at Garen, like an eagle who had locked onto its target.

His thoughts churned for a while, before extending his right arm.

Pa!

He snapped his finger.

In that instant, a circle of silver patterns formed from his fingertip.

The pattern rippled in waves, and it spreaded out to every corner of the ward. At the same time, it swept onto Garen’s body too.

The chivalry leader stared at Garen, as if he was looking for some reaction, but unfortunately came up empty.

At that point, the chivalry leader had a face full of expressions. It seemed like that he had relaxed. He violently squashed the cigarette butt, and threw it onto the ashtray on the table.

"Very well, very well, it seems that I have misunderstood you, you are indeed a newbie." The chivalry leader’s stern face turned warm. "Alright, have a seat, you’re a Luminarist? A traditional one?"

Garen looked at him confusedly. "Aren’t you?"

"No, not that. I’m a Luminarist, of course, but I belong to the totem user inside. Don’t tell me even this is beyond your knowledge?" Chivalry leader Eisenhart looked shocked. "Did your teacher not tell you?"

Garen shook his head. The other party looked even more weirded out.

"Alright." He pulled a chair over for Garen, signaling him to sit down. "It’s been a while since I saw a newbie so innocent. Call me Eisen, familiar people call me that anyway."

"Alright, Mr Eisen." Garen recollected his thoughts. "I would like to ask, what are totem users? And what’s the situation with the Lush Forest?"

"I can answer those two questions." Eisen held his hands together. "In essence, Luminarists are a complex topic and covers a lot of research and application. But human intelligence and energy is limited, so we have each specialize on our own fields. Luminarists have three core roles, Luminarists, Forgers and Totem Users. Luminarists fill the traditional role; where they forge and use their own totems. Forgers specializes in forging totems, selling totems that are not activated to totem users to earn massive profits. Whereas totem users specialize in combat using totems."

"And they differ in specialization." Garen nodded.

"Yes, division of labor." Eisen nodded agreeably. "This answers the first question. Now for the second question: the situation within Lush Forest. At this point, I can only tell you briefly, The Lush Forest is in unrest the moment. Are you aware about the situation at White Rose?

"Is it about the unrest at White Rose City?" Garen’s heart shivered.

"The nature of the situation is similar" Eisen nodded reluctantly. "It happened last night. The outbreak had caused multiple casualties, with ten-over injuries. So, we locked down the entire territory throughout the night, disallowing any entries. We just didn’t expect that you’d still come, let alone get assaulted.

"Then what about Trejons’ Territory, what’s happened there?!" Garen continued asking.

"Trejons’ Territory had a good base defense,plus there were three totem users stationed there. The territory owner himself is a Forger, and he’s got wide connections too, there shouldn’t be any issues in the immediate future. Why? Your house is in the Trejons’ Territory?" Risen observed his anxiety, hence the question.

"Yes, I came back this time to check it out. But I don’t know…." Garen sighed "Right, Mr Eisen, you are not local, are you?"

"Good hearing you have. I just transferred from Hann District." Eisen nodded. "Alright, I have answered whatever is necessary, you should get going. Look for a place to hide in other districts. Going in now, a novice like you would be exterminated by any totem users."

Garen laughed helplessly.

"I have offended the Mercenary’s Guild,, I’m afraid I would be in trouble wherever I go."

"Mercenary Guild huh… now that’s a bummer." Eisen frowned. "A Luminarist without a totem like you, you’re basically a goner in one strike."

He stood up, and walked a few rounds in the ward.

"So, like this, you’ll be urgently looking to create your own core totem right? He asked after standing still.

"I have trained in some martial arts, so I could defend myself…" Garen couldn’t help but to interrupt.

"Self-defense?" Eisen couldn’t help but to shake his head. "You still don’t understand the difference between the totem user and a mortal."

He raised his right arm, the green ring on his middle finger shined a bright green.

"I’m only responsible for Lush Forest’s small area for patrol, and I’m only using 10% of my ability. You should be careful."

Garen concentrated his focus. As the environment stayed still, his aura slowly spread out, covering the entire room.

The form he used to kill the two people just now was recreated. Even though his body did not expand, but he was at least 80% of his power just now.

The reason he refuted was because he wanted to understand the actual difference between him and a Luminarist. After all this while, he had not actually clashed against a Luminarist. This was a golden opportunity.

The platinum aura not normally visible by the naked eye swirled in the room.

Fuuu…

A breeze blew in through the window, raising the curtains and blocking Eisen for a moment.

"It’s over." Garen suddenly felt goosebumps behind his nape, Eisen’s voice was near him, standing behind him and a dagger in his hand was pointed towards his back.

Garen could feel it, the tip of the dagger had a terrifying power that was inexplicably sharp.

As he looked at where Eisen had been, the curtain fell to reveal that he had been long gone.

"When did you…" Garen felt that his throat was dry, the goosebumps rose behind him all over his skin. Obviously, this was a natural reaction towards threat. That dagger definitely had the power to break through his defenses.

"It’s not that I’m quick, you’re just too slow." Eisen kept his dagger, walked towards the side of the bed and sat down. "My totem’s ability is delaying, if you had a core totem, then you would be able to mitigate some part of the influence of my skill. But too bad you don’t. At least, for now. Therefore my ability could be utilized to its maximum: the hundred-fold slowdown skill had been fully utilized. When the wind blew, in that instant I just had to walk over to your back, pull out a dagger and point it at you. All it would take is a simple push. Chik!"

He imitated the sound a dagger would make as it pierced into a body. Only then Garen did lower his head, his expression calm, but with a hint of heaviness in his eyes.

"This is 10 percent of my ability. You, who does not have a core totem, are no different compared to a mortal.

Garen’s heart sunk deeper.

Just now, he had maximized his alertness to the peak, yet he could not react to Eisen at all. If he had really wanted to kill him, even with his maximum use of the Body Hardening Technique he would only last slightly longer.

"Alright, alright, you should leave, go anywhere you want, just not here." Eisen seemed to have lost interest, he lied on his bed and waved at Garen, signaling to him to leave lazily.

"Last question."

"Shoot."

Garen stopped for a moment.

"Among the totem users, are you considered strong?"

"Strong?" Eisen laughed in a baffled manner. "Brat." He sat up with a speechless face and looked at Garen." Totem users are ranked based on the evolution form of their totem. My totem is at its second form. There’s still a third form, some secretive big organization even has a unique fourth form, there are even some that could mutate based on the user’s talents to form the ultimate talent creature. With my little power, I am nothing but a small ripple…"

"I understand..." Garen finally got a brief idea on how each forms’ ability cap goes. The common knowledge that Teacher Emin gave him is too old and outdated…

"There is a night market nearby, you should go take a look. There’s no use in me telling you, you need to go and experience it yourself." Eisen gave advice like an old man. He waved at Garen again, not speaking another word.

"Thank you" Garen bowed slightly to him.

He could have obviously chosen not to care, but he was patient enough to explain so much to him.

Garen exited the ward, and closes the door.

"Be careful on the road, if you see totem users fight, do not interfere." Eisen’s voice from inside was sent directly to Garen’s ears.

He left the hospital.

Garen bought some clothes in Garcia to be changed, and then reclaimed the briefcase that was badly burnt from the police station after taking some notes. The police officers seemed satisfied, so they did not prolong his stay and allowed him to leave.

Garen found a motel to stay in. White Garcia was a small forest township with only three streets and about a hundred houses, but there was quite a number of motels, more than 10 in fact. A classic tourism township.

After paying two days’ worth of lodging fees, Garen brought his briefcase up to his own room.

Chapter 262: Totem Skill 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

Ka-chak.

He shut the door tightly and latched the chain.

Inside the dimly lit room, Garen drew the curtains, lit the oil lamp and dragged the trunk over to where he was sitting on the bed.

Click.

He opened the leather suitcase gently. The items inside included a book, consisting almost entirely of icons and some rumb coins he had brought along. There was also a change of clothes.

"Good thing they didn’t get burnt,"

Garen let out a sigh of relief. This book had been given to him by Teacher Emin. Even if he had finished reading it, the book would still hold sentimental value to him. The coins were of equal importance as well. At this moment, not much remained of the money he had on hand.

He stuck a hand into his pocket and dug around, fished out a grey purse, and threw it on the bed. Next, he took all of the money out of the trunk and piled everything together. Then, he began to count everything carefully.

Several moments later.

"2457 silver rumbs… 56 copper rumbs… And a handful of spare change copper pieces… I don’t have much money left,"

One silver rumb would be equivalent to ten bronze rumbs, which was equal to 100 copper pieces. The buying power of one silver rumb was slightly higher than one American dollar on Earth.

Garen furrowed his brows.

"This would definitely be enough for daily use, but… If I wanted to buy something else that would be… Whatever. I’d better go take a look first and decide later,"

He took a little map out of the suitcase, opened it, and began to look for something in the Lush Forest District. Almost immediately, his index finger landed on a specific dot on the map.

There was an annotation symbol next to the little dot on the map. Garen looked for the source of the symbol and found some additional information.

‘Palasi Night Market. Business begins at 5 o’clock in the morning and ends at 8. Management fee: 100 rumbs. Scale: Small.’

"The manor is temporarily off-limits for now, so I might as well go here. I might be able to find an opportunity while I’m at it. I’ll have a look at the night market early tomorrow morning. I should get a better understanding of the situation before making any moves," Garen planned everything out thoroughly and left the hotel lobby. He drank some mushroom soup and ate a few egg rolls before returning to his room to rest.

******************

The sky started to brighten as rays of light penetrated the darkness of dawn.

At the perimeter of Lush Forest district’s vast forest, a barren piece of land stood out from the rest of the green surroundings.

A large white disc-like region had been embedded in the middle of the sea of grass, like a white spot on a green carpet.

Looking into the disc, crowds of people could be seen bustling to and fro.

There were four paths for people to enter and exit the area; each point was connected to the outside by four slim, white coloured roads.

Near the exits and entrances, guards in grey robes stood watch and collected money from those who entered.

People who visited this place came dressed in various types of clothing. Some of them were slovenly dressed in dirty garments, while others came fitted in nothing but the finest robes. Some came with their faces painted in the most exquisite makeup, others just arrived in humble, simple attire.

At the entry point to the South, two young men who looked like brothers paid the fee and entered, followed by another young man in a grey robe.

The young man wore a hood over his head, save for the few strands of soft golden hair that were already exposed. He was fair skinned and had a boyishly pretty face. His slim body was slightly muscled, but well-proportioned.

He brought out a stack of silver rumbs and placed them in the guard’s big donation box to his left. Next, he took a number plate from the other man’s hand, and clasped it around his wrist.

This young man was Garen, who had arrived here by following the map the entire way.

Once he had entered the disc, his eyes began scanning the whole area.

Inside the white disc, there were about ten little white stone houses. Wooden signs with different names hung at the corners of each house.

There was a repair shop, an equipment shop, a totem shop, and a raw materials shop, among others.

The stone houses were the size of regular shops, with doorways above a constant stream of people going in and coming out.

Garen observed the people around him and noticed out of ten people, two here were emitting Luminescent breath from their bodies.

He furrowed his brows and kept his guard up, before walking towards one of the stone houses. A sign that read ‘totem shop’ was attached to the front, but it was a simple and crude sign, and obviously only temporary.

The interior layout of the shop consisted of crystal glass cabinets arranged in a large square, with a smaller square within it. The cabinets were filled with different types of totems.

All of the totems were silver, making it obvious that none of them had been activated yet.

Three beautiful young women dressed in short white dresses smiled sweetly as they tried to sell the totems to visitors of the shop.

There weren’t many people in the shop, only four or five others, and all of them appeared similar to Garen in one aspect: they were very young.

The instant Garen entered the shop, he noticed a young lady in a short skirt walking towards him.

"Good day, sir. May I know what kind of totem you require?"

"I’m just here to look," Garen replied with the first excuse that came to mind.

"Alright. Please take your time. If you require any assistance, do not hesitate to call me," the young lady replied gently and smiled as she bowed, before she walking away to attend to another customer.

Garen took a walk around the counter.

All of the totems were small-sized support totems that consisted of rat, cat, canine, various types of birds, and serpent type totems.

He took a look at an eagle totem with a marked price tag that read 250,000 silver rumbs. His heart dropped instantly, as he knew that all of the money he had right now was not even equivalent to 10,000 silver rumbs.

Once he had calmed down, Garen exited the totem shop and ventured into the other stores in the vicinity. Both the repair shop and equipment shops charged exorbitant prices; the raw materials shop was the only one that had slightly cheaper prices.

Garen went inside and bought a book titled "Totems Made Easy" and also bought a few commonly used standard encryption passwords. After that, he was left with only 120 silver rumbs.

He returned to the totem store to ask a few questions about core totems. It was known that core totems could only be made to order, and were only sold in larger night markets. They had to regulate them based on their series or types. The price range of a core totem was also significantly higher, and the young lady in charge told him right away that bespoke totems required 200,000 silver rumbs to be paid upfront as deposit. Furthermore, they would need to know the requirements of the personalized totem, as more complicated requests would also result in a higher price.

Garen calculated everything in his head carefully. He needed to know how much it would cost to order a white bear core totem.

And if his calculations were right, he would need at least 10,000,000 silver rumbs!

It finally dawned on Garen how much Teacher Emin had invested in him.

******************

Nearby Trejons Manor

In the burnt forest beside Black Swan lake.

Vanderman and two old men in white robes stood together. Their surroundings were in a state of utter disorder. In certain parts of the woods had tree trunks had frozen over, while others were up in flames.

"It’s them again! Nought a care for life or death!" One of the old men in white robes muttered angrily. "Did they think this was some backwards little country like White Rose?"

"I’m leaving this to the both of you," Vanderman said respectfully to the two old men. "The Obscuro Society is becoming more chaotic as the days go by, and now there have even been cases of second-form totem users appearing. Don’t tell me that the upper echelon really has no response to this?"

The two old men turned to look at Vanderman, and saw the agitated expression in his eyes.

"Believe in the organization. The imperial family would never sit back and watch the Obscuro Society sack and plunder as they please. The only thing we should do right now is wait."

"Understood," nodded Vanderman.

"Don’t worry. Second-formers may be slightly more troublesome, but it’s a problem we can handle." said one of the old men as he patted Vanderman’s shoulder.

Vanderman nodded again, but this time his eyes were downcast. He was not the type of person to leave his own safety in the hands of others.

******************

Inside the guest room

Garen sat up in bed next to the oil lamp while turning through the pages of "Totems Made Easy".

It was a quiet night, with nothing but the sound of pages being flipped. It wasn’t long before he had reached the most important section of the book.

‘Types of totems: Animal series, Plant series, and the theoretical Elementary series.’

‘The animal series is the most common type of totem used and understood by Luminarists. It is also regarded as the most ubiquitous totem type. Various types of dangerous beasts can be evolved into powerful mythical creatures. Obviously, the level of difficulty increases when evolving to the next level.

The plant series belongs to a field which is on the cutting edge of research by high-level Luminarists. It also possesses great power, and can be used for self-healing purposes. It is the most sought after totem skill. According to previous accounts, this totem type has been seen a few times throughout history, but quickly disappeared from the scene thereafter.

The elementary series, a type of totem that was worshipped by the Phantom Light users, was regarded as the most highly prized totem type. However, this series is still difficult to understand. If we were to say plant totem types still had traces for us to follow, elementary totems would be a myth that we knew nothing about. Thus, the elementary series remains theoretical, as there has been no proof that anyone has been able to create it.’

"Three series, huh?" Garen wrinkled his brow, and continued to turn the pages.

‘The animal series is the weakest, but also the most widely used. The first stage of the plant series is similar to the second form of the animal series. However, the level of difficulty is ten times harder than the animal series, regardless of creation or lighting up, restrained or manipulated. Therefore, Luminarists still mainly use the animal series.’

‘The animal series is divided into three main groups: ground, air, and aquatic. The types that are currently most popular include wolf, leopard, and hawk. Various schools of thought, associations, and workshops have done extensive research in those areas. These well-loved totem types were popularized on the market by the very first Heath school of thought that listed the top three most important composition theories, referred to as the Heath theory. This theory integrated various totem types, and finally concluded that the creation, manipulation and restoration of the wolf, leopard, and hawk totems were the simplest. The evolution of these totem types were also significantly easier than the rest. Therefore, this resulted in an increase in the sightings of these totems. Below is a list of well-known totems from different locations, as well as the places where they are produced, to provide further information to the reader.’

Garen’s gaze remained fixated on the page, before he noticed a little square diagram chart packed with information about various totem names and their categories.

He landed on the top part of the page where he had read about the Tashura school of thought, with its accompanying black wolf totem.

He let out a surprised gasp, and continued on to the next page.

‘Each country has its own national animal. Moreover, a large majority also have their own important imperial totems. For example: Bateman Empire, White Bat. Vandermantia, White Swan…’

Garen found the Kovitan Empire almost immediately.

‘Kovitan Empire, Red Wolf.’

Garen was about to continue reading the next page, when a sudden burst of red light flashed in his field of vision.

He was frozen in shock for a moment.

In the skill pane at the bottom of his field of vision, the three-dimensional image of a butterfly had appeared, proving that he had finally managed to complete this skill!

He took a deep breath, and subsided the surging emotions bubbling inside himself. A few minutes later, he finally opened his eyes and looked towards the skill pane.

‘Neon butterfly: First stage totem, upgrade available. Evolution success rate: 21%. Potential points to be consumed: 500%.

Ability: Poison dust attack (Releases poisonous butterfly dust, can be released up to three times a day. Effects: Paralysis, may cause death.)’

Garen noticed that the entire neon butterfly had become a new skill.

"Does this mean… I could just use my potential points to evolve my totems?"

He checked the amount of potential points he had left: 1272%.

"I guess these are my two most crucial problems right now. The first would be to determine the core totem, and the second would be to find new resources that can be used to gain potential points. A 21% success rate is way too low. My current amount of potential points is definitely still lacking…"

Garen thought back to the period of the emergence of the Three Heroes. They had overcome great catastrophes and powerful adversaries. Among those techniques the style that suited him the most was…

"Looks like I’d better hurry up and get to Iron Tank City…"

Chapter 263: Getting Acquainted 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

Before Grand Duke Goth ascended to his current position as the duke, he once spent a period of time in an expedition camp, where he was occasionally allowed to travel for pleasure. He was the third son in his family, but after the war broke out, his father and two older brothers died in battle one after another. He took over their responsibilities and carried on their fight, which led to the sudden discovery of new powers of frighteningly gigantic proportions. After that, he faced a series of betrayals and unrest, making his heart grow more like steel in the process.

But before this, Goth himself was a straightforward and friendly average young man.

Garen still remembered that before the war, Grand Duke Goth had already been a first-rate genius with hidden innate talents. He was also backed by his family’s thousand year-old collection of books and totems. However, due to the lack of attention he was given in his family and the sad reality that no one fawned over him, coupled with the fact that nobody knew about his concealed talents, everything took time to slowly and finally come together.

Among the people surrounding him, only a few cross paths with him occasionally. As for the two people that went on adventures with him, they quickly earned a place in his heart, and from that day until their last, became his only intimate companions.

"In other words, the current Goth would still be at his lowest point in life. He’s someone who knows clearly who to show gratitude towards and who he should resent. If I were to befriend him at this moment, it might be easier for me to gain his trust," Garen narrowed his eyes and thought carefully.

"An innocent and kind-hearted individual, though not someone I’d usually look up to., However, I can’t deny that he’s the type of person that everyone would want to befriend. It wouldn’t be necessary to constantly take precautions against this type of ally."

He took out the map and began to look for the location of Iron Tank City carefully.

After exiting the Kovitan Empire, he needed to take a steam train and pass through three other cities, before finally arriving at the main city of the Lavis Empire, Iron Tank City.

He estimated the distance, concluding that it would be a four day journey at least, assuming that they would be going at full speed without any stops.

"The current Goth, because of his undiscovered talents, would still be lowly ranked and unnoticed by the people around him. However, to get near him without making it seem deliberate would need some careful planning…"

Garen kept the map and counted the rumbs he had on hand again. Instantly, the expression on his face darkened.

"My money might not be enough anymore… I’d have enough for the journey there, but not much would be left for daily use after that… I need to think of a way to get more money."

He furrowed his brows slightly and pondered deeply for a few moments.

"Before Goth took over his responsibilities as the duke, he was a hired totem user. I can’t even defeat a regular totem user right now, so I shouldn’t even be thinking about that. However, totems do need to be repaired… Maybe I could try my hand at something like that instead. On one hand I could get some practice and sharpen my skills, while using my new position to get closer to Goth at the same time."

He decided that he would do that. After packing up his thoughts, he immediately lay down and extinguished the lamp before going to sleep.

On the second morning, Garen woke up early and went to the repair shop in the market. He went in and asked some questions about the fees for specific maintenance costs. As expected, totem maintenance required a great sum of money, and was even a frequently necessity at times. The scope of repairs was also an important factor, as well as the extent of damage to be repaired. Sometimes the maintenance cost was even higher than the price of the totem itself.

But the unfortunate truth was that totem repairs also required unit factories, and so far Garen did not have one. He was also at a loss towards the common types of totems available in the market. Not to mention the fact that he couldn’t tell one from another.

Without any other choice, Garen decided to leave the market for the time being.

Once he had bought his train ticket, Garen decided that it would be better for him to leave immediately, and ponder his maintenance techniques while he was on the road.

After leaving White Garcia, he travelled for two days straight and switched trains countless times, before finally leaving the Lush Forest district and entering into the Hanna district. Without further delay, he bought a train ticket from the capital of Hanna district that would take him to Gravel City. -------

Gravel City was nearby the edge of Iron Tank City, and was also a sprawling trade city. It was also one of the port cities of the Lavis Empire and was extremely technologically advanced.

It would take two to three day’s journey by train.

Garen purchased a bed for his train car, bought something to eat and drink. He then realised that he was only left with a little more than ten rumbs in his pocket, and decided that he had spent enough.

Two days and five hours later, he arrived in Gravel City, where it was already past nine o’clock at night.

He switched trains in Gravel City, and by the time he had reached Iron Tank City, it was almost dawn.

During this period of time, Garen finally understood what he had to do to evolve his totem. If he planned to use his potential points to strengthen his totem, there were two criteria that he had to meet.

Number 1: He wasn’t sure about other series, but for basic totems, he knew that the amount of potential points required to upgrade each totem would increase based on their size. The neon butterfly totem needed five potential points to evolve, but other than that, he didn’t know what else was required.

Number 2: Potential evolution required a specific amount of time for the totem to change. It wasn’t a goal that could be reached in one step or something that could happen instantly. It would be like the time when he first started using this totem; he needed time to slowly get used to it.

Garen didn’t evolve his neon butterfly immediately. Since he had yet to find a new source of potential points, he was afraid to use them carelessly. Following the increase in his power level, his current potential points usage had also gotten significantly higher. Once he had used up this potential, he would lose an opportunity to evolve.

******************

Daylight filtered into the window of the Silver Line loft, and tiny specs of dust floated in the golden rays of light.

On the second floor of the loft, a handsome harpist performed an amusing song about a clown while a crowd of onlookers sat around him laughing loudly.

The mostly empty second floor had black wood covering the floors, and various totem patterns and oil paintings hung on the walls. Behind the counter, an old man with a white beard dexterously wiped the dust off the counter before placing a bottle of an alcohol-like beverage on top.

In the corner of the second floor, a few patrons who disliked noise sat quietly in their seats and ate their breakfast leisurely.

Garen was among them.

He was dressed in a long black robe that, at first glance, made him resemble a monk. He sat quietly in his seat, eating his set meal of cheesecake and coffee.

The Silver Line loft was located on one of the lanes outside Iron Tank city, and was one the favourite leisure spots for many hired totem users. It was also a favourite hangout spot of the future Grand Duke Goth.

The first time Goth and his two friends met, it was in this very spot, on the second floor of the loft. Their meeting was an accident. A quarrel had occurred between patrons from two different tables, and when two people stepped forward to intervene, they were injured instead. Goth had also gotten himself involved, and then a huge fight broke out. People began kicking and punching each other, but nobody used their totems. This moment had become an important turning point, and the two people who attempted to mediate the quarrel became acquainted with Goth, and decided to invite him to join their task squad. Thus, that was how the formation of three future companions happened.

Garen had been here for more than half a month already. His leftover money was quickly running out. Out of desperation, he went to a totem repair shop in the market and found a job assembling units. His Master-level precision map-making helped him excel in one aspect of unit assembly. Although he wasn’t able to gain full exposure, his effectiveness gained him the admiration of the shop owner.

However, his wages were only released at the end of the month, leaving him dirt poor at this very moment.

He vaguely remembered that this was where the Goth trio had gotten acquainted. Goth, Andy, and Jessica. The three of them would not have properly met yet right now, but they would be meeting soon enough.

Garen chose to rush over to Iron Tank city, because picking the right moment to intervene was also of utmost importance. If any of the other two heroes arrived too early or too late, the timing would become unsuitable. Only Goth was currently in the vicinity.

But the current situation merely showed that he had been keeping watch at the Silver Line loft for at least half a month, and nothing had been amiss. Panic began to rise up in his heart.

Currently for Garen, time was already insufficient at this very moment.

There was only a month or more left before the war would break out. When that happened, the fury of war would spread to every corner of this world. Hired totem users would also increase, and Goth’s power would advance by leaps and bounds during that period of time. His relationships and friendships would also become much deeper.

"It couldn’t have resulted in a change of location because of the butterfly effect right…" Garen lifted his coffee cup to his mouth and sipped carefully, attempting to quash the anxiety in his heart.

Everyday he would come to keep watch, but to no avail. There were no leads in his quest to find a new source of potential points either. The period of danger was coming closer and time was running out. It didn’t matter that this was Garen, at this moment there was no way he could remain as calm as he was in the beginning.

Thump thump thump…

Suddenly a group of muscular men in bizarre clothing came up the stairway. At first glance they looked like speakers or ruffians because of their long robes, but the silver four-pointed star on their shoulders clearly stated that they were hired totem users.

This group of people sat not far from where Garen was seated. They ordered some cheese bread noisily, as well as a large jug of fermented goat’s milk. They began to eat and drink heartily once their food had arrived,

A while later, a young woman in a white robe entered. She wore a white veil and had a voluptuous figure. Her skin seemed somewhat rough, but it couldn’t hide the youthful curves of her body including her full bosom and her perfectly round buttocks.

Instantly, the men, who had already drunk some alcohol by now, began to whistle.

The woman in the white robe sat in the corner and ignored the noise around her. She merely ordered a cup of coffee and drank it quietly once it had arrived.

Seconds later, a group men and women in white robes arrived. The young man who led the group had an air of superiority around him, and wrinkled his brow at this scene.

"What’s with the whistling? You’re just a bunch of uneducated country bumpkins!"

Bang!

One of the ruffian totem users stood up in a rage.

"Fuck you! Care to say that shit one more time?!"

"Fools!" Unconcerned, the man with the arrogant face rolled his eyes. "No wonder you become horny at the mere sight of a woman. Looks like all of you know nothing but shameful behaviour. Tch tch."

"Fuck!" "He’s asking for it!"

The sound of yelling echoed throughout the place, and the ruffian totem users became furious and started charging towards the group in white robes.

Those in white robes were also unwilling to show signs of weakness, and began to flash silver light, before spreading out and advancing forward as well.

"I’m gonna beat you til your own parents won’t even recognize you!" "Kill them all! If anything happens I’ll take full responsibility!" "How dare you disrespect Miss Angela!"

Those in white robes seemed like fish in water. They were obviously seasoned fighters, as they rolled up their sleeves and rushed forward.

Both sides consisted of totem users, thus this scuffle would determine which side had stronger defense totems. When they collided, a normal person would be unable to tell if anything was amiss, but a Luminarist would know right away which side remained stronger after the collision.

Garen sat in the corner as his heart beat wildly at the scene before him.

The city guard would be patrolling nearby. Luminarists weren’t allowed to use their totem powers for no reason, and doing so would be a violation of the law. These were iron rules, and were not meant for anyone to go against. Therefore, these totem users were fighting with their bare fists instead of using their totems, in order to keep their wrongdoings to a bare minimum.

The two groups of people began to fight and merged into a chaotic mess, making it difficult to differentiate between both sides.

"Stop fighting, please stop fighting…" The old man yelled at them and tried to chastise both sides from behind the counter. However, no one paid him any mind.

Between these two groups of people, it was obvious that one group comprised of aristocrats and nobles, while the other group consisted of travelling totem users. Neither group was afraid of a fight. The place was wrecked into a state of disorder, and tables and chairs were broken and strewn into one big mess.

The singing harpist and some of the scared customers ran downstairs quickly.

Chapter 264: Getting Acquainted 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

"I said, stop fighting! Both sides should just take a step back, okay? If anyone has any issues they should just talk it out properly," At this moment, two young people appeared in the corner suddenly. There stood a man and a woman. The man chastised the group loudly and stood forward, trying to separate a pair of brawling totem users not far away.

The woman furrowed her brows. She was at a loss on what to do.

Bang!

The man received a punch to his lower jaw, causing him to stagger a few steps backwards.

"Get the hell out! You’re in the way!" One of the ruffian totem users had taken a blow at him, and was now resuming his scuffle with his opponent again.

"Why are you hitting people for no reason?!" Another voice echoed from the stairway. This time it came from a tall, strong, and honest-looking young man. "He only tried to stop the fight. Why did you have to hit him?"

"I already did, so why the heck do you care so much?!" One of the men in white robes rushed over to take a swing at him.

Bang!

The young man was dumbfounded. He had suffered a blow to his face, and was now in a daze and unsure of what had happened.

"This dumbass!" He wasn’t sure of the culprit, but someone had kicked him sharply in the crotch.

"Ahh!!!"

A loud cry of agony pierced through the room.

The well-built young man held his crotch area and hopped away, looking like a fish that had been thrown out of water.

"You’re gonna be dead! All of you! Do you know who I am? How dare you kick me in the crotch!" The young man raised his head suddenly and let out another great shout, before rushing into the group and joining their scuffle.

Bang bang bang! Thump thump! Crash! Clank clank!

The fight escalated into a messy and chaotic affair, and the young man found himself in the middle of both groups. Even the two people who had tried to stop the fight earlier had now been dragged into it.

Garen sat on the sidelines and sipped his coffee slowly, furrowing his brow as he looked at this group of people.

The muscular young man who had unexpectedly rushed into the quarrel was fighting viciously amongst the two groups and although he didn’t have a specific fighting style, his large built and great strength ensured that every hit he landed would result in an opponent being pushed back. But the totem users were not here for fun and games. Being forced backwards meant nothing to them, and they remained fine enough to continue surging forward to deliver more hits.

As for the male and female mediators from before, they were currently backed up against the wall, barely able to protect themselves from the oncoming onslaught.

Garen fixed his gaze on the young man. "Is this the fight I was waiting for?" He had some doubts about this because it was common for fights to break out here in times like this. He tried to clear his head and put everything into perspective.

Crash!

A ruffian that had been sent flying crashed into the foot of Garen’s table.

Clank!

The metal coffee pot on the table fell to the floor. Garen’s coffee spilled everywhere.

"How dare you spill that all over my face?!" The man’s face was a sticky, coffee-coloured mess. He couldn’t see properly, but immediately shot his arm out towards Garen’s body.

Bang!

The ruffian was given a hard kick that landed him quite a distance away. He collided with another table, causing yet another great mess.

"Get them!"

Someone yelled loudly, and another two ruffians pushed their opponents aside, picked up some nearby objects and pounded towards Garen.

Hmph!

Garen tapped the back of his waist gently, and a blue light began to flash. His body began to emit a thin membrane of blue light that blinked continuously

He took a big step and rushed forward into the group in front of him.

A minute later…

The ground was littered with totem users who were exhausted to the point where they had to crawl.

"Just you wait!" Both the white robed and ruffian totem users responded with the same threat, enraged like a pair of fighting cockerels. They left soon after, limping along as they went.

Garen’s clothes were in a state of disarray. He stood with the three others, and noticed that the muscular young man was badly beaten up, with a badly bruised face and swollen head. The man and woman who had attempted to stop the fight were in slightly better condition. Unlike the other man, they were only bleeding from gashes in the corners of their mouths and their black eyes.

The four of them were innocent bystanders who had been swept up in the fight. They turned to look at each other.

The young man pointed at Garen’s dumbfounded face.

"What’s up with that stupid expression? Did you get raped?"

"Could say the same about you," Garen replied mean spiritedly.

Both of them burst into laughter after that.

After cleaning up, the owner walked towards the damaged cashier counter and pointed at the wreckage sadly. Fortunately, the two groups from earlier had the decency to leave two stacks of money on the floor nearby, as a form of compensation.

This made it easier for the four people who had helped to clean up turn the other cheek and forgive them for their transgressions slightly.

Once they had finally finished cleaning, Garen and the other three people went downstairs and stood in front of the Silver Line loft.

"Seems like the both of you are pretty good fighters. I’m sure that means your totems are not the usual kind, right? Why don’t you join us? We’ve accepted a good task, it’s quite a decent offer, not too taxing and a good way to earn some money. It’s just that we don’t have enough people," said the man who had tried to stop the fight earlier. "We forgot to introduce ourselves. My name is Andy, and this is my little sister Jessica."

This man looked like a young teacher, and he spoke in a gentle manner. He had an earnest expression, and one look could tell that he was an honest man.

His little sister Jessica was a woman of few words, and had an air of learned sophistication about her. The only downside was that she lacked beauty, and was somewhat plump.

Garen listened, and suddenly felt his a jolt in his mind.

‘Goth’s two lifelong companions, their names were Jessica and Andy. In this case…’ His gaze unconsciously found its way towards the muscular young man.

This man was wearing a pair of red overalls over a plaid shirt. He had a taut, well built body. His nose was bruised black and blue and his face was swollen…

He patted his chest.

"My name is Goth. All of you are good people, and if you ever need help in a fight, look for me! Call me and I will come!"

"My name is Garen, and I’m different from the rest of you. I’m not a hired totem user," Garen shook his head and said. "I work in the repair shop in the market nearby. If you ever need something to be repaired, you are welcomed to look for me."

"Fixing totems, eh? That’s wonderful!" Goth chuckled happily. "You don’t have a core totem yet you’re incredible in your own way. To think that you’re skilled enough to fix totems!"

"Without a unit factory, the only thing I can do is to work for others," Garen shrugged his shoulders in frustration.

"Unit factory… that would indeed be difficult to obtain… Too expensive," Goth said as he stroked his stroked his chin and nodded.

"Say, why don’t you guys join us then? We could form our own little squad, and then completing the task would be a piece of cake," Andy stood on the side and said cheerfully.

"You’re not worried that we would slow you down? This guy doesn’t even have a core totem, and I don’t have money to repair mine. It would be only too easy for it to break," Goth quipped honestly.

"Not to worry, whether or not we actually succeed is another matter. Anyway, I like you guys already! There were so many people sitting upstairs, but only both of you took the initiative to stop the fight with your own hands. You guys are definitely good people!" Andy replied instantly.

"My brother is right," said Jessica softly while she remained on the sidelines.

"As long as you’re not afraid that we’ll slow you down," Goth said as he rubbed his nose, still feeling like he was burdensome in some way.

Garen also felt that he was getting in the way slightly.

"Are you sure we’re not taking advantage of you?"

"It’s no big deal, no big deal!" Andy waved their worries aside. "That’s settled. Let’s go. We’ll help Garen get the silver seal for hired totem users, and then we’ll split the tasks, before finally beginning our journey together!"

The hired totem users association was built in a silver mansion-like building. After speaking to the receptionist, Andy produced his own totem license, and registered his squad. He listed down the number of members as well as their important members. Next, he had a license made for Garen, and spent a few hundred silver rumbs.

"Think of it as a loan," Andy noticed that Garen was about to open his mouth, but stopped him from speaking immediately.

Once the four of them had completed the necessary formalities, the found a small table and sat there. Andy took a goat’s skin map out of his bundle, opened it carefully, and spread it out on the table.

Then, he took out a little booklet in which he had noted the goals and requirements of the task.

"The task that we have accepted is: to investigate the disturbance caused by robbers nearby Gravel City," Andy said softly. "This task suits us perfectly, because my totem is extremely suitable for scouting activities. With the help of my sister, this could be completed without much hassle.

"Then what do we have to do?" Goth asked quietly.

"You need to ensure the safety of both of us. Speaking of which, what do your totems do?" asked Andy curiously.

Goth’s face flushed red. He extended his right arm and placed something on the table.

A little bird hung from his right arm. The bird resembled a woodpecker, with its beak hanging from the crook of Goth’s arm. Its beady eyes stared at the other three, as the bird continued to hang quietly from its spot.

"This is my totem, the black bird. But it’s still in its heavily injured stage. Except for its eyes, the other parts of it are unable to move…" Goth shook his head regretfully.

Andy and his sister remained speechless, as their gaze turned to Garen instead.

Garen hadn’t expected Goth to be so badly beaten up.

He took out a short silver stick in his right hand, and tapped the table lightly.

The tip of the stick began secreting some blue-coloured liquid mercury, and the tabletop immediately solidified into a big blue butterfly.

The butterfly flapped its wings and flew upwards gently, flying circles around the four of them. It was an unusually beautiful sight.

Garen tapped the stick again, and the butterfly turned into a ray of blue light, which entered the stick and disappeared from sight.

"This is my support totem, the neon butterfly."

"Hmm… This would be sufficient as a core totem actually. Even though it’s just a support totem, it’s core is big enough!" Andy nodded approvingly. "Most totem users only have one main totem. You, on the other hand, already have plans for a second one. Do you really have that much money? One totem is already requires plenty of care to raise."

"That was my plan from the beginning. Even if I regret my decision now there’s nothing I can do about it…" answered Garen impatiently.

"What’s its ability?"

"Poisonous powder."

"This is useful!" The siblings let out a sigh of relief. Finally there was something they could use.

"What use is poison powder? A gust of wind would easily blow it away," said Goth with a look of pity present on his face.

"Fool, that’s only a problem when people know about it. What if they don’t?" Jessica replied. It was one of the rare moments where she spoke.

"How did you know I was a fool?" Goth turned to Jessica with a shocked look.

The three of them stopped speaking immediately.

"My totem is the black panther, while Jessica’s is the snow wolf. Their main focus is direct confrontation. Garen, your totem can be used for pre-planned ambushes, and when it flies it can be used for reconnaissance. Goth, you’ll be in charge of protecting Jessica. She tends to get distracted when controlling her totem, so make sure to keep an eye on her."

Andy began to arrange tasks for everyone.

"Below is the arrangement of our tasks."

After some careful planning, the four of them began to keep their belongings. They also made sure that they understood the plan properly. Garen and Goth had officially joined the sibling’s squad, which they now found out was named the Black Panther squad.

Garen separated from the other three, and once he had confirmed their meeting location, he finally let out a sigh of relief.

He was now one hundred percent sure that Goth was the future Grand Duke Goth. Although his current demeanor was still somewhat shocking to Garen, there was no doubt that he was the one of the future Three Great Heroes.

The creation of his core totem rested on this young man’s shoulders now. Not long after, Goth would awaken his true hidden talents. His perseverance and trust in his black bird totem would also give him unimaginable returns in the near future. This was the story of a man who had pressed on and continued on the same road for ten over years, whose hard work and determination finally bore the fruits of his labour in the end.

Goth’s innate gift was an invisible kind of gift. After a certain period of time, it was gone without a trace. Only someone as simple-minded as himself had the patience to persevere for more than ten long years without giving up on the first totem that he had ever chosen.

This kind of perseverance, coupled with the realisation of his inborn talents and the hardships faced during the war, allowed him to fully maximise his strength levels and unleash them fully in order to become one of the Three Great Heroes.

Garen knew that if everything went according to plan, Goth would soon arrive at the point where his strength would be heightened greatly. According to history, his two friends Andy and Jessica would be the ones who gave him the strength and motivation to grow, and were also a huge source of support.

It was somewhat unfair for him to use this opportunity as a stepping stone, but Garen was certain that this was the best time to get close to Goth.

He was different from Xianfulan, anytime there was an opportunity, Garen would never let it go to waste.

His goal wasn’t Goth’s black bird, neither was it the Grand Duke family’s White Dragon Hawk. He wanted to wait for the moment Goth was busy with a task, so he could wipe out the abundant resources owned by the rebel robbers.

It was important to note that this period of turmoil was not a simple, straightforward kind of turmoil…

As Garen picked up his suitcase and walked out of the inn, he looked upwards at the clear blue sky, and felt his emotions fade into a peaceful serenity.

Chapter 265: Bandits 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

Amidst the continuous stretch of burnt yellow mountains, the horse carriage lanes seemed like grey cotton threads winding their way around the rocky hills. Clusters of little green trees were scattered sporadically across the area, making it seem as if someone had accidentally splattered green ink on a yellow canvas.

The afternoon sun shone on the yellowish mountains, and was especially bright on the rocky peaks.

Four youngsters in khaki coloured hunting clothes lay beneath the shade of a fruit tree and nibbled on round red fruit while looking below intently.

There was a grey-white lane at the bottom of the hill, located in the narrow space between two cliffs.

The four of them climbed onto one side of the hill and stared attentively at the center of the lane in the crevice.

This quintet consisted of three men and a woman, who seemed like some sort of group.

"Garen, make your butterfly fly a little further towards the east. Try and see if there’s anything there?" said one of the friendly-looking men in a soft voice. "We’ve been waiting here for such a long time, yet we haven’t managed to find anything yet. Wasn’t this area supposed to be a hotspot for bandits?"

"I’ll try and see," said a handsome, golden-haired youth sat against the bottom of the tree trunk. The youth was Garen, who had just arrived from Iron Tank City. "My neon butterfly would be too conspicuous in this area. Besides, my maximum control range cannot exceed three kilometers."

"Right now the only thing we can do is wait like here like a bunch of fools," Goth said as he lay on his back. He took a large bite out of the fruit in his hand. There was already a pile of five or six fruit stones beside him.

"Be patient," Jessica replied softly.

Crunch.

Goth bit down hard on the red fruit. A look of utter boredom was plastered on his face.

Time continued to tick away. In a blink of an eye, half an hour had passed.

"I’ve found something!" Garen stood up suddenly. "I’ve found the bandits!"

"What’s their specific location?" I’ll send the black panther over!" Andy rose to his feet as well.

Garen knitted his eyebrows tightly.

"The bandits just left. Unfortunately, I’m afraid that we were a few steps too late,"

"Doesn’t matter. Let’s just hurry over and then we’ll talk."

The four of them got up quickly, and raced towards the direction that Garen had pointed towards.

Following the burnt yellow and grey rocky slope, the four people rushed down the mountain, and climbed up the slope of a different rocky hill.

Just as they reached the other side of the slope, they froze in their steps when they noticed the scene before them.

Two white ox carts had been toppled to the ground, and the black ox that had been pulling the cart earlier now lay in a pool of its own blood. At the same time, a swarm of green-headed flies circled its lifeless body.

On the football field-sized perimeter, corpses were strewn everywhere. The smell of rotting blood hung in the air, causing the onlookers to feel a sense of tightness forming inside their chests.

The dead bodies spanned a continuous distance of thirty-four meters. From the left to the right corner of the lane, not one living body could be seen.

The Black Panther squad had only been standing there for a few moments, but Jessica could not help but muffle her mouth as she began to retch.

Andy took a deep breath, and furrowed his brows at the sight that was laid out before him. "This is terrible… We should start looking for survivors for now."

Goth patted Jessica’s shoulders.

"Are you alright?" Although his own face was beginning to turn pale as a sign that he was also having a hard time, it was obvious that Goth’s patience was stronger than Jessica’s.

"I’m fine."

Garen, however, still had the same expression on his face. The only difference was that his brows were wrinkled now.

"I’ve seen worse places before. Now isn’t the time for chit chat. Go check at once if you can find any survivors. The bandits just left. If they decide to turn back now it’ll spell nothing but trouble for us."

Goth grunted.

"It’d be better if they came back here. This type of scum should all be sentenced to death!"

"I’m afraid we don’t have the power to decide that…" Andy walked towards the pile of dead bodies, and began to check them carefully.

The more he investigated, the darker his expression turned.

"At least three totem users were present! And it’s obvious that one of them possesses second form attack abilities!"

"Second form…" Goth was left speechless. "A second form totem user would never be this desperate for money in the first place! Why would he resort to becoming a bandit?"

No one replied him. This was a reason that everyone else wanted to find out as well.

Garen might have thought of an answer, but he kept it to himself.

The four of them continued to look for survivors in the corpse pile. The began their search in the middle and spread out in two separate directions.

Not long after, a cry of surprise was heard in Jessica’s direction.

"I’ve found one! Everyone come here quickly!"

Garen turned his head in that direction and saw Jessica pulling open the wooden section of a carriage. From there, she lifted out a bundle in white swaddling clothes.

"This baby is still alive!" Jessica yelled happily.

The four of them gathered together quickly, and formed a circle around Jessica.

They could see that the baby was still sound asleep in his wrappings, and did not wake up even as Jessica rocked him a few times. It looked as if the baby was in deep sleep. But they noticed the wet tear stains in the corners of the baby’s eyes, indicating that he had been crying for a while.

Andy reached a hand out to touch the baby’s forehead and nostrils.

"That’s good. He isn’t sick, and his breathing is also normal. I’ve also sent the black panther to notify the nearby marshall squad already. Someone should be arriving here soon to take care of this situation."

Garen stood at the side and looked at the other three people who were gathered around the baby. He attempted to access the old images and look into the memories of this period of time. Unfortunately, the images did not contain everything, and only the most important events were usually documented. A normal circumstance like this would not have been recorded.

He lifted his head, and looked at the blue neon butterfly flying circles in the sky. Suddenly, his expression changed.

"Watch out! Someone’s coming! It’s the bandits!"

"How many?" Andy asked calmly.

"Five of them!" The look on Garen’s face began to change again. "And three of them are carrying totems!"

"Scatter quickly!"

"There isn’t enough time! Hurry up and hide. They’re coming on to us really quickly! Bend down! Watch your breathing!" Garen hurriedly lay flat on the ground near in a recess near some rocks.

Andy and Jessica also climbed in quickly and crouched down, making sure that the baby was by their sides.

Only Goth reacted slowly, and couldn’t figure out what to do.

Garen yanked him aside roughly and pulled him downwards in one go, before pushing him into the rock pit.

"Hey! You…"

"Shh…"

Garen jabbed a finger at his mouth immediately.

At the furthest right corner of the murder scene, near the bend of the carriage lane, a group of silhouettes in black robes appeared almost instantly.

The sky was bright outside, yet all of them were dressed from head to toe in fully black robes. Even their heads were fully covered.

There were five of them in this black-robed group. The one leading the group stood all the way in front, wearing a black robe with white embroidery on the edges. The most eye-catching part of him was the black python wrapped around his shoulders.

On first glance, the black python looked like a thick black line that hung around the black-robed man’s right shoulder. This snake seemed like an average serpent, except for the third eye that had grown in the middle of its forehead that looked like a light green pupil.

The three pale green eyes stared coldly at its surroundings as the snake poked its scarlet forked tongue out of its mouth from time to time.

"It’s the three-eyed black python! Damn it! It really is form two!" cursed Andy softly. "How could a form two totem user resort to something as useless as stealing!"

"Shh…" Garen felt like pinching him.

Andy kept his voice down immediately. His voice was soft, but their enemy seemed to have heard something and was looking in their direction now. There was a sense of uncertainty in his gaze.

The four youngsters felt a chill down their spines, and quickly crouched down even lower. They were too scared to even look up now.

Garen like he could hear his heart threatening to beat out of his chest.

Form two referred to a totem user or Luminarist who had evolved their totem to the second form. He had witnessed a battle of a form two totem user with his own eyes before.

His own Teacher Emin once fought with a form two totem user and suffered serious injuries from two losses. He had almost lost his life, and was now in the process of recovering slowly. In the previous world, a Luminarist of this power-level would definitely be higher than B-level. If someone had enraged them, they had the capacity to become human nuclear bombs, except that the range of destruction would not be as vast as that of a real nuclear bomb.

Garen had realised now, that within the Luminarists, a large majority of form one totem users who had the opportunity to evolve to form two totem users, could only do so because of the support they received from specific organizations.

Judging from the luminescence of his current neon butterfly, there was no point in talking about form two Luminarists, or even form one Luminarists or totem users, when he couldn’t even shatter their luminescence.

This was the most troublesome part.

Garen himself was already very clear on this matter. He already had a Secret Technique and knowledge in combining a totem and martial arts, and would definitely be able to defeat a regular person. But when faced with a Luminarist, his skills seemed clumsy in comparison. Assuming that a form one Luminarist would just stand there and allow themselves to be attacked, it would still take him at least ten to twenty minutes just to break through their defense.

In the area of Luminarists, only form two totems were considered legitimate Luminarist totems. Beginning from form two, totems would then have the ability to access various evolutions. Furthermore, they would then be able to possess special capabilities.

The only problem was that the resources and knowledge required for a form two totem belonged to a range that would leave most people dumbfounded and in shock.

Crouching inside the pit, Garen noticed the paleness of his three companions faces.

"The three-eyed black python is the black python’s form two totem. I’ve seen its abilities," whispered Andy in an extremely soft voice. He sounded like he had been out of breath for a while. "Garen, don’t come out. The three-eyed black python’s third eye can will release a green coloured light that corrodes. You don’t have a core totem, so you won’t be able to block it."

Garen felt his heart beat quicker in his chest. He nodded obediently.

After staying downwards for a while, the four of them held their breath, still afraid to come out. They could hear the endless sound of footsteps approaching closer, but did not dare to look up and peek.

The sound of footsteps grew louder as they came nearer, before stopping abruptly at a certain location.

"Gaduma, anjisiladinghute." They heard the words being said in a young woman’s voice, but could not understand the meaning at all.

Garen furrowed his eyebrows, and looked to the rest of his companions. Andy shook his head, signalling that he too could not understand. Goth had a blank expression on his face. Only Jessica seemed to have an idea about what was happening.

Jessica met the trio’s eyes and begin to translate what she had heard into the Kovitan language. She mouthed the words one by one and made sure the others were watching.

Iron Tank City was one of the Kovitan Empire’s vassal states. The feudal lords of these territories were still involved in the imperial affairs of the Kovitan Empire, and still spoke a native variation of the Kovitan language.

But the language spoken by the woman in the black robe sounded more like a local dialect from the South, and sounded almost like a tongue-twister.

Jessica began to translate the sentences one by one for her other three friends.

The young woman said: "Captain, my totem had definitely sensed the presence of others in this area just now."

"How many of them were there?" This was probably said by the man in the black robe. His voice sounded low and full of self-control, giving people a sense of restraint.

"Four of them," replied the woman.

"What do they look like?"

"They were dressed in yellow clothes."

"Then they’re definitely not the marshall squad," replied the captain in a low voice. "Let’s go. They were probably just passersby going down the road. The marshall squad will be arriving soon though."

"Yes, sir."

The sound of footsteps began to move further away.

The four people hidden in the rock pit finally breathed a sigh of relief.

"Hey! This part was moved by someone!" The woman’s voice rang loudly once again. "There’s a hidden section here, something must be hidden inside!"

The footsteps stopped suddenly.

The heart beats of the four people began to speed up.

"Seems like there may still be survivors… Hmm… Interesting. Calania, continue investigating this area. See if there are any survivors left." The captain’s voice echoed throughout the area.

"Yes," replied a woman’s voice.

Suddenly, the sharp noise of bird’s cry could be heard.

Caw!

The shrill noise only sounded for a moment, and stopped right after that.

"There are no survivors inside the carriage," replied the woman’s voice once again.

"Alright then. Move out," replied the captain indifferently.

Chapter 266: Bandits 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

Inside the rock pit.

Garen felt Andy patting him. When he raised his head, he noticed Andy tapping the other two of them as well. Next, he mouthed the things he was trying to say.

"Wait for them to leave, and then spread out immediately! Don’t stop! The people from the marshall squad should be arriving soon. My black panther is leading them here."

"Understood," Garen nodded. The other two nodded silently as well.

The footsteps began to leave slowly.

Suddenly.

Waa… Waa…!

No one knew when the baby by Jessica’s side had woken up, and now he was crying loudly with his mouth wide open. Even though Jessica rushed to muffled his mouth, the noise had already escaped.

The sound of the footsteps stopped again.

Garen’s heart rose to the back of his throat. He saw Andy instructing him with his gaze: Spread out and run. He understood, the current black panther squad was still not as strong as it would be in the future. Two form one totem users, one disabled totem and his own support totem were up against at least three legitimate totem users, with one of them being a form two as well.

The difference in strength was far too large.

It was like a community policeman going up against a fully armoured special forces soldier. Not to mention that a form two totem user would possess specialized abilities, making the difference even greater.

"This is bad…" Garen could sense that the black robes had probably realised that they were hiding here.

"The noise from earlier probably came from here," said the black robed woman in a low voice.

The footsteps began to move towards the direction of the four youngsters.

Andy and Jessica’s faces were pale as ghosts, while Goth was grinding his teeth and balling his hands into tight fists, looking as if he was ready to burst out at any moment.

Garen’s heart began to sink.

"Found them! There really were people hiding here!" The woman in the black robe exclaimed loudly out of the blue.

"Run!" Andy roared loudly.

Garen grabbed a fistful of small stones and leaped out of the pit.

Tch tch tch!

The stones flew towards the sky and fell back down towards the black robes, unearthing a heap of soil and dust in the process.

********************

On top of a nearby slope.

Seven to eight White Horsemen followed a blank panther, rushing in the direction of the Black Panther squad.

The man leading the group was a White Horseman in black leather pants who wore a round brimmed woven straw hat, looking out of place. He had a scruffy beard growing on his chin, making him look quite different from the usual portrayal of the White Horsemen.

"Hurry up, everyone! Head to the small hill up in front!"

A woman in a similar straw hat followed closely behind him, furrowing her brows as she said: "Captain Jefferson, is there really any need for us marshalls to be called over for this? It’s just some bandits. Even if there were totem users they’d just be one or two stage one totems. It seems to me like someone’s making a big deal out of nothing."

"Just follow your orders, no need to question them," said the middle-aged leader impatiently. He kept his eyes fixated on what lay in front of him. "Everything would be easy if only it was so straightforward… Everyone, prepare to fight!"

At that moment, out of the seven or eight White Horsemen, five of them released their totems, illuminating their silver luminescence.

Jefferson put on a leather glove and stroked it gently as a ray of black light flew out of his palm and fell on his shoulder. Instantly, a black hawk with a red cockscomb on its head appeared.

The black hawk opened its beak, showing off its sharp saw-like black teeth.

Jefferson noticed that the black panther had began to growl softly in a worried manner.

"Pick up the speed!" He roared loudly. His right hand pointed towards the sky as he yelled: "Go!"

The black hawk let out a soft whistle-like ‘caw’ as it spread its powerful wings and raced towards the sky.

********************

"Ahnuxida!"

The black robed woman’s voice rang loudly in the air. Without Jessica here to translate, Garen couldn’t understand a word she was saying.

He leaped upwards and ran down the S-shaped road behind him.

Turning around to look back, he saw that the black robes had dispersed into a few groups to chase after Andy and Goth, while Jessica was holding the baby and hiding in another crack between some rocks.

The stones from earlier had barely scratched the black robes. When the stones crashed onto the surface of their clothes, they disintegrated into specs of beige coloured dust immediately,

A lot of the dust had been scattered everywhere by the wind, obstructing their vision.

Garen noticed that the leader of the black robes was now unconsciously moving towards Jessica’s location.

He narrowed his eyes and kicked a large rock.

Whoosh!

The rock flew towards the black robed man and hit his head, before turning into a pile of powder. The leader of the black robes let out a cold scream and spun around before laying his eyes on Garen. Meanwhile, the black python on his shoulder stuck its tongue out and hissed.

Garen trusted that Jessica had already seen what he was trying to do, so he turned around and ran.

"Jessica, the woman that Goth will end up falling in love with in the future. I’ve saved you once. This good deed will definitely be very valuable in the future." He continued to concentrate on the task at hand, and willed his legs to speed up as he dashed towards the slope behind him.

Suddenly, a bone-chilling sensation began to crawl up his body.

Garen spared no time before falling onto the floor and rolling down the slope. A ray of green light began travelling downwards from the top of his head.

The green light was like a thread. It shot straight in front onto a large rock. The white rock was immediately dyed into a large green mess, as the rock began to release a sizzling like sound of corrosion. The hard rock then began to melt into a sticky green puddle that flowed towards the ground.

Garen felt a gush of cold air emitting from his forehead, and dared not to conceal his power any longer. He stomped the ground with all his might and dashed forward, looking as if he was a white shadow racing down the slope in front.

"Gadate!" The sound of the black robed leader’s voice echoed behind him. The sizzling noise could be heard once again, as two rays of green line shot towards the slopes behind Garen, corroding the earth and stones nearby into a puddle of green, sticky liquid.

Garen refrained from turning his head but continued running down the slope instead. He covered his right elbow with his left hand, as his elbow had been slightly grazed by the green light earlier. There was a hole in his pale blue luminescence and his clothes were already starting to corrode. The cloth that had corroded turned into dots of green liquid that dripped on his skin, making him feel a searing pain as it touched his flesh.

Garen tore off his shirt and noticed that the milky skin on his elbow was now turning green. A little wound of rotting flesh had also appeared there.

This terrifying rotting ability, if it had happened to a normal person, their whole elbow would have rotted off by now. Garen toughened his heart before hooking a finger into the wound and digging out the rotting flesh.

At the bottom of the hill was a vast field. Not far away was a forest with patches of yellow and green-leafed coniferous trees. There were also lakes of various sizes that looked like mirrors, except that they were grey and seemed abnormally gloomy.

There were two little dots on the slope, one yellow and the other grey, that were going down the slope and rushing towards the field.

The yellow dot was moving at a rapid speed, and rushing down in an S-shaped path.

The black dot was much slower, and in front of it was a black python as thick as a fist, spanning the length of seven to eight meters, slithering forward. The black python lifted its head up suddenly, and shot a green light out of the third eye between its brows, straight ahead at Garen.

But not once did the green light manage to hit its target.

"Wandaxi, kashura!" The black robed man shouted angrily as he lunged forward and chased his opponent. He held a short black stick in his hand and kept pointing it at the yellow dot in front.

Both of them dashed forward, one in front and the other behind, before finally landing in the vast field.

Garen dived into the coniferous forest. After turning a few times, he jumped and braced himself against the tree trunk and somersaulted into the foliage. After that, he noticed the little lake in front and jumped down into the water. His whole body was submerged in the muddy water as he continued to swim deeper, holding his breath as he went.

The water in the lake was muddy and filled with soil and dust. However it was quite shallow, maybe only seven or eight meters deep. The bottom of the lake was mostly black mud.

Garen’s body shook slightly as he gently fell unto the mud, but it wasn’t a great fall as most of the mud remained in its original position. He lay face up with his body against the bottom of the lake and moved his shoulders carefully, unearthing some of the mud in the process and using it to cover himself.

A rustling noise emerged from the grass, as a large cluster of weeds were pushed aside.

The leader of the black robes rushed over angrily as his eyes scanned the entire area.

"Nuwataman!" He roared furiously.

The three-eyed black python was curled around his shoulders once again, and raised its head and made hissing noises.

It bowed its head slightly as its third eye suddenly shot out a ray of green light.

Tch!

The light shot onto the water in front, as well as the wild grass around the lake. The grass, soil, and stones all turned into a green sticky mess after being corroded by the green light.

The man in the black robe surveyed the area with his black python and walked around the lake for good measure, before running off to the area in front to continue his search there.

It was obvious that he was using the footprints on the ground as clues. Garen had jumped down directly from the tree, ensuring that not all of his footprints would be on the ground. The man was convinced that something wasn’t right, and decided to continue his search by crawling military-style instead.

The black robed man spent some time investigating the forest but failed to find anything. Suddenly, he raised his head and looked upwards.

Chirp!

There was a black hawk circling the sky and calling out in a ear piercing voice. The black hawk looked abnormal, because it had a red cockscomb growing out of the top of its head.

Garen continued to hide at the bottom of the lake, making sure to stay as still as possible. His aura could sense movements within a radius of slightly over two hundred meters in this area, and he could now feel the current location of the black robed man.

Bang!

Suddenly, a strong quake-like sensation shook the ground down to the bottom of the lake.

It seemed like a battle was going on outside. The sound of a hawk’s cry could also be heard vaguely.

A few minutes passed before the ground finally stopped moving again.

********************

Jefferson held the cockscomb black hawk in his right hand, as his eyes bore into the surrounding forest.

Some dark blood stains had seeped into the ground, and strips of black cloth were strewn all over.

In the fight just now, the leader of the black robes had been chased by him, and was heavily wounded. At this moment he was hiding somewhere and had left without a trace.

"Consider yourself lucky!" He said coldly, as he turned to leave.

The black robed man leaned against a tree trunk and panted heavily. His whole body was covered in a yellow-green sheen, the perfect camouflage colour.

He retrieved some medicine from his lap and hurriedly applied it on his shoulders. His forehead was filled with sweat droplets.

In an opening in the undergrowth nearby, he noticed that Jefferson could not find him, and had finally retreated, and was now walking away in a faraway direction. He assumed that the man was probably going to reunite with his other squad members.

The man in the black robe sighed in relief, and wiped the beads of sweat off his forehead. Only when Jefferson had finally disappear did he turn around and walk in the opposite direction. The sound of his footsteps were abnormally quiet, and he staggered when he walked, implying that he had suffered serious injuries.

He continued to turn back and check behind him as he walked. Suddenly, he heard a soft splash coming from the direction in front of him.

The black robed man felt his whole body stiffen, as his head turned around sharply to face the front.

Garen was standing in front of him with an expressionless look on his face.

"May the Gods become one, and may their divine punishment rain down on you!" He took a deep breath, as all the muscles on his body enlarged and expanded in an exaggerated manner.

Phoo!

A gust of wind blew over, and Garen’s physical body instantly leapt a few meters upwards. His palm came into direct contact with the middle of the man in the black robe’s forehead.

In a blink of an eye, everything quietened down.

His palm and the other man’s forehead were in direct equilibrium, and all noise ceased. In that moment, it seemed like everything in the world had become silent.

Bang!

The ground began to shake violently.

The platinum aura swept everything up, causing the blue light to explode in the middle of the black robed man’s eyes.

"Ahhhhhhhh!!!!"

The black robed man’s whole body began to emit black light, as his face distorted with every scream that escaped his mouth. After he was forced backwards, his eyes and mouth began to spurt out fresh blood unceasingly.

The spot where Garen had targeted was the wound where the man’s white luminescence had spilled out and had yet to heal.

Without any hesitation, Garen leapt upwards as his body emitted light and caused fragmented shadows to form. He shot as far as over ten meters away.

Rumble!

A thunderous noise sounded behind him, and a semi-circle shaped green light rippled in the distance and enlarged rapidly into an expanse of over a hundred meters. All of the areas within this vicinity became corroded into a puddle of sticky, green liquid.

Chapter 267: Gap 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

Boom!!!

A green shockwave burst outward on the soil in the yellowishgreen forest.

Garen used his aura to direct himself to the ground from the air. He gained his momentum and got out of the green shockwave’s area of effect and landed beside a small puddle. He took a few steps back as he landed, and he turned around to look at the green shockwave that had spread across the area as he stabilized his footing.

He raised his hand and looked at his right palm. It was glowing faintly in green, and there was white smoke coming out of it, with the surrounding filled with a sour and foul odor.

"What strong toxicity!"

He placed his palms down and gave them a gentle jitter. The green colored skin at the center of his palm sunexpectedly came off like green old cloth from the vibrations. The skin landed on the ground and immediately rotted the stones and soil into a greenish, viscous substance.

Garen’s right palm was instantly filled with blood, but a layer of dried blood formed and stopped bleeding in no time. He had presented that he had absolute control over his body.

This huge commotion would definitely grab someone’s attention.

He then saw that the plants that had instantly decayed the moment they came contact with the green shockwave.

"Damnit!" Garen’s expression changed as he cursed fiercely yet quietly. "Is every second form totem user this troublesome! They can even self destruct before they die!"

He was using his aura to stay aware of the battle between the Marshall squad and the man in the black robe. So why did he come out and ambush them at the end? It was because he wanted to obtain the intel and knowledge of the core totem from the man in black robe. Even if he didn’t manage to obtain the information he wanted, he could at the very least obtain some precious resources, right?

He didn’t expect him to self destruct at the end, and he couldn’t obtain anything any longer.

Without any hesitation, Garen left the place with great haste. Although he wanted to check out the place, he didn’t dare to enter as the core was so toxic that the air surrounding it was filled with its strong poison.

As he took a few steps, he stopped and turned around with a huge grin on his face. With a happy look on his face, he sped off into the distance and soon disappeared at the other end of the slope of forest.

Garen slowed down as he reached the shades in the forest. He then activated the neon butterflies and let them patrol around his head as he slowly went towards the place where the four people separated.

At the same time, he closed his eyes as he set his sights upon the attribute pane.

‘Strength 2.3, Agility 2.1, Vitality 2.5, Intelligence 2.1, Potential 1493%. Possess the qualification to become a Luminarist.’

His strength, vitality and intelligence had increased by an average of 0.1 and his potential points had increased from 12 to 14, and would become 15 fairly soon!

Garen started to think hard after feeling happy about it.

"It’s perfectly normal for the physical attributes to recover before it reached it peaks. However, my potential points have unexpectedly increased as well… Was it because I killed a Luminarist? I have just checked it yesterday, and there were no changes, and then there was a change the moment I had killed a Luminarist. If killing the Luminarist is not the cause of it, it will still definitely be linked to it!"

He was very sure of his assumption. His worry over the source of obtaining potential points had finally reduced slightly.

"Should I try to evolve neon butterfly now?" He immediately scratched off the thought; if he were to evolve the neon butterfly without any inherited knowledge, besides the extremely low success rate, the evolved neon butterfly would be impossible to hide. If that were to occur, how was he going to explain the evolution of the neon butterfly without any inherited knowledge to the others?

"Forget about it, I should find another core totem first."

After discovering a clue to obtaining potential points, Garen was determined to follow his original plan, which was to become the best Luminarist. As the risk and rewards were directly proportional to each other, he had to take a huge amount of risk to obtain a huge amount reward.

"This way, I just need to get through the crisis that will occur next year, and I can think of changing my totem afterwards. The second world war is going to last for years…" Garen had a plan in mind. With his eyes filled with determination, he sprinted off and he went forward.

As he went over the hill, he soon returned to where he parted with Goth and the others.

There were already a few people in the Marshall Squad’s white vests standing by the grey road. The middle aged team leader seemed to be discussing something softly with Jessica. There were no traces of anybody else.

Jessica burst into tears and rushed towards Garen as she saw Garen return.

"Garen! You’re okay!?" He ran towards him and held Garen’s hand tightly. "I thought you were…" Her tears almost went down her cheeks.

"I’m alright. I won’t die so easily, since I trained my body a bit back in the day." Garen patted himself on the chest. "Where is your brother, Goth and the others?"

"There’s still no news yet…" Jessica quickly wiped off her tears as she said sadly.

"Don’t worry. It will be fine since the one going after them is not the strongest." Garen comforted. "We will definitely earn a huge amount after this, since this mission’s difficulty is very high. The one who went after me was a second form totem user. If not for my speed as I jumped into the pond, I would have definitely not been able to return."

"So you were hiding in the pond." The middle aged man came forward as he showed him his white badge. "Jefferson, leader of the Marshall Squad. So you’re Garen? What a brave man for a fellow without a core totem to kite the second form totem user away. You deserve praise!" He commended Garen as he patted his shoulder. "Rest assured. You guys have done more than necessary for this mission. Naturally your reward will increase as well."

"Thank you team leader Jefferson." Garen acted flush as he wanted to get a closer relationship with him. After all, his age was much younger than this man. "I wonder how my two partners are doing?"

"Don’t worry. They will be fine. They were only kiting away the first form totem user. They should return before you know it." Jefferson smiled as he looked at the sky, in which there was a black eagle flying in circles.

"Alright, it’s time to cover up the influence. You know the rules right?" Jefferson whispered. "We will minimise the rumors of the battles between the totem users from the general public."

"Are we still able to cover this?" Garen whispered.

Jefferson frowned. "We’ll do what we can…"

He continued questioning Garen relating to the details of the leader of the men in black robes. He turned around and left as he gave his subordinates the orders after he was satisfied with the intel. Garen managed to convince him that he was able to escape from the pursuit due to his speed. After all, it was not surprising to see a totem user practice martial arts to make up for their lack of physical attributes.

After ten minutes of waiting, Andy, who was leaning on Goth appeared in Garen and Jessica’s sights.

"Are you two alright?"

Jessica and Garen quickly went up to welcome them.

"Andy injured his hips." Goth shook his head as he replied. "We would have return earlier if I carried him, but he insisted on walking on his own."

Andy had a miserable expression and felt like committing suicide at the thought of being princess-carried by Goth.

Jessica couldn’t help but burst into laughter when she saw goth’s hopeless face, and her brother’s embarrassment when they came back safely.

For some reason the term ‘hips’ was supposed to sound very normal. However, it became rather funny when the word came out of Goth’s mouth.

Even Garen couldn’t help but to reveal a hint of a smile.

"I’m glad you’re okay. Team leader Jefferson had said that he would increase our more rewards for this mission."

"I was just about to ask this!" Goth gave Garen a big thumbs up, whereas Andy gave a sigh of relief as he smile wryly.

"Okay. We need to take a good rest after this mission. What do you guys plan on doing now?" Andy voiced out. "I will talk about Jessica and my plan. We are currently living in the inner city’s Air Wing region and our address is No. 109 Vine Street. You should visit us when you’re free."

"Have you forgotten, brother? Father is sure to scold you when you go back with this injury…" Jessica softly added.

"Eh…" Andy started sweating cold sweat on his forehead.

Goth curled his lips as he scratched his chest with his hand.

"I live in Kovitan’s Main Street Region, the bread shop above the red wolf statue is opened by my mother. You can find me when you have any needs, and please let me in on any good missions as well. However, I think I will get scolded when I go back as well. My mum doesn’t like me being hired as a Luminarist…"

Garen started laughing as himself as the other three had finished their sentences.

"I am currently considered as a free man since my parents are overseas at the moment. I plan to travel around for a bit. I’m staying in a hotel at the moment. Let’s leave this place while we talk since all of us are planning to go back."

"Fine." "Alright."

The four of them wanted a stamp on their mission list as a personal validification from the Marshall Squad’s leader Jefferson. After that, they quickly went back to the Luminarist’s hiring guild in Iron Tank City.

Under the effect of Jefferson’s stamp, the mission was reevaluated to an active mission, which was a grade higher than the investigative mission that was originally given. They had obtained a total of fifty thousand silver rumbs.

They split the reward into five portions. Since Garen had managed to lure away a second form totem user, the other three insisted on giving him two portions worth of the reward, which was twenty thousand.

After a little bit of dispute, Garen didn’t argue any further and accepted the twenty thousand rumbs.

It was considered a huge sum for him currently.

It’s way too easy to earn money as a capable Luminarist.

The four of them parted ways after dividing the money. Goth and the other two went home since they were locals, whereas Garen, as an outsider could only stay in a hotel.

He was travelling alone for a while at the outskirts of the city.

The current situation had started to become slightly chaotic.

In the past, Luminarists existed far away from the civilizations. However, due to the outburst of conflicts between the Luminarists among the commoners, rumors regarding the Luminarists had started to spread in the commoner’s world.

The commoners had started to grow accustomed to the word Luminarist, or the specialised totem users.

The chaotic news kept spreading throughout the RAL via newspaper. The blue birds that were used to sent mails through the sky were consistently spread about in the sky. These types of blue pigeons possessed incredible speed and endurance. With its small and compact body, it could fly over ten thousand kilometers in a day. They were evolved from the falcon by the Luminarists via the second form support totem.

No matter how far away the recipient was, the news would definitely reach them within a week.

Garen bought a few pieces of newspaper on the street, and he noticed the news regarding the turmoil had started to gain traction. There were discussions regarding the duration, scope, degree and ultimate beneficiaries of the unrest everywhere.

As of now, no one had really realized the horror of this upcoming chaos.

After hanging around by the outskirts for some time, Garen started to enter the Iron Tank City.

The Iron Tank City was a big open style city. There were no walls covering the city and the buildings were densely packed from the inner perimeter to the outer circle. From a bird’s eye view, the city looked like a giant grey circle.

The buildings inside were either white or grey in color. This was to reflect enough sunlight away from the city to reduce the amount of heat energy.

Garen entered the city via the famed, half open city wall which could be found everywhre. There were stores selling snacks and fruits at both sides of the city gate. Garen bought a small fruit that resembled the roxburgh rose fruit, and ate it while he walked around.

Chapter 268: Gap 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

The price of resources had naturally increased as war was near approaching.

No one expected that the unrest would be this serious and would last this long. As a result, everyone had started collecting all kinds of resources like stocks, and took it as a form as an investment.

Garen went to at least ten rice shops in the inner city. He eventually found a cheaper shop and used all of his hard earned twenty thousand rumbs to buy rice.

He knew that the moment a large scale battle occurred, society at large would not be able to harvest rice, and the price would ultimately inflate to an unbelievable amount.

These investments do not require him to wait for a long time, and he would be able to earn at least ten times more.

Garen rented a warehouse at the deserted part of the inner city and placed all the rice he had, called green rice there. This rice was extremely filling and had high vitality, which meant that it was very easy to reproduce them. This was the main reason why they were so cheap. When the war occurred, this green rice would be very popular among the citizens due to its high satiety. This meant that they could be sold off at a higher price than regular rice.

Garen felt much more relieved as he had found a lead in obtaining more potential points. He had decided to mingle around in Iron Tank City. Vanderman and the Trejons Household were protected by the RAL and survived the first world war. The Trejons’ manor crisis would only surface during the second world war, when the Three Heroes were defeated and the RAL had collapsed.

There were still about a year before the crisis occurred and Garen decided to use this time to train himself.

There was still one month left before the war spreaded, and the Obscuro Society officially made a large-scale mobilization. Garen decided to use this month’s time to come up with a good plan.

After he finished dealing with the green rice, Garen rested for two days, and took two solo investigative quests. Both were relatively safe and did not have a high reward. It was only two thousand rumbs, which was better than nothing.

Furthermore, he did not encounter any Luminarist during the quests. He did, however, encounter a few General-class commoners.

*************

Bam.

The beer girl, who was as fat as a water bucket, placed a cup of beer, which was about the size of a water ladle, onto the table. The beer rocked about as a huge amount of foam bubbled to the top. A fully bearded customer picked it up and chugged it down without mercy.

Garen stopped looking at the adjacent table, instead choosing to quietly cut into his medium well steak with a small knife.

He sat at the quest hall that was filled with lights that resembled the sunset, surrounded by totem users and Beginner-level adepts. There were the high pitched sounds of beer bottles clashing into one another, people whispering among each other, drunkards shouting about and even people enquiring for information from the bouncer.

The air was filled with a mixture of the putrid smell of alcohol and vomit. It was horrendously nauseous.

The War Guild was completely different from the Luminarist Hiring Guild. It didn’t matter to the War Guild whether one was a Luminarist or a commoner, they only cared about the completion rate of the quests. There would only be business here when there were wars and would be completely deserted if there’s none.

The quests here were all high reward high risks quests. The lowest ranked quests that could be found here was the very risky quest of fighting against form 1 totem users. The relatively safe investigative quests were nowhere to be seen.

Garen had been here for the past few days, scouting for the quest that suited him the most. He had already completed three quests from the Luminarist Hiring Guild, and all of them were investigative quests. It was not challenging, and he didn’t have the opportunity to go against a Luminarist.

Hence, he came here.

"This is your quest." The beer girl with the waist the size of a bucket walked over and slammed a slightly crumpled piece of black, thin paper from the edge of Garen’s vision. She immediately left after placing down the piece of paper.

Garen picked it up, read it and quietly placed it inside his pocket.

The quest was very simple. It was to hunt a serial killer who had killed thirteen aristocrats from households in the inner city. The enemy was a form one totem user, and his totem was a leopard. He was also a rogue from the Obscuro Society’s outer circles. The Royal Alliance had started to invest a lot of money in attacking, and the Obscuro Society’s outer circle was one of the targets.

Garen wiped his lips with the handkerchief and stood up after he quietly ate the last piece of his steak.

"No. 25478 Has been revoked." A petite beer girl shouted from the quest counter as she wrote down the battle level and the latest quest onto the blackboard.

The battle level represented the highest level quest which the user had succeeded and it also represented the difficulty of this quest. The last quest was the quest where the numbered candidate failed. It was only when the death of the candidate was confirmed that the candidate’s number could be revoked.

This way, people would know the risk of the quest that was previously overlooked and prevent any weaklings from taking such a highly risked quest.

"It’s Lumba. I can’t believe he’s dead." "There’s at least ten numbers that have been revoked in this month alone. Looks like the situation is getting worse."

The hall was filled with discussions.

Garen stood up and left the hall with the quest receipt.

He didn’t have to do any investigation as the quest receipt contained the overall intel he needed in detail. The only thing he was required to do was to kill the target at the given time and location.

This was similar to an enforcer’s task. In the eyes of the royal government, The War Guild itself was the enforcer of the underworld. The employer of the War Guild was called the Hound, as in the Hounds of the Royal Alliance of Luminarists.

***************

A day later. 3.26pm in the afternoon.

Among the scorching golden sunlight, there was a small alley in the residential area of the outskirts of the city.

Garen silently stared at the man in white opposite him.

The opponent was in white long robes with a white scarf on top of his head. It was a classic arabian attire, which was also what a majority of the citizen’s wore here. The light colored shirt and scarf could reflect more sunlight and prevent the body from overheating.

It was a brown man with blue eyes. He had very deep eye sockets, and a pair of eyes covered in blood vessels. He looked so tired, as if he hadn’t rested for multiple days.

"Royal’s lackey!!" He shouted as he stared at Garen. He felt comfortable as he saw Garen’s weak totem light.

This Hound seemed to be a misfit. With such a weak totem light, he believed that Garen’s attack wouldn’t be very strong.

"Wayne Stain. Do you have any last words?" Garen whispered.

He gently threw a black compass-liked item. As it landed on the floor, it immediately spread and covered the area of about 100m in diameter.

Within seconds, the noise and wind from the outside world stopped appearing. It was as if both of them were separated from the rest of the world.

"Speak? You people won’t let me go even if I said anything." The opponent immediately replied. "You really are a Hound from the War Guild. You even brought along the War Prison. What else do you want me to say?"

"This thing can only separate us from the rest of the world for an hour. It’s more than enough time for us to solve the problem. "Garen shook his head. "Since you don’t feel like saying anything, let’s start."

"What a joke. With such a weak totem light you…" He didn’t even had the chance to finish his sentence, before he was unable to speak further, his eyes wide open.

With ten of his fingers, Garen pressed at least 10 pressure points on the opponent’s chest.

As he inhaled, the flow of air started to become turbulent and became a white gas surrounding his body, like a white ribbon. His body instantly expanded from 1.78 meters to at least 2 meters.

His usual thin body was instantly filled with muscles that were as strong as iron.

Huuuu….

The air that he gently exhaled became white, and blew away the pebbles as it flowed to the ground.

Under the golden light, a giant shadow was casted from Garen’s body and completely engulfed the target.

"Let’s start… Let’s see how big of a difference there is between the totem light and a commoner…"

"You’re not even going to use the totem light!!" The target had noticed that the blue light on Garen’s body had disappeared and gave off a shocked expression on his face. "You asked for it! You asked for it! Haha!"

He swung his right arm and a golden spotted leopard slowly came out from behind him.

Roar!!

The golden leopard opened its mouth widely as it leaped towards Garen.

"Divine Martial Fusion!" Garen’s body expanded once again and a circular faint white light was floating around his body. The glowing white light was a divine phenomena when the aura entered the body.

He clapped his hand and instantly disappeared.

Boom!!

A gigantic hand filled with blue veins landed onto Wayne Stain’s head. However, the attack was blocked by a thin layer of yellow light filament. When the palm came in contact with the light, the sound of one hitting a wood could be heard.

Garen clearly felt that as he attacked, it was as if his attack had pierced through a very deep pond and its momentum kept going deeper and deeper but it wouldn’t reach the end of the pond.

"Red Jade!" Both of his palms instantly became as red as jades and gave off an incredibly high temperature. The sizzling sound could be heard as he was holding onto Wayne Stain’s head.

The layer of yellow light seemed to be burnt by the high temperature as well.

"Since it can be burnt, it means that it can be depleted." Garen said without changing his expression. His body instantly disappeared and appeared behind Wayne Stain and avoided the golden leopard that was attacking him from behind.

Boom Boom!

Another two palm attacks were released onto Wayne Stain’s back.

"Thousand Mammoth Traction!!"

Air flow and the scream of the elephant surrounded Garen as he attack Wayne’s back with both of his palms.

Boom!

Strong wind blew from all directions and the deafening sound kept reverberating in the alley.

The yellow light finally started to vibrate and destabilize.

"You bastard!!" Before Wayne could even react, he was attacked by Garen four more times. His speed was so fast, even the golden leopard totem couldn’t keep up with his speed. "A Master-level adept? How stupid! Do you think you’re the only Master-level who are trying to go beyond the limits?!"

His yellow gemstone ring on his right hand lightened up and swiftly drew some sort of a symbol with both of his hands. A trail of yellow light followed his hand as he drew the symbol.

Without any hesitation, Garen avoided the attack at lightning speed. A trail of yellow light flashed past the position where Garen originally stood.

It was a basic support tactic; only the traditional Luminarist would combine their totem with such tactics. These kind of Luminarists were very rare and he didn’t expect to meet one here.

Unfortunately, Garen came from the same background as well. Although he couldn’t use any supportive tactics, he had knowledge in tactics as he learnt it from Emin.

The tactic Wayne was currently using was an attacking created by focusing the totem light. Its attack speed was incredibly fast, and its direction could be easily manipulated.

This skill was incredibly useful when used against the Master-levels of this world. However, its damage towards a Luminarist could be completely neglected.

Unfortunately, Garen wasn’t afraid of such an attack, due to his aura and his knowledge in supportive tactics.

Without making any sound, Garen rushed up towards him with a very calm look.

Chapter 269: Roll 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

Boom!

Garen’s fist once again landed onto the yellow totem light and at the same time, an incredible amount of pressure was consistently applied onto the yellow light filament.

The two of them were in the alley. Garen’s tall and strong body kept revolving around the target, and every time he attacked, he would simultaneously avoid the attack from the golden leopard.

Within the alley of the white buildings, a grey figure was constantly moving around the man in white at high speed, and a dense knocking sound could be consistently heard.

Wayne started to panic as his tactics were ineffective against him and his leopard was not able to catch up to him.

"What do you want?!" He started to shout.

Garen didn’t react and continue to gently place his palms onto him.

As the palms were in contact with the yellow layer of light, a huge bout of air was pushed away and the surrounding dust flew about in the air. Garen’s shirt was flying behind as well.

He took a step back and twisted his hand.

Boom!

He attacked the same location of the layer of light.

"West Phoenix!"

Garen placed his hands together and pierced forward.

Chirp!!

Two enormous wings appeared from his sides. The wings were shapeless, transparent and kept producing a clear chirping noise as it followed Garen’s hands as he strike forward.

Crack!

A small crack could finally be seen on the yellow totem light. The crack propagated throughout his body, and the yellow totem light was broken into pieces.

"No!! How is that possible??" Wayne was beyond horrified. He turned around and attempted to flee, but instead only saw garen.

As he fell to the ground, he stared at Garen with his big, bulging eyes.

"How dare you…!"

Screech!

The yellow totem light was shattered like glass into pieces and fell to the ground.

Like a raw egg, once the outer layer of shell cracked, the yellow light leaked out onto the ground like a liquid. In a matter of seconds, the liquid became transparent and completely disappeared.

Garen was lost in thought as he saw the scenario.

"No wonder my attacks were ineffective. You used a layer of shell to hold of the impacts, and then absorbed the energy by using the liquid.. A rather interesting structure. It reminds me of the structure of an egg."

"Don’t kill me… Don’t kill me!!" Wayne stood up in fear and attempted to ran out of the alley. The golden leopard was blocking Garen’s path and growled at him in rage.

Garen didn’t even look at the leopard and casually snapped his fingers.

Pew!

A stream of white gas fired from his fingers and pierced through Wayne’s brain from the back, which resulted in the blood splattering about freely.

The golden leopard scattered and transformed into a pool of silver liquid.

"Thirteen hits." Garen muttered. "With my current strength, I would require thirteen hits to break the totem light of a form one totem user…"

His strength was slowly recovering back to its peak, and his strength would soon be the same as when he fought Sylphalan. With that amount of power, he could pierce through a tank with just a single punch, and would only suffer minor injuries from a shell. The only thing that could harm him was a highly explosive bomb.

However at this strength, he would need to hit a form 1 totem user thirteen times to break his defense. If not for his knowledge towards the tactic, it would be hard for him to avoid such a fool proof attacking tactic.

Garen estimated that he took about two to three minutes to win against this world’s trash soldiers, which would not even be thought as trash in the future.

He suddenly thought of something and set his sight onto the attribute pane. The potential points have increased to 1512%, which was also 15 points. It was increased from 14 points, close to 15, and had now became 15 points.

"This means that I only gained 20 to 30% of potential by killing a form 1 totem user. Killing off a form 2 totem user gives so much more than this."

Garen frowned as he walked towards Wayne’s corpse. He started to fumble about the corpse and found a black leather pouch and a small black note.

He opened the money pouch and saw thick stacks of rumbs mixed with a type of green banknote. These green notes were tai, and were this country’s currency for small change.

Garen didn’t even bother to look at the tai,and took out the crumbs and he counted them. There were about fifty to sixty thousands crumbs, and even a passbook at the very bottom. However, he couldn’t withdraw the money as he did not have the password.

He placed the note and money into his bag and proceed to cut off Wayne’s ear. He then drained the blood from it before placing it inside a black napkin. After that, he picked up the black compass which was on the ground and left the area.

As Garen left the alley, he soon heard a girl screaming from behind him. Someone must have found the corpse after the War Prison was deactivated.

Garen, who was very poor now, would even collect molten silver if the silver could be recycled.

He threw away the pouch that was in his hand and went straight to the War Guild.

****************

Ten days later…

Garen was sitting quietly in the main hall of the War Guild, which was filled with the warm, yellow light.

He had a malt wine in his hand, and he would occasionally have a sip as he scanned his surroundings in the main hall.

In the past ten days, he had accepted another five hunting quests. Adding in the rewards he had obtained from killing Wayne, his total rewards added up to sixty four thousand rumbs, which was a fairly high amount.

All of his targets in all five quests were form 1 totem users.

Garen understood well the situation and position he was currently in. Due to his unique aura and secret martial arts, his strength had exceeded this world’s Master-level, and was on par with the form 1 Luminarists.

He gently touched his scar that was on his left side of his neck. It was a scar left by his second target. The target knew how to use Tactics, and they had been very mysterious as it could be activated by a word syllable. At that time, Garen took a huge hit by this surprise attack.

However, The Divine Statue Technique seemed to activate its effect well. Garen wasn’t split into half from that fierce attack, and only injured his neck. As the opponent was stunned by this feat, Garen managed to win this near-disastrous battle due to his speed.

Garen gently touched the scar on his neck. It was difficult to recover from the attack of a Tactics of the totem light. He required two days to fully recover, even with his Divine Statue Technique’s recovery speed.

He had an epiphany after fighting so many form 1 totem users.

Among them were different tiers; he had tried to obtain intel from the other Hounds after he suffered.

A typical form 1 totem users could be separated into two types.

The first one was a normal totem user. This type of totem users knew nothing and could only rely their totems and some basic Tactics to battle. Their strengths were heavily determined by their strength of totem and their battle strategy.

The second type was the one Garen met yesterday. There were the specially gifted totem users.

A form 1 user called Judra had a typical White Headed Black Hawk as his totem. What’s strange was that Judra seemed to have some of the totem abilities as well, which was superhuman vision.

He had already noticed Garen from afar and cunningly hid himself among the crowd.

These types of gifted totem users were very valuable and their strengths were beyond this world. This bastard Judra even had two Master-levels as his bodyguards who would protect him for 24 hours everyday.

At the same time, there were three other form 1 totem users approaching Garen as well.

Garen had no choice but to retreat and gave up on this mission.

He knew his limits as clear as day.

He could still manage if he were to go against one form 1 totem users. To fight against multiple at one go was too much for him.

The biggest threat to him was the totem user’s ability to possess Tactics. Although not all totem users were able to use Tactics, the totem users from the Obscuro Society seemed to have many who could.

The Tactic that was completely ineffective towards the totem users, but was the ultimate weapon to fight against the Master-level commoner. This was the difference between using a normal attack and a totem light.

Garen knew his place, which was equivalent to the form 1 totem user.

"Fifty four thousand… With the addition from the previous battle it should be almost time… The potential points have reached to 16 points. At this phase, it’s about time for Goth to explode."

Garen stood up and scanned his surroundings.

There were a lot of quests recently, and the originally cramped hall had become rather empty. Even the big bald man who was casually having a conversation with him was nowhere to be seen.

The Hounds duo that he obtained his intel from had their battle number written on the revoked blackboard. Clearly they had died on their previous mission.

The totem user who had partnered with Garen was also killed as well.

"The war is getting closer and closer… There are ten more days left before the movement spreads out, and the items that I have collected can be sold for a fortune. With the addition of rewards that I have collected during this time, I should be able to obtain some intel on the high level totems from the Obscuro Society. Naturally, everything starts after Goth moves out." Garen understood. "It’s time to see Goth and the others."

Goth was one the traditional heroes who were hardworking and gifted. He was very stubborn and couldn’t care less about other things except researching the Blackfield Birds. In addition to his gifted talent, his strength would eventually go beyond everyone’s imagination.

Garen’s objective was Goth’s key battle during his explosion.

During the battle, they had exploded one of Obscuro Society’s Totem Processing Associations. What was originally a simple investigative mission became a high risk confrontation mission.

What Garen wanted was the huge amount of totems that were yet to be activated from the Phantom Light totem light during this explosion. According to the images from his memories, the totems from the Phantom Light were just normal totems. However, there were still some high grade totems as well, and there was even a factory unit that was completely unaffected by the explosion.

If Garen could successfully obtain it, it would definitely result in a a huge leap and increment in strength.

He will then use the money and resources in his hands to fill in the intel that he lacked. He would then pick an outstanding core totem and evolve it using by his potential points. This was the plan that Garen had in mind a long time ago.

After sorting out his series of thoughts, Garen walked out of the main hall with a cheap grey robes which covered his scar on his neck.

Next, it’s time for him to participate in this risky quest.

Chapter 270: Roll 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

The Kovitan Empire

Vallarta Defense Department.

Inside a triangular and compact room.

Vanderman was sitting opposite two men with a stern look.

"Is there no other way to avert the situation?" He asked in a deep tone.

"Unfortunately, Vanderman. You and I have been pals for many years, even my son was under your guidance back then. I will act if I can. However, this time…" The man in white robe had a hopeless look on his face. "You need to be more proactive, and hopefully there would be an opportunity for you to turnaround."

"It would be very difficult." The other man in white robe shook his head. "As of now, there are a lot of crimes currently pointing towards you. They were accusing you of researching for a forbidden totem. The trial have already frozen the Trejons Household official accounts. I believe that it’s because you ignored the upper echelon and he decided to show no mercy and announce it to the public."

Vanderman was silent.

"That was years of my effort. They are forcing me to die…"

"They are still being considerate about you. Your teacher, Master Shylock had been trying to speak for you. You still have your influence so you don’t have to worry that much. However…" The man in white robe sighed.

"Alright, I will take my leave, as I have matters to attend to." One of the man in white robe stood up, patted Vanderman’s shoulder and left the room. As the door was closed, the footsteps became fainter and fainter.

Only Vanderman and one man in white robes were still inside the room.

"Perhaps there is still a chance." Vanderman’s gaze was cold as ice. "Ola, you’re involved in this experiment too. If this is exposed, neither of us will be able to escape. We need to think of something!"

The remaining man in white robe became cold and emotionless as he stood up to leave.

"Don’t worry too much, I will do what I can from my side. Let’s not panic, or we will fall into their hands."

"They are already at my doorstep!" Vanderman gritted his teeth. "A while ago there was a form 2 totem user that appeared near the manor! My son’s whereabouts are currently unknown! They have crossed the line!"

Ola looked at him. "Stay calm. You should be fine as long as you send out more people. They won’t lift their fingers since they’re only here to probe." He stood up as well. "Remember to stay calm. I will send some people to deal with this incident since they cross the line."

Vanderman looked at Ola leaving in disappointment.

These people were trying to protect themselves by using him as a shield, and didn’t even want to life a finger at all. The situation was getting dire for the Trejons Household. Everyone wanted to take credit for his many years of effort.

"The special ultimate form… I will eventually succeed! Just you wait!" He had placed all his hope on his own research product, which was a biological weapon that was made and controlled from medicine and Tactics.

"If I succeed, There should be at least one out of the three biological weapons that can become the ultimate form…"

Vanderman stood up and left the room.

Outside, there was a beautiful woman with big bosom and brown hair waiting for him on his right.

"Master, do you have any solutions?" The woman asked softly.

Vanderman shook his head. "Go back. I have been forced by them!"

"Master, don’t tell me you’re planning to use it already?" The woman was slightly shocked.

"There is no other way. My bank account has been frozen and my son’s whereabouts are unknown. The household is under a tremendous threat and there is no one else but myself to rely on." Vanderman was filled with rage. "It’s time to show my results to the public."

"Call Maxilan and Edney to return at once. It can’t be helped if they can’t find him. I can only hope that Cia is unharmed. We have to prepare for battle! The Obscuro Society will never show mercy to us."

"Understood."

*************

Lush Green District, Aquarius Manor.

At the white semi circular balcony, Aquarius, who was in a white dress, was holding the guard rail with both of her hands, her hair moving freely to the evening breeze.

The red evening light from the sun shone on one side of her body, revealing her seductive body curve.

"Is there any advancement from the Trejons Household?" Aquarius asked calmly.

Behind her was a beautiful girl in a yellow short skirt, kneeling down on one knee.

"The probing mission has been interrupted. There are a lot of totem users appearing in the Trejons manor, all of them are evolved form 2 totem users.

"Looks like the Trejons Household is plotting something big, and they seem to be hiding a lot of secrets." Aquarius started to laugh. "The Royal Alliance seem to not be willing to protect Vanderman anymore. That old man has been putting up with him for so long. Let’s see if he can keep it up this time."

"We are not sure if any form 3 totem users will appear in the manor. If the ultimate form appears, we may require you to move out as well." The girl in yellow skirt said softly.

"Ignore them. Let’s wait for a while more. We have more important things to do. When the time has come, we will deal with these eye sores." Aquarius waved her hand.

"Yes, Master." The girl in yellow skirt retreated.

Aquarius looked at the red sunset in the distance with a comfortable smile.

"Those two elders from the Royal Alliance, you’re already dead."

***************

Iron Tank City

Among the small district of white residential area, inside the three storey building located at the left side of the district.

Garen and the Andy brother and sister were sitting in the spacious living room on the first floor. Three of them were sitting in a row opposite the kind old man with white hair.

"Our home rarely has any visitors. I hadn’t expected a totem user to visit us. What an honor."

"You’re being polite, old man." Garen sat on the wooden sofa. "It’s just that I have not seen Andy and his sister for a while, so I’ve decided to visit them."

The old man nodded his head. His name was Xihande and he was a retired security deputy of the Iron Tank City, which was similar to the deputy director of public security bureau. In addition, he was also once a reasonably strong totem user, although he had not been in action due to old age.

"The two youngsters in my house have created their own team. At their age, all they think about is running around. I heard about the quest, the outcome might have been dire if not for you."

"Andy and his sisters would be fine even without me. You worry too much." Garen immediately replied.

"They? Hmph." The old man gave a hateful sigh. "Whatever. This old man isn’t going to be in the way of your conversation, so I will go up and read a book or two. You guys do whatever you want. Please take care of our guest you two, do you hear me?

"Loud and clear!" The siblings immediately replied.

The old man Xihande slowly walked up towards the second floor. The siblings finally relaxed after the footsteps disappeared into the distance.

Garen looked at the two of them as he laughed.

"Is he that scary?"

"You have no idea… My father is a high level form 2 totem user and he was no ordinary character. He has been torturing us for the past few days…" Andy looked as if he had suffered a lot. "Oh right, how’s Goth? We, the Panther Group haven’t been on the move for a long time. Isn’t it time to take on a quest? I don’t have enough money to spend lately…" He glanced at his sister Jessica.

"I’ve spent all my money on books." Jessica whispered. "Let’s listen to the old man and work in the security department." She was still traumatized by the previous incident. If it wasn’t for Garen, she would have been in grave danger.

As she thought of this, she looked at Garen with gratitude, as she thought of when to return him this favor.

"You know nothing. Freedom is the most blessful thing! Once you have joined the security department it will be difficult for you to leave!" Andy sighed. "Let’s find Goth and go pick up some quests."

"Whatever floats the boat." Garen shrugged his shoulder.

Under the lead of Andy, the trio left the building and went straight to Goth’s address.

They did find the bread store Goth mentioned, that was above the giant wolf statue.

Goth, who was in all grey went into the shop with bags of flour.

He was stunned as he saw the trio entered the shop and immediately ran towards them after placing down the flour.

"Why are you guys here?"

"We are preparing to take on some quests ,since our hands are tight on money lately." Andy scanned the bread shop. "Aren’t you a totem user? Why are you living off like this?"

"Shh… My mum doesn’t know I’m a totem user." Goth shook his head. "Plus, I did nothing last time and I feel ashamed for that…"

"Is there a better human shield, other than you?" Andy patted on Goth’s shoulder. "Let’s go, there’s nothing to think about."

"I don’t think I should go…" Goth recoiled. "I heard there are a lot of people dying on the outskirts…"

"If you earn more money, maybe you can revive your Blackfield Bird." Jessica couldn’t help but to butt in from the side.

Goth flinched, as if he was motivated by Jessica’s words.

"We will find some safe and easy quest. Have you used up all of your money?" Andy whispered.

Goth nodded.

"My mum took it away…"

"..." "..." "..."

"Goth, how old are you this year?" Garen couldn’t help but to ask.

"24." Goth answered sincerely. "Why do you ask?"

Garen was speechless. No matter how you looked at him, how could he become the Grand Duke of the future. Garen started to doubt if he had made a mistake.

The three of them tried to convince him, but eventually they dragged this guy as they moved out.

As the four of them left, a beautiful, gentle and long haired woman walked out of the bread store and looked at the back of the four of them leaving. Sigh.

As the four of them were in the city, they went to search for the latest newspaper at the bookstore Goth recommended.

The owner of the bookstore was a middle aged uncle who greeted Goth with laughter when he saw him. He allowed them to sit down and read the newspaper, free of charge. Judging from how he familiar he treated Goth, it was obvious that this wasn’t the first or second time he was here.

After understanding the overall situation, the four of them entered the totem repair shop which contained a variety of survival tools. The boss was a straightforward lady and gave the four of them 40% discount since Goth often helped her to carry stuff. She even helped everyone to maintain their totems.

Lastly, they went to a dry food shop. The owner was a kind old lady and was ecstatic when Goth called her grandma. She then stuffed everyone a big packet of biscuits and chocolate candies each.

After leaving the city, they went into the Luminarist Hiring Guild. The three of them were carrying packets of snacks as they looked at Goth with a questioning gaze. This guy seemed to be very popular.

Garen purposely followed from the back, and looked at the beginner quest that was hanging in front of them.

His gaze shrunk slightly .

Chapter 271: Investigation 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

"I knew it…" The investigative quest related to the wild and dangerous creatures’ nest was hanging up there. The name was "Nest Investigation". This was the important quest where Goth would explode the Obscuro Society’s nest.

This investigative quest would require one to investigate this so called dangerous creature’s nest. However, it was actually the Obscuro Society’s Totem Battlefield Processing Plant.

As the three of them were accepting the quest, Garen took a step back and scanned his surroundings.

These totem users were spiritually drained, tired, and most of them were injured. However, they did a good job in covering up. The head count was slightly less than before.

Garen overheard the lady who announced the quest that there was not enough people lately, and no one was willing to take the beginner level quests. On the other hand, commissioning quests had been stacking up day after day.

Dang dang… Dang dang… Dang dang…

Garen walked to the wall and looked to the distance through the window.

The tallest bell tower was ringing at the center of the Iron Tank City, which was white and circular.

With Garen’s superhuman vision, he could faintly see a lot of high level people in white robes with silver sleeves climbing up to the top of the tower beside the bell tower via the spiral staircase.

There were like termites climbing up trees.

"Meeting at the Spiral Tower, the highest level meeting of the Iron Tank City… I wonder what’s happened." Garen tried to suppress his curiosity.

"What’s wrong?" Andy patted Garen’s shoulder. "We have accepted the quest. Let’s go. The location is quite far away this time, since it’s located at HIlkan. It would take us four days to travel back and forth and we can’t take a carriage there. Fortunately the rewards are quite decent. Everyone will be getting five thousand and a transportation fee of two thousand."

"Sounds good." Garen smiled. "However Hilkan is rather far. Oh right, what’s the name of the quest?"

"Nest Investigation." Andy said casually.

"Andy, Are you guys going for the Nest Investigation as well?"

Suddenly a group of people came from behind them. The one who was leading the group was a youngster in a brown armor asked as he smiled.

Andy turned his head around and his facial expression dropped all of the sudden. "Are you doing this quest as well Cayduran?"

Cayduran, who was in the brown armor smiled.

A short haired macho man appeared behind him as he was putting away his silver dagger looked at Cayduran. "Friends of yours?"

Cayduran nodded.

"Sir Johnson, I will be staying back for a bit to have a chat with my friends."

"Sure, we will chat when we’re free." The short haired muscular guy nodded his head and brought a group of people passed Garen.

At the entrance of the main hall, Andy with his three team mates and Cayduran with his two other teammates gave some space to let the rest enter or exit the main hall.

However, these two had a healthy rivalry between them and they would never cross the line.

Cayduran pointed at the two teammates and said as he smiled.

"These two are the supports I have hired. My team has lost two people recently. Cana and Valerie are totem users from the Kovitan Empire."

One of these two, Valerie, was a man with a golden ponytail. This self proclaimed Valerie looked arrogant and ignorant. He only nodded to the rest he was being introduced.

The other girl was called Cana, who looked at Andy’s team members. She immediately ignored Jessica due to her mediocre figure and face, who graduated from school and kept training herself. Along the road on her training, she had seen most sides of human beings.

Her sight stopped for a moment as it landed on Andy and Goth, and soon set her sight onto the handsome Garen.

"What a coincidence. Garen here is from Kovitan as well." Andy smiled.

"You’re from Kovitan?" Cana’s interested peaked as she looked at Garen.

This woman had both butt and bosom, and had an above average look. Her purple hair was at shoulder height and there were free strands hanging on her chests as well, which made her bosoms looked even more filling.

Garen answered by nodding and smiling politely.

"Which part of Kovitan are you from? Perhaps we are from the same hometown." Cana felt that among this group, Garen had a passable facial figure and looked sexy due to his good fitnesse as well. In addition to these, he was a totem user and this made him even slightly more interesting.

Among the totem users in Kovitan, there are a lot of disciples voluntarily travelled around the world to train themselves but accepting quests. There were a lot of them doing this everywhere.

Although she was from just a merchant household, her siblings who were in a similar social status had changed for the better when they became the significant other of these disciples. What they currently eat was of a different class, as if their lifestyle had completely changed.

They, who came from the merchant household were naturally not competent against the aristocrats. These sisters had became the center of everyone’s attention when they went for a gathering. The foods they ate and the clothes they wore everyday were something only an aristocrat could get hold of, and the places they went to could not be accessed by any typical person.

Even totem users could not simply get into the circle of the aristocrats. The totem users with an aristocratic background, on the other hand, were who she had been looking for.

Perhaps this fellow was an aristocrat who had came out to train himself?

Cana assessed Garen carefully. She had seen a lot of people along the journey but she had never met someone who was as handsome as Garen. Most importantly, this person’s skin was almost as smooth as hers. She couldn’t help herself but to fall for him the moment she saw him.

"I am from the lush green area." Garen smiled as he replied

"Oh, lush green. I have been there for a vacation. It’s a nice place with good air quality and the environment is very beautiful. My sisters and I had only been to the Ivy Park and the environment there was superb. The squirrels there are not afraid of humans and they even asked food from us." Cana smiled.

Garen had never heard of Ivy Park, but he went along with it and smiled as he listened to Cana’s conversation regarding her time in the park.

On one end, the atmosphere between Cayduran and Andy was not enjoyable. On the other hand, Garen and Cana seemed to be enjoying their time talking casually.

Jessica, Goth and Valerie started to talk as they had nothing better to do.

Valerie felt unease and frowned as he noticed Cana’s warming attitude towards Garen.

Cana and Valerie came from the same sect, and they went on a journey together as well. He always had some feelings for her and he couldn’t help to feel jealous when he saw Cana having a great time with Garen.

As he was chatting with Jessica, he always kept a constant eye on Garen and Cana.

Garen noticed it and he didn’t want to cause any trouble. However, the current situation was that Cana initiated the conversation with her. As a beautiful and well figured lady who came and initiate a conversation with him, he could only listen and look, even if he didn’t have the intention of having a conversation with her. He couldn’t just push the person away as it would offend her as well..

After a few exchanges of words, Andy and Cayduran felt irritated towards one another. However, they kept the conversation going as all of them were of the same rank. The current situation outside was rather dire, so both of them had some intention of working together since they were all form 1 totem users.

After a few words, both teams decided to work together.

They rented a few horses from the stable, brought along the survival tools and tent and separated into two groups.

These two teams merged together and soon exited the suburbs and entered the the highway.

The distance between Hilkan and Iron Tank City was very far. The road during the beginning of the journey was rather easy, but its difficulty inreased as they approached their destination. The map they bought recommended using a horse as their main transportation, not carriages.

Everyone had their own horses, as they sprinted forward along the highway.

Along the journey, Cana would intentionally get closer to Garen and occasionally crack a joke or two. Two of them slowly got to know each other better.

Valerie’s expression got worse along the journey as he looked at Garen with jealousy.

He understood well that totem users who came out to train themselves were mostly members from their local sects. Although the numbers of a noble totem users weren’t little, they were considered the minority.

If Garen was a noble, he would be totally different from the merchants as most of the totem evolving techniques were in the hands of the aristocrats. The was a huge difference between a typical totem users and a noble totem user. A typical totem users might spend a few decades to become form 2 totem users, which was considered very strong. On the other hand, the nobles had the opportunity to attain the third form. Furthermore, both parties had different amount of resources, as the nobles would have more Tactics compared to the typical totem users in terms of support and attacks. The typical totem users and noble totem users had a different starting point from the very beginning.

He would not want to mess with Garen if he really were a noble.

Along the road, Goth and Jessica were at the back, Andy and Cayduran were at the front with Garen, Valerie and Cana in the middle.

After a few hours on the road, two teams stopped for a rest to eat some dry food and water. They also took this opportunity to separate their work clearly. Although Andy and Cayduran didn’t get along very well, they do know each other very well since they grew up together. They would rather work together than to work with other people because they at least knew each other’s personality.

After they came to an agreement in terms of splitting the rewards, they continued on their journey.

As the night approached, the group started to set up the tent between the river and the road.

As Garen wasn’t experienced in setting up the tent, Cana came and gave him a hand and nailed the wood onto the ground to stabilize the tent.

"Have you not slept inside a tent before?" Cana asked as she helped out.

"Yeah, I have never done this before." Garen shook his head. This world’s tents were very detailed and sturdy, and would require every foundation to be set up straight in order to work. He indeed had never done this before.

As Cana heard his answer, she was even surer of her assumption. Every totem user should know how to set up this tent, as it was one of the must-bring equipment when one went outside. Since Garen didn’t know how to use it, it was obvious that someone had been helping him to set it up.

Her smile became sweeter as she thought of this. If she could get a hold of a noble disciple, she would be able to obtain the evolving techniques and the remaining resources in the future. Her chances of becoming a form 2 totem user would greatly increase as well.

"I have a self inflating tent. I will give you one later, it’s the latest product." Cana smiled as she said.

"It’s alright. This tent is decent enough."

"It’s alright, it’s just a tent anyway." Cana turned around and came back in a short while. Before Garen could even open his mouth, she placed some sort of a black stick towards Garen’s arms. "I still have a lot of these so don’t worry about it. Take it as a token of our newly formed friendship." Although she said that on the surface, her heart couldn’t help but ache as she passed it to him. These inflating tent made use of chemicals to inflate and deflate at will and its price wasn’t cheap. However, she believed it’s a must to ensure the foundation of this friendship needed to be firm and sturdy.

Chapter 272: Investigation 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

Two days later.

Evening.

On the wide grassy plains, behind a little hill, there were two yellow bonfires within close proximity of each other, emitting two yellow halos of light.

The two groups of people surrounded each bonfire, each doing their own preparations.

"Garen, you’re in charge of tonight’s recon, we’ll be counting on you for the night," Andy said to Garen softly.

"You guys can go ahead and sleep, relax." Garen nodded, and stood.

Reconnaissance was mostly up to him and Valerie, because both of them used flying type totems. Valerie’s was a small bluebird, which flew at high speeds and could be used as a messenger.

After delegating their work these past two days, they had started getting more familiar with one another.

Cana and Valerie sat beside their captain, baking by the bonfire. When they saw Garen stand, Cana finally couldn’t help but ask,

"Cayduran, what on earth is Garen’s core totem? Why have I only seen him using the neon butterfly as his totem this few days? That’s a very unpopular kind of totem, isn’t it, I don’t think anyone’s even researched how to further improve on it."

Cayduran was stoking the bonfire, and raised his head when she said that, looking at her in surprise.

"I’m telling you to stay away from him, his core totem? You’re the closest to him, and you still don’t know?"

"Know what?" Cana asked, frowning.

"This Garen doesn’t have a core totem, he only does recon in his team." Cayduran looked at Cana curiously. "If you think he’s some rich noble kid, you’re wrong. That Garen was working at a totem repair shop by the nightmarket back there, and Andy only pulled him into the team later. Even if he’s nobility, he’d only be washed-out nobility. That’s why I advised you to get all your facts straight before you make any plans. I thought you knew."

Cana was rather stunned.

She never guessed that the answer she was looking for all this time would be that simple.

But she still had more faith in her own judgment. This Garen had an aura she just couldn’t see through, in other words he was really weird. There was no way he was just a normal totem user.

"Stop fantasizing, nobles always take their own safety very seriously. Without even a core totem, he can’t even guarantee his safety on a mission like this." Valerie couldn’t help but speak, "That guy is actually the weakest in our team." He had long since been unhappy with Garen. Every time he saw Cana initiate a conversation with Garen and get a cold shoulder in return, sparks flew in his heart.

"Let’s wait and see…" Cana frowned and said softly, but her passion had also been doused. She was beginning to doubt her own theory.

Early the next morning

Garen kept away his neon butterfly, preparing to mount his horse and rest for a moment by taking a nap. The horse would be led forward by the connecting ropes anyway.

He soon realized that Cana, who would usually approach him for a chat, had gotten a lot colder, riding her own horse as she chatted with Valerie.

It was a rare moment of peace for him, so he slowed down his horse and created a little distance between them. He began to check his current condition.

After hunting down so many missions for the War Guild, he was also beginning to understand some things about Luminarists.

Most totems were divided into two types, Seraph Lights and Phantom Lights. There were fewer Phantom Lights, but each of these were extremely strong. The scar on Garen’s neck was left by a Phantom Light.

He was aware that he didn’t have a core totem yet, so his abilities plus his secret techniques only added up to the level of a Form 1 Phantom Light, equal to a peak Form 1 totem user. But if he was to go against a Form 2 totem user face to face, then he would be way out of league.

In the two small teams present here, only Andy and Cayduran were slightly stronger. When it came to controlling totems and the strength of their Totem Light, the two of them were the strongest, and that made them the main fighting force in head-on confrontations. The others were all rookies, at the same level as the general average. They were all relying on their totem’s attack type, and determining their strength by the strength of their totems.

As a thought occurred to him, he saw that in front of him, Cayduran was whispering something into Valerie’s ear. Cayduran nodded, and turned around to look at Garen.

"Garen, we need to check that small patch of forest ahead on the left, we’ll have to rely on your butterfly for a bit."

Garen nodded, and pulled out his silver-colored short staff to release the neon butterfly. He then let it patrol around the small forest ahead on the right.

Finding nothing, the neon butterfly returned, and the team continued forward.

Not long later, just as Garen was getting ready to rest, he heard another call from ahead.

"Garen, don’t sleep yet, something seems to have come up behind us, go send the neon butterfly to take a look," Valerie said loudly.

Garen had stood guard all night last night, and was just growing sleepy. He planned to rest, and recover a bit. Upon hearing that, he opened his eyes and frowned.

"Valerie, your totem is a flying type too, why are you always making Big Brother Garen do the work?" Jessica asked, slightly unhappily.

"He’s the weakest, so he should work more," Valerie said smoothly with a pout.

"Forget it, it’s fine." Garen didn’t want to pick a bone with this team either. This assignment was extremely important to him, he didn’t want to influence the path of history too much.

Releasing the neon butterfly, he let it take a round behind them, chasing away a few young deer. Only then did it return to rest on Garen’s shoulder.

They slowed down their horses, proceeding at a speed that was neither fast nor slow. The group decided they might as well settle their food and drink on horseback. It was only in the afternoon that they stopped to let the horses rest and drink.

In the afternoon.

Cana hesitated for a while, but still came over to chat a bit with Garen. Valerie was instantly put off. From what the captain said, he finally understood that Garen wasn’t any noble at all. Even if he was, he’d just be a washed-out one, and so he posed no threat at all. Seeing Cana approach Garen even now, the discomfort in his heart got even stronger.

"Garen, I’m a little tired, so I’ll take a nap now. I’ll leave patrolling to you." Valerie walked up to Garen and said loudly.

"What do you mean by that?" Beside him, Andy frowned and stood up. "You’re supposed to patrol during the daytime, right?"

"It’s okay, it’s okay." Garen didn’t say anything more. His endurance was out of this world, he trained in the secret techniques, and his spiritual power was brimming, so this little bit was nothing to him. This assignment was related to Goth’s explosion, and it affected the variables that might appear after he joined the team. He didn’t want to completely fall out with Cayduran’s side over such a small matter. After all, in the images in his memoriesm Cayduran and the others had gone into the caves together too.

Seeing that Garen himself wasn’t bothered about it, Andy and Goth, who was just about to stand up, couldn’t interfere much either. Both of them sat back down.

As requested, Garen began to patrol the surroundings immediately.

When he stood up, however, Valerie said to him in a soft voice,

"This is just a little lesson for you. If you understand, then you’d better leave Cana alone, otherwise it won’t be this easy next time."

Garen almost wanted to laugh.

This brat actually dared to threaten him. This mother-suckling brat, without a whiff of blood on him, actually dared to stand directly in front and threaten him, face to face.

If he weren’t so scared of causing too many changes, creating too many variables in this mission, he would have long ago given this kid a tight slap.

After one round of patrolling, he returned to the temporary camp. Garen approached Goth and sat down next to him. Seeing the way Goth ate half a baguette in one bite, gorging himself like a pig, Garen suddenly felt especially hungry. He picked up the rock-hard baguette, dipped it into ketchup, and enjoyed it more than he thought he would.

"Garen, go fetch some water from around here." Valerie’s voice sounded again.

"Hey, what’s the matter with you?" Goth got to his feet in an instant. "You got legs and hands, can’t you get it yourself?"

Valerie stood as well, laughing coldly. "Someone who doesn’t even have a core totem would be a burden anyway, why should we give him a portion of the money if he doesn’t do a little something? Anyone on this team can contribute to the team, and fight for the team. He’s the only exception, not only is his totem so weak, it’s not even a core totem. He can only be a burden for the team."

"Alright, Valerie, isn’t that enough?" Cana finally had enough, standing up as she said coldly, "Don’t make me look down on you!"

"Alright, alright, no more fighting." Andy and Cayduran both got up. Cayduran glanced at Garen, frowning, "This matter ends here."

Valerie glared at Garen. Since he was scolded by Cana just now, he was even more pissed off than before.

The two teams suddenly stopped talking to each other and sat separately on two sides.

After getting enough rest, they continued on their journey.

Although Cana now knew that Garen wasn’t any nobleman like she had hoped, but she still couldn’t act like how Valerie did. She didn’t want the two teams to split over something like this. So she still sought Garen out and personally apologized, followed by a short chat.

Unfortunately, when Valerie, who was just rather annoyed, saw that Cana still insisted on sucking up to Garen, he got even angrier.

Looking at his dark expression, it was clear that he had begun to hate Garen.

A full four days passed.

The two teams began to slowly enter the wilderness. The surrounding cottages and hunting houses grew sparser and sparser, and eventually disappeared altogether.

There were more and more weeds on the road, almost enough to cover the surface of the road entirely. And this was covered by a lot of loose pebbles.

The two captains gathered together, holding the map and tracing the route. Soon enough, they left the road for cars and horses, following a narrow dirt road, turning into some other unknown territory.

Everywhere around them, there were endlessly vast expanses of grassy green fields, and almost no trace of humanity whatsoever. The spattering of woods also grew fewer, as they had evidently arrived at the dirt plains.

The team continued pushing forth, eventually finding the little mound that looked like a pitchfork.1 The whole team stopped.

"This is where we start." Andy held up the map to compare.

"There’s blood here!" Cayduran crouched behind the little mound and said loudly, "The assignment description said that a few people disappeared here, leaving behind traces of blood and fighting. Seems like we got the right place."

The others quickly hurried to look, and saw that there were some clots of dried red-black blood on the grass. The soil underneath had also been dyed dark red, making it very obvious to the eye.

"Thank goodness it didn’t rain these few days, so the blood stains weren’t completely washed away," Cayduran said in a low voice. "Check the map, how should we go from here? If I wasn’t wrong, there should be a bandits’ nest nearby."

"The assignment mentioned that regular city guards came here to check a couple times, but the never found anything. That’s why they handed the assignment over to the Guild. But I bet they’re just slightly more cunning normal people, it shouldn’t be much of a problem." Andy walked over and spread open the map as he said, "If we search right from here, we should be able to an underground cave. The last time the city guards went in, five days before we received the mission, it was too dark inside, and they couldn’t advance because there were too many traps and switches. After a few of them got hurt, the city guards came back out, but mentioned it on the assignment."

"C’mon, let’s go in and look." Cayduran stood up.

Translator's Thoughts

J_Squared J_Squared

Lit. 山字形, meaning a mountain that looks like the Chinese word for ‘mountain’ (山). It does look like a pitchfork, don’t it?

Chapter 273: Entrance 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

The group walked along the mound, and entered a small patch of woods to their right.

In the midst of the forest, a pitch black pit gaped open at a slant on the grassy ground. It was surrounded by vines and grass, and they could only vaguely feel the cold draft rushing out from between the cracks.

Andy went forth, using his hunting knife to cut apart some of the wild growth, revealing the entire cave.

He lowered his head, and immediately saw a row of faint footprints on the ground. Some grass had been flattened underfoot, and had yet to bounce back up completely.

"It’s here." Andy pointed ahead, and a black shadow darted out from behind him, leaping into the cave with a whoosh. "I sent Black Panther ahead, please wait for a moment, guys."

The group scattered and stood apart, constantly aware of the surrounding situation.

A black wolf appeared by Cayduran’s feet, white smoke bubbling from its mouth. It was evidently a Fire Wolf that had been raised to a very high level, almost approaching Form 2.

His hand moved slightly, and the Black Wolf immediately stood up, and began to walk casual circles around the surrounding forests.

Everyone was on alert. This was a bandits’ cave, and they needed to be constantly aware of any movements around them. After all, several batches of city guards had already perished here. The other side would surely anticipate stronger reinforcements to follow.

Garen stood beside Goth, the neon butterfly perched on his shoulder.

He knew very well that there weren’t just any normal bandits in this cave, but an extremely powerful Luminarist.

The Totem Light would only demonstrate its own defensive power when similarly attacked by Totem Light.

With his current Neon Butterfly’s defensive power, even twice of that wouldn’t be anything in front of regular totems. Even a Black Wolf would be able to break through his defense easily. Garen was mainly relying on his own Divine Statue Technique for defense. Due to the different in quality, the Divine Statue Technique’s Body Hardening Technique couldn’t be all that powerful against the Totem Light either.

Garen compared himself, and after adding the two together, he decided he was more or less equal to Andy’s Black Panther.

"Cayduran, your Black Wolf is almost Form 2, isn’t it?" Jessica started talking to Cayduran quietly. The two of them grew up together, and although Jessica’s older brother didn’t get along with Cayduran, Jessica herself was pretty friendly with him.

"There’s still a long way yet. Although I managed to find some ways to raise it, there’s still some distance to go before it reaches Fire Wolf level." Cayduran shook his head. "The later part of evolution is an upgrade in total quality, too many people get stuck here."

Jessica found some questions about evolution and start chatting idly with Cayduran, as a way to kill time.

Cana had her hands tied with Valerie, but no one knew what they were talking about.

Garen released his Neon Butterfly to make patrols in the sky over his head, paying close attention to anything that might happen.

Goth, on the other hand, released that ink-colored Blackfield Bird. It was just a wooden bird, that couldn’t do anything but move its eyes.

By then, Andy had also more or less completed his scouting. Frowning, he turned around and said, "There’s a fork in the road ahead. Two roads, do you want to go on?"

Cayduran hesitated.

"It shouldn’t be too big a problem, they’re just bandits. I myself cleaned up a lot on my own before, and that was totally fine."

"What if we’re sealed inside?" Jessica began to hesitate.

"It’s fine, I know penetration tactics, I can open up a tunnel in a second. As long as there isn’t Totem Light in the way, we don’t have to worry about any other materials," Cayduran replied with a smile.

"I’ll be the one to lead my sister, I don’t need your crap." Andy gave him an angry glance.

"Would it kill you to keep your mouth clean!" Cayduran was mad too. "Forget it, we’ll go in first. When we reach the fork, we’ll each take one side, just read the signals when we get there. Let’s go."

He led the Black Wolf down into the tunnel, followed closely by Cana. And then Valerie glared at Garen with disdain, chasing behind Cana.

"We’ll go too." Andy waved his hand, and was the first to enter. He held a small white ball in his hand, but Garen didn’t know what it was. Judging by the expression of wariness on his face, it evidently wasn’t any normal item.

Goth went second, Jessica third, and Garen was the very last.

It was pitch black in the tunnel, and all they could hear was the smattering of Andy’s footsteps from ahead.

Garen followed behind the three of them, feeling the air grow colder and colder, and the tunnel grew wider. Cayduran and the others, who had gone ahead, were gone without a trace.

"Be careful, don’t get left behind," Andy’s voice came from the furthest front.

"I know." "Relax."

The three of them replied in turn. In these pitch black surroundings, the four of them couldn’t see very well with their eyes, so they had to follow behind Andy’s Black Panther to advance. The Black Panther’s brilliant green eyes shone slightly luminescent in the darkness, like two oval emeralds.

After walking another distance, Andy suddenly stopped.

"We’ve reached the fork. They took the left side, we’ll do the right."

The group continued advancing down the right side, and quickly came across yet another fork in the road.

"Wait!" Andy’s voice suddenly held a hint of anxiety.

He walked a little further forward, to the front of the Black Panther, and took out two flints from his pocket

Hiss!

The spark lit and died in the darkness, followed by the soft rustle of burning. The small torch Andy had prepared was instantly lit up, and it lit up the rest of the cave as well.

"There’s some trouble…" Under the bright red firelight, Andy’s complexion changed slightly.

The other three quickly hurried up to him.

"What’s the matter?" Goth approached him.

"Ah!" Jessica suddenly clapped her hand to her mouth and took one step back.

Garen saw it too. In front of Andy, there was the naked corpse of a man hanging upside down.

The corpse had brown hair and deathly pale skin. A large hole had been dug out of his abdomen, with swarms of maggots and black ants crawling around within.

The man’s eyes were opened wide, as though he had encountered something especially painful.

With a whoosh, the Black Panther leapt up and cut the rope suspending the body with one wipe of its paw.

The corpse fell to the ground with a whumpf, landing next to Andy. He crouched down to examine it closely.

"He’s been dead for four or five days, but he doesn’t stink at all… This damned bandits!" He turned the corpse, and pulled a short black arrow from his back. Andy looked at the color of the arrow tip carefully, and his expression changed.

"Garen, you don’t have an automatically activating Totem Light, so you stand guard at the cave entrance. The others, come with me and don’t get left behind, we’ll have to speed up. These damned bandits! Jessica, you’re okay?" Andy glanced at his younger sister.

"It’s nothing, I’m perfectly fine." Jessica’s chest was heaving non-stop, but she still forced herself to keep her emotions steady.

"Goth, you protect Jessica. Although your Blackfield Bird can’t move, its skin is very hard, and its feathers can deflect impacts. Your job is to defend Jessica from any Totem Light attacks nearby. Garen, you stay outside. This place is too dangerous for you, your Totem Light can’t activate automatically, and you have to control it yourself, so it’s likely you can’t block hidden poisonous arrows attacks." Andy started delegating jobs one by one.

"That’s why we need you to stealthily protect the cave entrance. Only then can we make use of your strengths, is that alright?"

Garen nodded solemnly.

"Leave it to me." He had long since made plans of his own, so naturally he would agree at this point.

"Then we’ll leave it at that, let’s head out!" Andy barked the order, and the Black Panther led the way as the three of them quickly ran ahead.

Garen started retreating to the back. At first his speed was average, but once there weren’t any footsteps or firelight ahead of him, he began to speed up. The lightless surroundings had no effect on him whatsoever.

His highly capable physical attributes made his five senses extra powerful, so naturally his eyes and ears could clearly replicate the conditions he just saw before.

Soon enough, he had returned to the first fork in the road.

"Eh?"

Suddenly he paused for a moment. He realized that the tunnel ahead that led back to the entrance had somehow vanished completely, replaced by a stone wall that was exactly like the surroundings.

If he didn’t have extraordinary memory, and memorized the traits of this exact spot, he would have probably assumed he took a wrong turn.

The Y-shaped tunnel had suddenly become V-shaped, the path back was gone.

Garen reached out his hand to touch the stone wall, it was very hard rock.

"As expected, we’ve been discovered." He hesitated, and then ran faster down the corridors Cayduran and co had taken. The Neon Butterfly rested on his shoulder, emitting a gentle, pale blue light, so he could clearly see the things around him.

In no time at all, there was another fork in front him. He crouched down to look at the footsteps on the ground, they led to the left.

He stood up and dashed down the right.

After taking a few more turn, running about a few kilometers of distance, he vaguely saw firelight ahead.

"Who’s there!!" A piercing woman’s voice came from ahead. A short-haired woman walked out from the tunnels ahead, still putting on her clothes. She was in her early twenties and had a decent figure, a thin waist, a delicate chest, her unbuttoned collar revealing a white lace bra.

There was a dent in the wall on the woman’s left. Inside, there was a candle on a wooden trunk, and the candlelight also illuminated a semicircular bed.

After waiting so long without a reply, the woman’s rather plain face looked confused.

"Is it Ada? Stop joking around."

And still no one replied.

The woman picked up a dagger that was lying on the wooden crate and arched her body like a female panther, as she slowly began to move.

Whoosh!

Suddenly there was a gush of cold wind, lightly stinging the woman’s widened eyes. She instantly blinked them.

She couldn’t help but rub her eyes, but there wasn’t anything out of place at all in the tunnel.

"Did I hear wrong?" she murmured, straightened up, and returned to sitting on her bed. Then she took her clothes, bra, and underwear, then actually pulled up the covers and went to sleep naked.

Garen stood on the other end quietly. In the instant where the wind blew just now, he had already darted past this woman in the blink of an eye, reaching the other side.

This guard woman was only a Soldier-level who had done a bit of training, there was no way she could notice his peak Master-level speed.

After getting past this patrol point, Garen continued running ahead soundlessly.

His speed was exceedingly fast, like a gust of wind.

With a smack, his leather breeches stepped past the ground. Before the underground spikes of the trap could even snap up, he had already gone past the trap and was several meters away.

As he flitted past, poison arrows shot out from the walls on both sides, and rope nooses appeared suddenly on the ground, ready to hang someone upside down at any moment. The further ahead he went, the more traps there were.

Some higher difficulty compound traps also started appearing, with many things like poisonous liquids or powders.

There were even two Form 1 venomous wasp totems resting in two dents on either side of the tunnel.

Relying on his speed, Garen dashed past the Wasps in an instant, but he had barely taken a few steps before several black bats flew down from the ceiling ahead.

Chapter 274: Entrance 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

Squawk!

The bats screeched as they pounced at Garen. There was actually the pale black glow of Totem Light on their bodies.

Garen hurriedly avoided them, retreating backwards to avoid the bats’ attack.

"Someone came in! Don’t you know this area is restricted!"

A man’s deep voice came from the tunnel ahead.

It was a skinhead who wore a black robe and had four red stripes on his collar who suddenly appeared in the tunnel ahead. A male lion with a black mane crouched next to him, and a black bat perched on his shoulder.

As soon as he came out, the skinhead saw Garen, who was avoiding the bats.

"Intruder!!" He instantly roared, pointing a finger at Garen.

Brrr!!

The bat on his shoulder, as well as the two black bats in the air, opened their mouths and emitted shapeless soundwaves at the same time.

The soundwaves fanned opened, completely enveloping Garen who was trying to avoid them. They came in waves, like seawaves breaking over the rocks.

The soundwaves had just touched Garen when they broke past the Neon Butterfly’s Totem Light in an instant, directly entering his body.

Suddenly there was a tight and dull on his chest, and Garen felt his head vaguely aching.

His vision was a blurry mess, as though something was pressing down on his eyelids, so he couldn’t see anything clearly at all.

His ears were also constantly echoing with a ringing sound, so he couldn’t hear a thing. His heartbeat accelerated, growing faster and faster, and that dull nausea kept rising from his chest and into his threat.

He suddenly tasted something like iron in his throat.

"Shit!! Form 2 totem!" Garen immediately understood his opponent’s level. Before he could think too much about it, he somersaulted backwards, his feet desperately tapping the ground, and he disappeared into the darkness within a few leaps.

The bats chased him for quite a distance, but still couldn’t catch up to him in the slightest.

The skinhead called back his three bat totems coldly, caressing the black lion’s head beside him.

"Suicidal. A tiny Form 1 totem user who didn’t self-implode after taking a hit from my Triple Ultrasound Waves, consider yourself lucky." The other guy escaped, but he didn’t mind in the slightest. Anyone who got hit by Triple Ultrasound Waves basically wouldn’t live for more than five minutes.

He fixed his collar, and raised his hand to look at the time on his watch.

"I should go check on Phillip, there have been little bugs getting in here all the time now, and now they’ve almost entered the restricted zone. Looks like we oughta move this position soon."

He strode into the pitch black tunnel, the bats and black lion following closely behind him.

*************

Garen panted heavily, trying to get air into his lungs. The Neon Butterfly was perched on his shoulder motionlessly, its light dimming, its body wrinkled and dry. It had obviously taken damage in that soundwave attack from before.

Not only was the Neon Butterfly damaged, tiny red dots were also blossoming all over Garen’s whole body, as countless blood capillaries erupted at the seams.

He leaned heavily one of the tunnel’s stone walls. His whole body, inside and out, felt like it was swelling up as though someone was inflating him with air, making him liable to explode at any moment.

His blood and qi were boiling intensely like never before. Garen tried his hardest, did everything to press it down, desperately using the Divine Statue Technique’s methods to control and adjust it.

It took a full ten minutes for there to be some sort of effect.

He stretched out his hands, and saw that there was blood leaking out all around his fingernails.

"What a strong effect!!" he murmured softly.

All the blood in his body was trembling from the soundwave attack, roiling over like waves. His peak-level Body Hardening Technique, that had completely merged with his body, actually started to waver.

All this time, ever since he came to this world, he had confidence based on his highest achievements from the world of secret techniques. Even when he witnessed his teacher Emin’s battle against an opponent, he didn’t think he was too far away from them. It was just a difference in their strongest outputs.

And now, a regular unknown Form 2 totem user from out of nowhere, nearly injured him grievously at just first glance. It was like pouring a bucket of cold water over Garen’s head.

Although he did know inside that he couldn’t match a Form 2 totem user, he was still not that afraid or worried about his opponent, because the other person would find it hard to hurt him as well. Especially after he ambushed and killed a Form 2 totem user recently, this line of thinking had been reinforced even further.

To think that he would suddenly stumble into that skinhead totem user in this tunnel, and that guy had a total of three bat support totems. And his main totem, the black lion, hadn’t even attacked, but it was already enough to injure Garen to this level.

Only then did Garen understand more about Form 2 totems.

"Three support totems, and one core totem… He’s definitely one of the higher-ups here! A Form 2 totem user like that can’t possibly be a no-name character!" he hazarded a guess. At the same time, he kept stabilizing the situation inside his body.

Right now, his blood and qi were unstable. The impact had caused internal bleeding, and if he were to fight with anyone now, his abilities would be drastically reduced. At the most, he would have half of what he did before.

Faced with the soundwave attack that also carried Totem Light, the Divine Statue Technique could only resist a little better than normal people. Other than that, he had no other advantage.

After resting for a while, Garen knew that this was the key period. In his memories, he knew that as long as he found the core area in here, he shouldn’t be able to get a rare totem. This was Obscuro Society’s main factory, after all. If he could obtain the Obscuro Society’s totem and bring it out of here, it would be surely stronger than regular totems.

"I must be patient now, and wait for Goth’s side to trigger his power. It will disrupt the entire underground headquarters and factory, then I’ll have my chance to move in the chaos!" Garen’s heart slowly started to calm down. He began to dig stones, bit by bit out of the cave wall he was at.

Curling his hands into claws, he could paw out a large rock with each swipe, Soon enough he had dug a trench out of the stone wall, and darted into it.

He then squeezed all the rocks and shards he had dug out into very fine black sand, scattering them on the ground around him. This way it was very hard for anyone to notice him.

Shrinking quietly in the stone wall, Garen used the clothes on his body to hide the trench. It was hard to see in the darkness anyway, so it had a very strong camouflaging effect.

He shrunk into the stone wall, listening silently to the disturbances in front and behind him in the tunnel.

The reason he rejected using his teacher Emin’s White Bear as a core totem was because he knew that no matter how strong the White Bear totem got, it couldn’t defeat special animal totems without evolving to the very peak. And these special animal totems could barely go against Terraflor’s plant totems, not to mention the strongest ones, Obscuro’s element totems.

He didn’t have over-powered talent, so if even his basics were one step behind everyone else, it would be hard for him to advance.

Acacia’s talent could support two totems at most, and that was also because the Neon Butterfly was very weak. If it was the White Bear, he would only be able to support one at most.

He didn’t know how long he waited, but Garen -- hiding in the stone wall-- suddenly felt footsteps coming from the tunnel outside.

A large group of people were running past this tunnel, their footsteps hasty.

"Hurry! Hurry!" Voices came from outside.

Boom!!

An intense tremor came from the distance, jolting Garen, who was inside the stone wall, into getting a face-full of sand.

"It’s begun!! Goth and the others must have engaged the enemy! I have to hurry!" After the footsteps had passed, Garen quickly darted out of the wall, put on his clothes, and hurriedly dashed deeper into the tunnel.

After that moment’s reprieve, he had recovered most of his speed.

The tunnel ahead of him kept turning and twisting.

Soon enough, he returned to where he had been injured earlier. That skinhead in black robes was no longer there.

Garen didn’t wait for even a moment, and directly ran past this area.

The path ahead was suddenly illuminated. It was a wide tunnel with torches on both sides of the wall.

There were a few corpses scattered over the floor, each of them with their necks snapped and their eyes wide.

There was a light splatter of blood on the walls, leaving a smell of iron in the air.

On the right there were two white stone doors, one tightly shut and one half open.

In the distance ahead, he could faintly hear the sounds of intense battle. The two fighting sides had evidently just left here, and hadn’t gone far. They could be back at any time.

Garen walked up to the half-open stone door, and quickly peeped inside.

There were also corpses strewn about inside, blood flowing into a little stream from the corner of the walls to the door, dying the black stone floor a sticky dark red.

This stone room was probably a place for recreation and meetings. He could still see the bar counter, beer bottles and sofa inside.

Garen quickly walked up to the second stone door, and pushed it slightly. It didn’t budge at all, meaning it was locked.

It was a boost to his spirits. Garen aimed his right palm for the keyhole, and hit it abruptly.

Hiss!

A hole instantly appeared where the keyhole to the stone door had been.

He pushed open the large door, and quietly but quickly pulled it to a close behind him.

This room was wide, and had many long white rectangular shelves inside. There were like so many book shelves, neatly arranged.

There was a hint of pale red mist in the air.

At the furthest right, by the corner of the wall, there was a silver unit factory on a large table. A pile of intricate instruments made of silver were continuously spitting out silver, cubed units from a black exit hole.

There was a mess on the assembly table next to it, and the chairs by the table had also fallen askew. It was evident that the people here had left in a hurry.

Garen didn’t hesitate, and struck out a palm at the silver shelves.

Whoosh!

A strong gust of wind blew past, but did not trigger any movement.

He relaxed slightly, and quickly walked to the first shelf on the left.

The shelf was stuffed full of drawers, he pulled out the first one with a clatter.

Inside, there was a silver bat neatly arranged.

Although the bat had strong soundwaves, it was still an animal type, and so wasn’t what Garen wanted.

He pulled open the second, the third, the fourth.

They were all bats.

Everything in the first shelf were created bats.

He quickly walked up to the second shelf.

This shelf was full of silver poison wasps, each of them as big as a fist, and the poison needle on its end as long as half a finger.

The third shelf was half empty. In the larger doors towards the bottom, there were many wolf-shaped totems, all silver and unactivated.

The fourth shelf, the fifth shelf.

Garen casually took some of the smaller totems, so he could sell them outside as revenue. But that wasn’t what he wanted most just now.

In front of the sixth and final shelf.

This shelf only had a dozen long doors, dividing the shelf into a dozen long compartments.

Garen pulled out the first long door, and the thing inside gave him a slight shock.

It was a pitch black large metal ball, about as big as a person’s head.

The ball was covered in tiny, cramped and seemingly random white carvings, like a toy ball made out of voodoo parts.

Even more strangely, this black ball was suspended in mid air.

Just as he was taken aback, a clear woman’s voice came from within the black ball.

"Pleases insert the password." The voice repeated in several different languages, and then fell silent.

Chapter 275: Injured 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

Password?!

What’s that?

Garen went over to pull out the rest of the shelf doors. The others were all either empty or similarly contained this strange black ball. All of them made the same woman’s voice, asking for a password.

But even then, only four out of the dozen doors had this black ball.

"Password?" Garen frowned deeply, knowing that he had hit the jackpot.

Originally, everything in this base should have been totally destroyed. After Goth exploded that time, he fought with the mastermind of the Obscuro Society, and ignited the base’s kinetic furnace. In the large explosion that ensued, the entire base was destroyed to the ground. Nothing remained.

And so Obscuro raged, sending assassins after Goth.

Garen was only thinking that since these things were going to be destroyed in the explosion anyway, he might as well use them himself. The one he felt would be the biggest waste was the unit factory. It’d be great if only he could take it away, but unfortunately…

And the black ball in front of him looked mysterious, so it was very probably one of the most important items in this base.

"Password, Obscuro." Garen attempted to reply.

"Incorrect. You still have two chances. Incorrect answers will cause total lockdown." The female voices from the four balls replied at once.

"Password, Phantom Light."

"Incorrect. You still have one chance. An incorrect answer will cause total lockdown."

Garen narrowed his eyes and scanned his surroundings continuously, but unfortunately, there wasn’t anything for him to refer to.

This black ball’s password was probably decided by the higher-ups, so its user required a password from the higher-ups. They then had to come to the base for the actual thing, and the two together were needed for them to use the black ball. So the password and the black ball should be totally separate.

Garen’s mind moved at high speeds, as he thought non-stop about the possible password. He could tell at one glance that this sort of thing was mass manufactured, and besides, the security and secrecy around it was so thick. It was probably used by the higher-ups only, and they would probably use a common password known to all the higher-ups.

"I’ll just wing it!" Garen knew, that the black ball in front of him was most likely the most precious thing here.

"Password, Hellgate!" Hellgate, the true name of the Obscuro Society’s mastermind.

"Incorrect. Password error, commencing lockdown."

Sma-ack!

There was a crisp sound.

Garen’s blood ran cold, and he knew it was all over. Once it was locked down, these things would be excruciatingly hard to unlock.

The continuous smacking sounds also stopped then. Garen suddenly noticed that only three of the black balls were locked down, while the third one in the center didn’t move or reply.

"Password correct." After a pause, a cold woman’s voice came from this black ball.

Garen was instantly overjoyed, rushing up to this black ball and watching its changes carefully.

Suddenly, the center of the black ball fell apart like countless puzzle pieces, slowly opening to both sides to form a medium-sized round hole. It revealed yet another black ball inside.

Another hole also opened up in the black ball inside, once more revealing another layer and another black ball.

The third layer of the black ball split apart again, revealing a fist-sized red crystal ball inside.

The crystal ball was propped up by a milky-white pillar like a champagne glass, glowing with a faint silver and red light.

"Ampera no.7, Derivator, for your perusal." The woman’s voice came from the black ball again, informing Garen.

"Derivator?" Garen was rather surprised, and then quickly took the black ball out, stuffing it into the pocket of his long robes.

No matter what, this was good stuff. With prize in hand, Garen grabbed a few more smaller, unactivated totems, and was just about to leave.

Wooo…!!

Suddenly there was a piercing wail from the shelf. It sounded like an alarm.

"There’s someone in the totem room! Hacca, you stall him!"

"Dammit! It was the brat I met just now! The Triple Soundwaves just now didn’t kill him! Siva, you stop him from the other side! Don’t let the brat escape!"

From a corridor far away outside, there was the sound of angry shouting.

Garen’s blood ran cold, and he quickly rushed out of the stone door, dashing down the way he had come.

Just now that one skinhead was already more than he could deal with, forget the other guy that sounded like he’d be at the same level.

Turning into the dark tunnel ahead, Garen used all his speed to dash madly down the corridor.

"Judging from the voices just now, it’s highly likely that they can see footage of the totem storeroom, so I need to leave as fast as possible!"

In the pitch black tunnel, Garen’s whole body nearly morphed into a black shadow, quickly dashing down the way he had come.

"Over here!!"

Suddenly there was a deep man’s voice calling out from up ahead.

Garen could vaguely hear the low roars and howls of beasts ahead. His heart gave a jolt.

Whoosh!!

Two red fireballs came flying suddenly down the corridor that had been dark just a while ago. They were as big as soccer balls and came spinning, drawing out two tracks of fiery red after-images, coming straight at Garen.

In the path of the fireballs, they lit every part of the passage bright red. Some of the mosses and grass were instantly charred and smoking.

With two loud smacking sounds, two stones shot out from Garen’s hands. They actually went directly through the fireball, becoming transparent red stones. They did nothing at all to hinder the advance of the fireball.

He leapt up, his feet gaining momentum by stepping onto the walls, and then his whole person shot out with a pop. He went right through the gap between the two fireballs.

Boom!!

The two fireballs basically exploded at once, the intensely high heat enveloping Garen in an instant. They simply became a ball of fire in mid-air, and burst.

With a pop, a charred black body fell down from mid-air, and moved no more.

"Hmph!" There was a cold snort from far away. Followed by the sound of hurried footsteps hastening away.

A dozen seconds after the footsteps faded, the charred black body finally moved a little. He opened his blue eyes, and glanced around warily.

Garen slowly crawled up from the ground. His whole body had been burnt, and not a single spot didn’t sting and hurt from the heat. His blood and qi was continuously roiling, having been nearly scattered by that hit just now, and only regathering now.

His face, his neck, his arm, were all blistering, like so many flesh-colored grapes, round and filled with pus.

His previously fair skin was not red, but charred black. In some of the more grievously injured areas, his stomach and forearms had even started to carbonize and harden.

He gritted his teeth against the pain, and quietly but quickly moved forward.

A guardpost soon appeared in front of him. It was a dent in the wall, with a small bed, a few large wooden crates and barrels, and a few half-melted candles burning on top of those barrels. This type of candle lamp was created by putting candles in a glass bottle. The dim yellow light shone through the blurry glass, making it seem even dimmer.

Going past the guardpost, and after progressing for a certain distance, he somehow entered a large empty space. It was as big as a football field, and he could vaguely hear the sound of flowing water.

Barroom!!

It was yet another dull sound, as though something exploded.

Garen knew that this was Goth’s battle with the leader here after his explosion.

He considered his surroundings, and vaguely felt as though this was no longer part of the underground base. It was obviously an underground cave.

He had been following the previous path back this whole time, but despite it being the same path, this time he reached not the exit, but such a cave as this.

Garen slowly moved to the other end, following the walls of the cave. There were large rocks arranged close to each other on the ground, and water flowed through the cracks to make the splashing sound.

He advanced for a while, feeling his lungs struggle more and more for breath. The more he moved, the faster his blood and chi flowed, and the more the burns on his body hurt.

He pushed himself for a while, working up a huge sweat. The salt-tinged sweat flowed past his burned skin, stinging so much he couldn’t help but groan.

"Who!?"

Suddenly, a wary voice came from the other entrance stretching out from the cave ahead.

A tall and thin figure walked out from the entrance, leaping from one large rock to another as he entered the cave.

His gaze swept about the surroundings, on high alert.

"Come out! I already saw you. Hehe, did you think I wouldn’t discover you hiding behind the rocks?" The man laughed coldly.

He waited for a pause, but there were still no movements. Only then did he relax, and slowly ran towards the entrance into the underground base.

By then, Garen had already quietly moved to a spot by the wall on the opposite of the cave. He found a gap behind a large rock and sat down.

Right now, his whole body was scalded and his blood qi was a mess. It practically had to be adjusted and activated again from the start after being shattered apart. The Divine Statue Technique had extremely strong healing powers, and was continuously cleaning up the heat toxins in his organs and on the surface of his skin.

But even so, he was basically partially paralyzed now, and couldn’t move at all. His physical qualities had dropped drastically, and he was being haunted by powerful Totem Light, so he temporarily couldn’t heal.

This was a special type of fire, that seemed to have some polluting properties. It completely polluted and destroyed most of the Garen’s cells that had been scalded in the high heat within an instant. This pollution also contained heat toxins, infiltrating his organs and notoriously hard to deal with. Plus, it was constantly worsening.

If it was a regular person, they would have probably breathed their last as soon as the flames exploded, killed instantly by this polluting power.

"I need to increase recovery speed!"

Garen glanced at the Attribute Pane at the bottom of his vision. He clenched his teeth, and added a potential point to his Vitality attribute, that hadn’t healed completely yet.

His Vitality instantly rose from 2.5 to 2.76, the highest point his body achieved in the previous life.

Exactly as the value changed, an ice cold current flowed out of his brain into every other part of his body. His organs, his skin, his bones, anywhere that was hurt were all soaked into that current.

In that moment, cold and heat weaved together, creating a pain several times more intense that shot into Garen’s brain. It was followed by waves of extreme itchiness. Every inch of his skin that was burned began to itch mysteriously.

He wanted to scratch, but he kept himself in check. He didn’t want to move, and couldn’t move. His whole body went limp, his back leaning closely on the stone wall to prevent himself from falling.

The polluting power of the Totem Light that invaded his body kept crossing swords with the cool current from his special power, mixing vigorously inside Garen and making him sweat waterfalls. His sweat dripped onto the scalded wounds, bringing a fresh wave of even more intense pain.

Pain and itchiness wove together. Garen was completely and totally stiff, the blisters scalded onto his body popping one by one. The pale red pus drenched his nearly charcoaled clothes, emitting an unbearable stench.

Chapter 276: Injury 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

Right now, he had practically no resistance at all to anything. He didn’t know how long the conflict would last, and the intense pain inside his body made him unable to even think clearly. He clenched his teeth and forced himself not to make any sound.

At first he could force himself to move at high speed, but to think that after activating his regeneration skill, it backfired instead and resulted in his whole body going stiff, rendering him immobile. If he knew that earlier, he wouldn’t have activated his regeneration skill here!

Now any totem user, or even a non-totem user, any normal person who was just a little stronger than average, would be able to easily end him.

Listening as the steps slowly moved away, Garen, however, heaved a sigh of relief. Thank goodness that guy just now had left already.

Sploosh!

Suddenly he heard the sound of something heavy dropping into the water beside him.

Garen’s whole body stiffened.

He tried his hardest to turn his head, looking at the totem he had kept in his pocket. It had actually fallen out, sliding into the water beyond an edge nearby.

His clothes had been burnt away by the flames, and his front had been more or less carbonized. A large hole had been burned into the side pocket, and that was how the totem fell out.

"Who!!"

A man’s voice abruptly stopped.

The voice sounded rather familiar, actually.

Garen’s heart skipped a beat, and then he suddenly remembered, it was that Valerie’s voice.

"What’s he doing here!?" He resisted the pain and tried to analyze the situation, but the pain came in waves, making him unable to concentrate.

Valerie carefully glanced around the whole cave, there seemed to be some movement amidst the splashing of the water just now. He was slightly uncertain.

It wasn’t easy for him to escape that damned base. Thank goodness for Goth’s explosion, which blocked the totem users on the chase. The two sides were now embroiled in battle.

Upon discovering what this situation in this hideout, Valerie connected all the scenes and decorations he had seen along the way, thinking he had seen something similar in his teacher’s notes.

After thinking about it carefully, he suddenly remembered, this was very likely the secret base of some Phantom Light totem users.

After Goth started fighting the enemy leader, the others were in shock but all Valerie could think of wasn’t how amazing Goth’s abilities were, but what treasures might be hidden in this base!

The main powers were being distracted by Goth, so the back must be even more empty and unguarded.

While everyone was distracted, he quietly left from behind, ducking into another branch in the tunnel, attempting to go around behind the totem users.

After proceeding quickly down this tunnel for some time, he realized he was right when no one stopped him. Ecstatic, he increased his speed, and soon entered this cave.

But there seemed to be someone here.

Valerie’s heart sank.

He was worried there would be someone here! If he were to be discovered and the alarm raised, they would come from both sides, and he would be immediately surrounded. When that happened, he would be dead before he even knew what was happening.

The voice seemed to comev from over there.

Valerie’s gaze was aimed at the direction where the sound came from, and his feet moved over there quietly. At the same time, he flipped his hand, and a blue bird flew out, flying towards that place.

"Pierce!!"

He steeled his heart, and the Bluebird became a sharp blue arrow, piercing towards the rock where the sound came from with a hiss.

Hiss!

The Bluebird directly pierced through the stone, emerging from the back, and making a few circles around it. Just like a steel nail going through tofu, it was effortless.

"Nobody?"

He frowned, could it be a fish?

Somewhat hesitantly, he called back the Bluebird, turned, and left.

Garen slowly emerged from the water beneath the stone cracks. In his urgency just now, he had ducked into the water. That was the only way he could avoid the Bluebird’s attack, otherwise that pierce would have made a hole through his chest.

Putting aside his condition now, even at his peak, he would not dare to go directly against a totem user’s attack.

Phew… Garen released a long breath. The piercing cold stream water soaked his body, and mixed even more with the two other stimuli in his body. His condition right now was unprecedentedly troublesome.

He used both his hands and legs to climb out of the water, lying on his back on top of the stone and panting deeply.

"So it was you… Garen?"

Valerie’s voice suddenly came from above.

Garen jolted slightly, and turned his head with difficulty.

Garen didn’t know when he got there, but Valerie was already standing on the stone that had been pierced through, a hint of amusement on his face.

"Not bad… It’s actually just as I thought." Valerie’s gaze fell on the hole in Garen’s pocket, where the silver glow of a totem was peeking out.

Seeing that it was an inactivated totem, his gaze instantly became passionate.

"You came out from inside too, didn’t you? A punk who doesn’t even have a core totem, could actually bring out so many totems from inside? Tsk-tsk… it sure makes me envious." Valerie licked his lips.

Garen’s heart sank. Judging from his actions just now, he could tell that this Valerie fellow was an extraordinarily cunning character.

"Hehe… did you think… I could escape from there… without some tricks up my sleeve…?" Garen smiled with difficulty. It was just that his appearance, covered with boils, was rather terrifying.

That was what Valerie was worried about. Since his attack just now didn’t hit, he was starting to feel doubt.

And now, seeing that Garen wasn’t dead despite looking like this, and could even smile, he was starting to feel the hairs rise on his skin.

"You’re already like this, I’ll just send you out for treatment." He acted as though coming over to help Garen up, but his gaze was unreadable.

Suddenly he froze, seeing the round object protruding from under Garen’s charred-black clothes.

"If you come here, we’ll all die together!" Garen grinned horrifically. "I still have a totem bomb here. Come over if you don’t want to die."

"Listen to what you’re saying. We’re teammates, you know, why would I possibly hurt you!?" Valerie’s gaze went a full circle, and suddenly he was all smiles. "But are you sure you don’t need me to help you? Look at how serious your injuries are…"

"You don’t need to worry about that." Garen tried to withstand the pain, looking at how Valerie still stood there and refused to leave, it was obvious that he was plotting something. "You’re still not gonna leave?"

Valerie chuckled, but didn’t say anything, his greedy gaze fixed on the totem peeping out of Garen’s pocket.

The Bluebird beside him kept flying rounds around him, its intention very clear. It would be easy for him to put some distance between them and let the Bluebird attack Garen from a long distance. At the most, he would just lose one totem.

Seeing this, Garen’s eyes shone with despair.

He clenched his teeth, his whole body shaking, his chest rising and falling fast.

"Fine, fine, fine!! I’ll give you the totem!" Furious, Garen managed to bring out the bat totem, the poisonous wasp totem, and a few beetle totems. Wrapping them up in the remains of his clothes, he tossed them over.

Smack.

Valerie controlled the Bluebird to grab the package of totems in its beak, and bringing them over for him to check. The smile on his face grew even deeper.

"Are you really sure you don’t need me to help?"

"Scram!!" Garen’s eyes turned red, panting as he roared.

Boom!!

There was yet another explosion. A large tremor shook even the cave ceiling.

Both of their expression’s changed.

Valerie glanced at Garen, and knew that he wouldn’t have to get away if he didn’t leave now. He clenched his teeth, turned around, and strode towards the entrance into the hideout.

Hiss!

A flash of blue pierced Garen’s body mercilessly, going right through his right arm while he could only move slowly.

Garen cried out loudly, and fell into the water. In an instant, there was no trace left of him.

Valerie was somewhat confused. Although the Bluebird did seem to find its target, it hadn’t seemed to hit the vitals.

"With such serious injuries and heavy blood loss, he should be dead for sure."

His expression had a hint of cruelty.

"If you have to blame someone, blame yourself for bumping into me."

He ducked into the tunnel, the Bluebird flowing closely behind him as they disappeared into the darkness.

**************

Inside the hideout,

The skinhead totem user and a white-haired totem user were riding on two black male lions, advancing rapidly down the tunnel. Many black bats squawked around their heads, following behind them.

The skinhead was holding up a round crystal mirror, with a bright red dot blinking on it. He would occasionally glance down at the red dot on the mirror, a sardonic smile on his face.

"Did you think our Obscuro’s totems were that easy to acquire? You idiot. To think you could resist so well, you’re not dead despite taking two hits."

The white-haired man beside advanced in tandem with him.

"Is that side not settled yet? Why is Debicci stalling so long even for a smallfry like that?"

"I don’t know, he probably wants to play. That guy loves nothing more than to torture his opponent. The more stubborn the opponent, the more excited he gets." The skinhead licked his lips and laughed. Suddenly he looked at the round mirror in his hand, surprised.

"What’s the matter? This guy didn’t run out, but dared to return?!"

"What?" The white-haired man looked over from the side, and saw that the little red dot on the round mirror was actually running towards them.

"Does this guy think that our Obscuro Society is a free treasure vault?" The skinhead was getting slightly angry.

"Maybe he thinks we haven’t discovered him? But this kid definitely wouldn’t know that we installed tags on all our totems. Of all things, to think he dared to take an inactivated totem…" The white-haired man couldn’t help but chuckle. "This kid’s pretty quick, we can’t let him escape now. Send more people to block the exit."

"Leave it to me." The skinhead grinned. "I missed once, but I won’t miss again. This time, he’s truly pissed me off!" He revealed his creepy white teeth.

The two of them dashed ahead and turned the corner, then stopped abruptly.

A tall and thin man was standing in the opposite tunnel, a bluebird perched on his shoulder. It was Valerie.

Valerie stopped dead in his tracks, staring blankly at the two totem users, the skinhead and the white-haired man.

"Fuck...!!!"

He was instantly covered in cold sweat, his whole body freezing cold to the bone.

"This was… this was the back tunnel…? How??"

"Hehe, kid, did you think I wouldn’t recognize you after you changed your appearance?" The skinhead’s expression was vicious. "After stealing our stuff, you dare to come again for seconds?"

Valerie stumbled two steps back, terror making his whole body tremble.

He could feel the horror of the two men facing him. The bats flying in circles over their heads were actually all Form 2 totems, and there were six of them!

Besides, there were the black lions they rode on, the saliva dripping from the lions’ mouths actually corroding many large holes in the ground.

"Finish him!!" The skinhead pointed at Valerie, and the bats above his head instantly pounced over madly.

"No!!!!"

Valerie’s scream kept on echoing through the tunnels, going very, very far.

Just then, he suddenly remembered Garen’s expression back then. That looked like fury, but it seemed to hide a trace of faint mocking.

It was only then that he realized just how brutal that man called Garen secretly was inside. This was all his own fault!

Chapter 277: Empower 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

Wishh.

Garen’s head popped over the water surface

He shook his head, allowing the ice-cold water flow through his face down his cheeks, his right arm holding the wound on his left arm tightly. He shivered as he looked at the direction where Valerie left

He suddenly recalled, as he was in the totem storage chamber, his heart felt uneasy as he felt that as though Baldy was observing him in real time. That he will kill Garen when he leaves.

As he had guessed, Garen felt a lot better after he dumped all the totems to Valerie.

As his secret technique was trained to the pinnacle, his five senses have been honed to react to imminently dangerous situations. This was an effect of his innate extreme agility. It is also an ability that the Luminarists would never achieve, as this would require the senses of the body to be extremely sharp.

Even though the secret arts are not as powerful as a totem, it does have many benefits that the totems do not possess.

"Not running after taking the things, yet you still ran in to take more advantage, it would be baffling if you don’t die." Garen sarcastically said as he got out of the water. Without stopping, barely being able to get up, he ran towards the tunnel that would lead him out.

The aura of the ability almost finally mitigated the poisonous flame from the totem’s power. His body had also started recovering, but the ability’s aura had also proportionately been exhausted. Recovery became extremely sluggish.

Garen looked at the attributes beneath his vision.

The Potential points used to kill the Totem used were already been at 16 points, now it fell yet another point, becoming 15 points again.

At a critical time like this, if he were to depend only on himself to recover, it would require at least a week’s time. The injury this time was worse than the wounds received from Sylphalan in the previous world.

His body is a mess, internally and externally, his Qi was also unstable at a time like this.

He clenched his teeth and looked at the Body pane.

The potential point nudged, but it did not add onto the Body section.

He shook his head in disappointment. Enduring the pain inflicted by the wounds, he walked out of the cave, going into the tunnel leading to outside.

Suddenly he heard a vague scream of terror. As he paid attention, it was indeed Valarie's voice.

Garen stopped for a while and smirked.

"This Idiot."

He had to leave as soon as possible, after the explosion at Goth’s side, who knows how long he had before the next kinetic furnace would explode. If one decided to stay, it would not matter that he were a totem user, when a huge explosion occurs, and he’d be buried deep underground, gravely injured, if not dead.

The kinetic furnace was no ordinary thing, it was specifically used to refine a special silver ingot used in the forging totems.

The reason Obscuro Society was so strong \was because they owned too many cutting edge techniques

Among them were totem raw materials, the core silver ingot, which was much stronger than the rest.

Garen held the red, round crystal sphere in his arms, and was sure that it was something valuable, even though he had no idea what it was. However, for it to be so heavily guarded, it had to be valuable.

He had a hunch that he had picked up treasure.

Enduring the pain, Garen picked up his pace and rushed out towards the exit.

Even though he was covered in injuries, he had to find a way to rendezvous with Goth and the rest. As to how he got injured, he did not plan to hide it.

As he walked along the tunnel, what he had originally already possessed had all been robbed by Valeria. This issue could be pushed to Valerie completely.

Soon, the light that shined from beyond the exit was visible. Even though the tunnel was not guarded by anyone, nor was it within the area of the lair, but Garen felt that it was best to get out of the underground and onto the surface.

He rushed out of the cave and he staggered onto the plains for a while.

As the sun shined upon him, the boils on his body burst, which invited another wave of intense pain.

He looked up to the sun, and the sun rays blinded him. His vision became blurry for a moment.

"I can’t take it anymore; the potential points have been used up… If I did not have the potential points to enhance my body in the moment for recovery, I would probably be finished by now. " On retrospect, he picked up his pace and ran towards the shade of a tree, sitting down on the grass, his back against the tree trunk, panting for air.

This shade was facing directly towards the exit of the cave. From the exit to Garen’s location was a trail of yellow puss forming a line, emitting a gross smell under the sunlight.

Garen quietly sat under the shade, trying hard not to let himself faint.

But his consciousness was being attacked by the waves of intense pain, his vision still blurry.

"What a huge loss!" He was angry inside. In the realm of secret techniques, I was unbeatable, even the final direct clash with Sylphalan only ended in a tie.

But when he is here, he’s been wounded all over by something as ridiculous as totem’s power. Secret techniques have close to no power to resist.

"I have to find a way to fight against the polluting nature of a totem’s power. The reason the totem’s power is this strong, is primarily due to its polluting nature. Aside from that, a totems’ damage and power are not too different from a normal situation.

Garen tried hard to stay conscious

He’d rather move to the other side of the tree; now with his back facing the cave exit, he could hide himself.

A breeze blew, rustling the leaves in its path. An oval-shaped leaf fell and touched Garen’s body; causing immense pain on top of what he was already experiencing now.

He slowly took out the crystal ball, resting it on his palm

As he focused his vision on the top, the crystal ball emitted a dim red light for a while. A few rows of words showed on the ball.

"Thank you for using the Enpaler Derivator, please select your operating language."

Beneath it are rows upon rows of different languages; Canbria Language; Kovitan Language, Ender Language….

Canbria, Kovitan, Ender, are the three strongest empires among the hundreds of kingdoms within the East Continent, of which Canbria and Kovitan allied themselves to fight against a superempire in the West Continent. Although Ender is considered a strong country, its sphere of influence was significantly worse than the two before it, furthermore, it is a vassal of the Kovitan empire, while being much stronger than other countries. But due to its small size, it can only be a strong country; not a big country.

Garen only recognized these three languages, the rest of the countries seemed foreign to him. From top to bottom just seemed like a bundle of unknown words.

Garen’s thoughts sidetracked, and went back into focus onto the crystal ball

"Is this a touch interface?"

His index finger reached out, clicked onto "Kovitan Language" shown on the crystal ball.

The words disappeared, and reappeared with a simple interface

"Functional introduction: You are now using the General-Level specialized Derivator, dear esteemed General, please input your full name via voice, the derivator will use your voice pattern as an encryption."

"General-Level?"

Garen’s heart skipped a beat, he indeed found a treasure.

"Garen" He tried to calm his voice as he answered.

"Sir Garen, below are the functions of the derivator.

Function 1: This derivator will provide up to 10 totem control systems, you can use the derivator to control up to any 10 Silver totems, and cause no toll on the body.

Function 2: The derivator controls the totem’s nature, but only for empowering totems. The derivator is able to use a living creature’s core to be converted into a semi-living totem’s ability. Cannot control pure Silver totems. Please proceed with caution.

Silver totem: Using a living creature’s core to be converted into a controllable empowered creature totem. Be aware, the Silver totem itself will not be guided or controlled during evolution, it is completely dependent on the influence of the creature’s genes. Please choose the creatures to be empowered wisely. – functionality abnormal, please proceed to the fourth Obscuro maintenance center for a checkup.

Garen meticulously rearranged the messages shown on the crystal ball, using the up-down swipe motion of his fingers, he could browse through the content of the crystal ball, it is almost as convenient as an electronic touchscreen.

"This thing is indeed extraordinary…" Garen looked at the functions’ introduction, he suddenly understood something. "to be able to research a way to turn living creatures into semi-totems, Obscuro Society is indeed strong. No wonder, at the later point of the war, they dared to pick a war against the entire world., the reason behind it was this. One of these objects could control 10 totems, and those are additional totems that do not burden the user at all. Not accounting the user’s own core totem, one person can control more than ten totems, if these totems are form 2, or form 3 ultimate form…" Garen felt his body numbing as these thoughts run through his mind,

That is practically a single-man mechanized army, one totem user fighting against a Mech user.

He looked upon the crystal ball, he suddenly thought, everything on Earth had a barcode. He wondered if there is a barcode on this.

"Show derivator code" He tried using the voice enquiry function.

The crystal ball indeed showed a tiny row of numbers

‘Code: 0032gcr, your derivator is the 32nd piece in East Continent, There are a total of 10 derivators placed in the Kovitan Empire, please exercise caution regarding the functions.

Garen was shocked, there were actually ten of these in Koviten.

Keeping the crystal ball away, his heart had a brief idea. The derivator was a futuristic invention from the Obscuro Society, being able to additionally control the remaining totems, even though it would have been converted from living creatures. They were probably not as strong as real totems, but this would suffice, as quantity would make up for quality.

However, this thing is not a real totem… what he really needed, was a core totem. After fumbling for so long, having one would indeed increase his own abilities, but there was still no core totem...

He felt slightly helpless. He reached into his pockets and fumbled for a while, all of the totems have been dumped over to Valerie, those things should have a tracking signal, so he couldn’t have brought any out.

If he did not correctly guess the encryption correctly and unlocked the ball, he guessed the derivator would have a tracking unit on it, and it would have been stronger too.

"Only core totems can defend me 24 hours continuously without deactivating. Fuuuh…" He exhaled, the breath had a hint of blood’s. Suddenly his gaze was laid upon a bush.

"Perhaps I can experiment on the derivator’s empowerment ability…"

As he focused onto the bush, there was some rustling sound.

Swiftly, a greyish white rabbit came running out of the bush. This wild rabbit had cute drooping ears. Its butt bounced as it jumped out of the bush, it looked at Garen with curiosity.

"Come here, little one, come to brother." Garen let out a laugh "hehe", as he quietly picked up a piece of pebble

Pap!

The pebble was shot out in an instant, it hit the little rabbit’s head, its power is just nice, just enough to knock it out.

Garen endured the pain as he walked towards the rabbit, picked it up, and walked back to the tree.

He took the crystal ball from the pocket in his clothes, and put it next to the rabbit.

"Do you want to empower the raw material?" The ball showed a row of words asked.

"Yes"

Garen replied surely.

Chapter 278: Empower 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

Suddenly, the red crystal ball slowly turned luminescent, just like a metal ball diffusing a ray of silver light.

At the core of the ball, a silver light shot out, and hit the rabbit’s head

In about 5 seconds later, the silver light dissipated, the crystal ball returned to its red color.

"Empowerment completed, Creature sample saved. Creature transferring… please do not move." The ball then shot a red light towards Garen

Garen only felt warm and fuzzy on the spot where the light illuminated on him, he felt comfortable.

Under the Skill Pane at the bottom of his sight, suddenly popped up an additional 3D icon of the totem, the icon is the indeed the rabbit who had fainted.

"Iron Rabbit: first form Living Totem, upgradeable. Evolution success rate: 81% (the weaker the original creature, the higher the success rate). Cost on potential points: 200%.

Ability: Knockback, Grass feeding."

Garen looked at the second ability speechlessly.

"grass feeding counts as an ability?" as he glanced the wild rabbit that just recovered, this little guy seemed to be stunned, being barely able to get up, shook its ears, then looked at Garen.

It jumped a round, then running to Garen, snuggling up to Garen’s legs to rest in a very friendly manner.

"so, this is the half living totem, creature totem, silver totem?" Garen held the rabbit up by its ears, and took a better look at it.

"I could probably evolve it, just to check out how it looks like after."

Finding a new source of potential points, Garen had laxed his usage of potential points.

In the war guild, he continuously took up so many missions, and so long as he had enough strength, he could then sneakily gain some potential points. Otherwise, its completion would have been extremely difficult., even to the point of possibly aborting the missions. Which was the reason why he still had zero potential point gain after so many missions,

He saw his current potential: 1594%.

After so many missions; some that had succeeded some that hadn’t, killed 3 form 1 totem users, which allowed him to rush to 94% progress.

"Only by being strong can you earn more potential points… let’s try it out."

He started focusing onto the Iron rabbit’s icon for three seconds.

The iron rabbit’s icon started getting blurry, the description behind the icon have also gone blurry.

Garen puts down the rabbit in his hand onto the grass, quietly observing its changes.

Tsssss…

Suddenly, the rabbit stood upright, its entire body started showing serious signs of expansion and twisting. Its body started bulging with tough muscles.

Woo!!

The rabbit is suddenly howled like a wolf, from the size of a palm, rapidly growing into half a man’s height.

Its eyes are blood red, with green veins popping under the skin, protruding its fur up. All of its four limbs grew longer. As it stood on all fours it was as big as a horse.

Chii!

It exhaled loudly from its nose, like the neigh of a horse. Its tongue protruded like a dog gasping for air. It squeezed around Garen in a friendly manner.

Miiiii!!~~

This rabbit pampered for a while, then it lifted its head and howled again.

Garen’s face twitched as he looked at the rabbit, he then looked at the skill pane, at the clear new totem icon.

"Howling Wererabbit, second evolutionary form of Iron Rabbit, second form creature totem. Can be evolved, evolution success rate at 54%. Potential point use: 300%.

Abilities: Exploding kick, plant extermination (extremely able to eat)."

Looking at this ability, Garen wanted to laugh, but was unable to due to the pain on his body.

The Iron Rabbit suddenly turned into a creature that’s half a man’s height, dog-like, wolf-like, and even more like a horse. Looking like a wolf in a rabbit’s skin.

However, during the evolution on the howling wereabbit, Garen realized that the totem’s light in his body is now much thicker. A layer of glass-like transparent totem’s light had been naturally covering his entire body.

"Luckily, totem’s light is still effective." Garen extended his arm to feel the totem’s light on his body, he nodded in satisfaction forcibly.

He had a thought, then the howling wereabbit sprinted towards the forest in a distance, quickly entering the forest.

Boom!!

There was a sudden quake in the forest, Garen was caught off guard and almost fell.

A huge shockwave emanated along the ground, much like an earthquake. He could vaguely feel, as if there was something exploding from beneath the ground.

Garen immediately turned back and looked at the direction of the cave exit.

There was a mix of hurried footsteps, fast approaching, soon three silhouettes came rushing out from the cave. It was Jessica, Andy and Goth. The trio were covered in wounds; Jessica’s left cheek had a long gash, making her look scary as she ran. Andy’s left arm was twisted and fractured, his forehead is full of sweat, but he bit his lips and endured it.

Goth was the last to come out, his face paled. He was even stumbling as he walked, sometimes he needing Jessica’s support to move forward.

As the trio walked out, they saw Garen, who was standing under the shade

"Garen! Let’s go!" Andy shouted in a rushed tone.

Garen did not hesitate, followed up to the trio, running in the opposite directions from the entrance, showing no signs of stopping.

Before exceeding 100 meters, it suddenly felt like the surrounding grass had all turned white. A strong light ray was shot from behind.

The three turned back as they were running.

At the entrance of the tunnel, and its surroundings within a 50-meter radius, was engulfed in a pillar of light shot from the ground, shooting up to the sky.

A deafening ring was heard, severely vibrating the trio’s eardrums. The surface of the ground had also been vibrating severely due to the vibrations. The soles of their feet were starting to numb.

The white light pillar had a diameter of several tens of meters, piercing the group, tearing the sky, illuminating everything around it in a bright white ray,

The soil, boulders, trees, creatures, all had disintegrated in the white light, as though it was completely broken down.

The trio continued continued running for several hundred meters, only then did they dare slow down, and slowly come to a halt.

For a while, they looked at the light pillar piercing the sky, and found themselves speechless. Only feelings of shock and dumbfounded-ness were interlaced, not knowing what to say.

Goth sat on a patch of yellow-green grassland, pressing his hand against his chest as he gazed blankly at the direction of the white pillar. His thoughts were unknown.

Andy patted Garen’s shoulders, placed his backpack and sat down. He also seemed not to be in the mood to talk.

Garen’s whole body was charred black. A set of torn clothes were all that remained on him. He took out a set of clothes from Andy’s backpack and put it on.

"What happened to you guys? How did you guys become like this?" he asked in a low tone.

"That wasn’t a bandit’s lair at all. It is a totem user’s base!" Andy replied in a low-spirited tone, "we ran into the totem users inside, then… if it weren’t for Goth, I’m afraid nobody would have survived."

Jessica nodded silently at the side, looking at Goth, his eyes seemed to be complicated by something.

Garen realized this, and understood that something must have happened between this trio that is hard to explain, there’s finally some development between Jessica and Goth.

"What bout you? How did you turn out this way? It’s as though you were burnt by fire." Andy looked at Garen.

The light pillar then dimmed, slowly become thinner, and then completely extinguished. The golden sun rays shone once again, covering the white light that engulfed the sky and earth.

At the location where the the white light was, a crater of several tens of meters was left behind. It was pitch black, with green smoke around the edges.

Garen looked at the crater, and exhaled in relief. He could feel that the howling wereabbit was fine, obviously it had also run to safety. He suddenly felt that the wererabbit had an urge to eat. It actually got hungry, letting it feed on grass in its surrounding, while keeping itself in hiding. Only Garen got back into focus, and answered Andy’s question.

"Ï was hit by a fireball casted by a totem user… I don’t know what flame that was, but thankfully the temperature wasn’t high, otherwise I would have been dead…" Garen forced a laugh.

"I’m guessing it’s that black lion’s fireballs, it can spew two kinds of fireballs; a red one, which he could shoot as many as it wished, and a green one which had a long interval between attacks. Its destructive power is much greater, and has some corrosive effect."Andy explained, "Goth withstood about a hundred of those."

Garen was shocked and looked at Goth, who was sitting on the ground.

This young man, who is wearing a red bib, had a sad looking face as he sat on the ground. His pose had a seductive, sexy vibe, as he crossed his legs, showing a slender, beautiful curve.

Ugh…

Garen and Andy turned away, trying hard to resist the urge to puke.

"Goth, can you close your legs and slant them… you’re not Jessica, thanks." Garen can’t help but to say.

"But my legs are injured." Goth lifted his head with puppy eyes.

" Even if you’re injured, don’t put up this gross pose!" Andy choked Goth’s neck and shook it.

"I’m warning you! Don’t choke me! I hate people choking me the most!" Goth shouted as he struggled.

"Like I care! Argh!! Fuck! Don’t grab me **!! You bitch! Grab me!! Grab me!!"

The two rolling into a lump, Jessica stood on the side, red faced, turning her head away from them.

Garen squatted, gazing blankly at the direction of the light pillar

"What was that, just now?"

"Kinetic furnace, it is something created by an organization called the Obscuro Society."

Jessica answered quietly.

"Goth finally exploded the furnace, then everything, everything exploded."

Garen quieted for a while, and then asked.

"What happened to Goth’s body?:

"His talent erupted, Black Continental Bird could suddenly move…. And transformed into a huge bird!"Jessica talked as she recalled, "then… then… he stood in front of us…" She did not continue speaking, but she looked at Goth who was brawling, her lips revealed a hint of gentleness.

"Perhaps all of us were wrong." Garen also looked at Goth. "He is not some sort of garbage, but a real genius."

"You have also discovered my uniqueness, hahaha." Goth happily laughed, "Do not idolize me too much! I’m born to be the legendary hero! Ha! Ha! Ha!"

This brat’s bib strap fell off, with one hand on his pants, another pointing towards the sky with a finger.

On the ground was Andy who was howling in pain from the fractured arm.

Four of them had their head lifted towards the sky.

A few blue birds flew past quickly, slapping their wings, into the clouds and against the strong wind.

On each blue bird’s feet, was a white paper scroll tied onto it. On one of the scrolls, had a little bit of blood stain on it.

Chapter 279: Reward 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

The Black Panther’s small squad of four had returned to Iron Tank City. Under the help of the close connection to the castle border guards belonging to Andy’s father, all of them were admitted to the hospital under the wing of Chialunar Academy.

This was the best hospital in the entire Iron Tank City, and had the best doctors.

In the ward.

Garen laid down on the bed, feeling bored.

Up, down, left, right, the floor, everything was white. On the bedside counter was a vase filled with lilies, and among them, some petals had slightly withered.

On the right side of the bed was a metal rack, on top of which was a bottle of medicated drip. The medicine flowed into Garen’s vein drop by drop through a thin pipe.

He could clearly feel the cold medicine seeping in through his wrist. The room was pin-drop silent, only some echoing footsteps could be heard from the corridor outside the ward.

Garen was lying alone in the middle of the ward bed From his angle tilting his head and looking out, he could still see the trees outside that had blossomed into many white flowers. The noon sunlight beamed down, through the leaves, forming mottled golden geometries, rustling as the wind blew.

Gacha.

The door was opened slowly, a chubby nurse dressed in white walked in. She was pushing a medicinal cart, and when she reached the side of the bed, she tapped the medication that was finishing soon, taking it down and changing it with a fresh bottle of drip.

"Pretty good body." This middle-aged lady looked at Garen, "such a large surface burn could heal this quickly."

"I have had a good body since young."Garen laughed. "Right, may I know how are the few friends that were admitted together with me?"

"I don’t know." The nurse simply answered. "I am not in charge of them, you can try asking the doctor."

"Then it’s fine, I will rest a little bit more and then try looking for them." Garen said, and remained silent thereafter.

The nurse left immediately after changing the drips, closing the door as she left.

Garen turned on his side, his body having felt stiff from the inactivity and staying in bed all day.

Soon, the door squeaked once again, and a fairly young, 14 or 15-year-old girl walked in. She was also wearing a nurse’s uniform, and on her hands was a large plate, which had a lot of white lunch boxes on it.

"Lunch is here, sorry to keep you waiting."

The girl placed the plate on the bedside counter, took one lunchbox from the plate and placed it on the countertop.

"The menu for lunch is carrot and potato…. Potato stewed with pork skin, white bread….. unlimited. Please enjoy your meal."

The girl looked pure. As you looked at her you’d notice some naivety; she dared not make eye contact with Garen, who was on the bed, and she stuttered some as she spoke.

"May I know your name?" Garen looked at the girl funnily, suddenly thinking of Ying Er, his younger sister in the previous world. His eyes showed gentleness. "Can you do me a favor?"

"My… My name is Wei Xi. What do you need?" The girl seemed more comfortable, but she still dare not look at Garen.

Wei Xi is a student who worked at the hospital, she had just entered the Chialunar Academy this year, the best medical academy in the city. Although it was renowned in the suburbs only, it was considered to be a good place to be already.

Unexpectedly, among all the nurses that were interning, she’s the only one who was chosen to the advanced care area due to her nice appearance. Especially to care for rich patients.

Inside the advanced care area, if it weren’t nurses with a lot of experience, would be nurses like this; who had very attractive appearances and bodies. To the patients here, the experienced nurses are in charge of practical tasks, while attractive nurses served to soothe the heart and emotions.

Before Wei Xi came, she already heard from others that the patients here are either rich or noblemen; she could easily bump into anyone and meet someone with an immense background.

As she thought of this, she cannot help but feel anxious.

Would he request for something inappropriate from me?

Even though she was thinking that way, but the helpless romantic teen in her couldn’t help but to fantasize that perhaps she could meet a nobleman’s young master. Handsome, charismatic, gentle, compassionate, or he may just like someone like her type, who knows.

At times where she was in a tight spot, he would stand out, shielding her with a tall stature, beating some villains from somewhere, then turned back to gently lift her chin…

The girl was stunned, her face blushing red, occasionally smiling like an idiot.

"Could you help me check on the situation in room 235 and 257? My friends are staying in those wards."

Garen speechlessly sat there as the girl smiled like an idiot, he lightly used his finger to push the girl’s arm.

"Hey, hey, you alright?"

"No… Nothing!" The girl snapped back into focus, "I will immediately check on it for you." Her face blushed red, taking a peek at Garen on his bed, she was shocked and lowered her head again.

"Am I that scary?" Garen picked up the lunchbox, he touched his face with confusion.

Lunch was great, the meat was stewed tender and the soup was very thick, very fragrant.

After hurriedly finishing the lunch, he placed the lunchbox aside.

Garen wiped his mouth, lying against the bedframe, both his arms thickly rolled by rounds upon rounds of bandages, much like a white baseball bat. Only his fingers could move freely

"Was I that scary?"

He was confused, so he picked up a small mirror from a drawer in the bedside countertop, to take a good look at himself.

Looking into the mirror, was a bald head, no hair, no brows, no beard, nothing.

What was a handsome, good-looking appearance, had indeed become appalling under these transformations.

Garen touched his smooth bald head. His hair had been shaved off during the treatment; beard and brows as well. As the flame’s high temperature had burnt off the follicles, rather than a black patch stuck onto the face, they might as well had just shaven it all off.

He touched his own brows, he felt like an alien in an Earthling movie., except he had white skin and facial features.

Not having any eyebrows did make him look slightly fierce. No wonder that little girl would be so afraid.

Over ten minutes later, the girl called Wei Xi knocked on the door and came in again.

"Sir, the two patients in those wards are fine, their situation is under control. The sir called Andy asked you not to worry."

The little girl stood by the door, fearing to approach.

"Do me another favor, I will appreciate it." Garen tries to let himself smile more warmly, so that he doesný scare this little kid. "I am feeling bored; can you grab me some of the latest Global Weeklies?"

"Global Weeklies? Su…. Sure!" Wei Xi, hurriedly agreed. "There’s some in the reading room, I will take it for you immediately."

There were actually free magazines inside the ward, but not the latest ones

Garen didn’t have to wait too long before Wei Xi came back with a stack of newspapers, passing it to him.

"Here’s your newspaper."

This little girl’s smooth brown hair was tied in a ponytail, her pubescent figure had become apparent, as she breathed heavily from all the running to and fro Garen’s bedside. She carried the mild, refreshing fragrance of a teen.

Garen’s warm tone seemed to have worked, Wei Xi are also not as afraid as before, her guts seemed have grown too.

"Anything else that you would like?"

That’s it for now, thank you, cute little one." Garen smiled as he flipped the newspaper.

As he flipped, his first glance landed on a surprising headline.

"Ender’s Ambassador: Orlando’s Diplomat killed."

He continued reading

"Orlando faced a large-scale terrorist attack on the 15th this month; Orlando’s royal guards were defeated in a night, the Royal Family held hostage. This terrorist organization made a public announcement, claiming to be an organization called the Obscuro Society.

During this assault, Diplomat Quelia, who was in talks with the Prince Edinberg of the royal family, was killed.

The Ender Kingdom has issued an emergency press release. The death of Diplomat Quelia is a direct challenge to the integrity of the Ender Kingdom, which the kingdom will not forgive. At the time of the press release, Ender’s third column General Veron has led the Third Military Division towards Orlando, to assist the local royalty in suppressing the terrorists. General Veron had made an announcement before leaving for Orlando, he views the current situation as…."

Garen put down the newspaper, exhaled slightly and did not continue reading.

"So it has begun…"

Even though the newspaper did not do a follow-up coverage, if he hadn't guessed wrongly, what happens next would be General Veron’s team being completely annihilated. Three more small empires will continually be engulfed in unrestl. Obscuro Society’s warring locations will exponentially increase. Heading towards the East Continent’s strongest territories; the three strongest empires.

Canbria, Kovitan, Ender; the three empires comprised the strongest alliance in the East Continent, and also served as the RAL’s main congregation point of power. The strongest totem users were within the Three Departments of the three empires.

The Three Departments may seem like a tool used to iron out administrative or national issues, but it actually consisted of the Luminarists of the RAL.

He flipped through the Global Weeklies, and in the third publication there was a news piece that grabbed his attention.

"Appearance of horrid creatures assaulting humans in Canbria," Under the title was a piece of black and white photograph. This world already had technology similar to photography technology on earth, the research prowess of the Luminarists may not be any weaker than Earth’s scientists.

On the image was a mouse carcass the size of a basin, being held by its tail by a strong man. The men held the mouse on one arm, and showcased the injuries caused by the mouse’s bite on the other forearm.

The flesh on the forearm was bitten badly, the flesh looked mushy, completely red.

"Recently, Canbria had many sightings of strange creatures assaulting humans.. These animals have odd shapes and sizes, and are much more violent compared to normal animals. The Canbrian biological researcher, Eddier, believes that this is a rare reversion symptom, where these creatures will sometimes reverse due to an unknown cause, causing gigantification, and became more violent. According to research estimates, the most likely cause of this reversion is likely pollution.

At the time of the writing of this publication, the Canbrian environmental protection agency had launched spot checks on three separate provinces on the pollution index.

Garen realized that the mouse in the image had something shining in its iris. He squinted and suddenly thought of the howling wererabbit that has successfully evolved, having similar scary looking eyes.

He looked up to his surroundings; The girl called Wei Xi had gone out, and closed the doors behind her.

He got up, walked to the doors, hung up the "Do not disturb "sign, quietly locking the chain of the door.

He pulled up the curtains as well, then sitting on the bed. Garen took the clothes hanging on the rack, taking out a red crystal ball. The sphere was only the size of a fist, and looked like a crystal decoration.

Garen took the ball and lay on his bed.

Chapter 281: Future 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

As he snapped back into focus, the employee had already taken out the keys and opened the door.

"This time, the Governor’s manor took out a grand total of 100 White Dragonhawks as the large scale appendment reward for the mission. One can say that they really hauled their assets. But even then, the missions’ acceptance and completion rates haven’t not increased all that much either." The employee sighed, "The missions’ difficulty recently is really hard to determine, most of the totem users do not dare to simply pick up a mission. Furthermore, the amount of people accepting mission have also reduced greatly. That’s why there was the White Dragonhawk being given out as a reward."

She looked at the checklist.

"But there’s none for you to be amused for, that is primarily the reward for the Hurricane Group. Your reward is at the lowest rank."

Garen was stunned.

"The main completer of the mission is Hurricane Group? What do you mean?"

The employee gave him a weird look. "Of course they are the main force of this mission’s completion. The Hurricane Group annihilated this terrorist totem users’ hideout, exploded massive amounts of white totem bombs, they have already pick up their reward yesterday. You small fries are lucky, not being sucked into the midst of the battle and yet qualify for the rewards, that’s one hundred thousand Silver Rumbs for each of you."

Garen’s heart sank.

"You mean, this mission is mainly completed by Hurricane Group?"

"Like this, there was actually a form 1 totem user inside, I saw their mission process, they completed with blood sweat and tears. What’s up with you?" The female employee looked at him weirdly.

"One form 2 totem user…? Haha…" Garen laughed coldly, such blasphemy of saying three top ranked form 2 totem users from Obscuro Society was said to be one, it was obviously the explosion of the kinetic furnace, but they said it was the white totem bomb. This Hurricane Group is so talented, they can make up any stories.

He walked into the wooden room.

"This is your reward." The employee gave Garen a small black bag.

Garen did not budge, and did not take up the black bag.

He glanced, and he sse that three middle-age men standing on the right side on the window, quietly looking over here.

He knows, in the situation where Goth was is absent, whatever he said carries no weight. Nobody would believe a group that has no form 2 totem user, to be able to kill three form 2 totem users, and yet being able to walk out of the hideout without any deaths.

Comparatively, everyone would definitely believe Hurricane Group’s lies better.

It’s believed that even Hurricane Group were not entirely sure about what happened, and not knowing the changes on Goth’s body. That’s why they would simply make up the story.

Garen admitted that even though he has an additional Howling Wererabbit and that his defenses are slightly stronger, but in a frontal confrontation, needless to say that he still could not break through form 2 totem user’s totem light.

"I’m sorry, but I feel that this reward was not calculated properly."

"Not counted properly?" The female employee frowned, she is also a totem user, even though just a form 1 totem, but her time was not to be wasted recklessly. "Which part did we not calculate properly? You point it out, I want to be responsible to my work."

Garen smiled politely.

"I actually want to say, in this mission, there were some minute details that the Hurricane Group did not explain properly. That would be something my group leader personally experienced, so I hope that when my group leader gets discharged, he can come over to amend the process of the mission."

The female employee looked at Garen for a while

"If you insist, I can stop this reward claim, but you have to understand, it may happen that these rewards may be claimed by others."

She stopped and frowned.

"Or, if you think Hurricane had inaccurate recount of the missions, they you are wasting your effort. The people from the guild have already sent people to check it, everything is normal."

Garen realized, the man by the window have left unknowingly. He had some plans, so he didn’t say too much to the employee.

"It doesn’t matter, soon our group leader will come personally to speak, saying anything now serves no purpose."

He did not plan to iron this out, the Hurricane group can be left to Goth, who can erupt his talents. That dude can even take on three form 2 totem users from Obscuro society, nevermind the tiny Hurricane Group.

"Up to you." The lady shrugged her shoulder.

Both of them turned around, left the room and walked back.

A few passers-by workers saw that Garen had come back with nothing on hand, they couldn’t help but to looked at him a few more times.

Back in the mission hall, Garen politely said thank you to the female employee. And asked her for a name card.

"Tavi Nesser" Garen looked at the name card, then carefully kept it.

The mission hall at the time it was bustling with more people, among them was a sturdy, looking tall man, staring at Garen with a smirk.

As he saw Garen walking out, he slowly stood up.

Garen frowned as he glanced at these people. He exited the mission hall, walked down a few steps, and headed straight towards the Chialunar Hospital.

As he expected, there were a few people tailing him.

He realized that these people are wearing a hurricane badges around their chests.

Garen picked up his pace and walked along the streets. The three people behind him followed closely.

Two people walked in a single file and mixed into the crowd, walking against the current of people.

Garen turned his head around occasionally.

"I’m just reconnaissance, not a combatant, these things are best left to the professionals." He mumbled as he moved faster.

The footwork of his secret ability was used without sound, the speed got faster and faster.

Soon they were left behind in dust.

He hadn’t received the rewards. He took a huge detour around town, and in the end he still decided to go back to the hospital. He was prepared to tell Goth and andy about the rewards being taken by Hurricane, so that they, in turn would be mentally prepared.

He rushed into the hospital. By the entrance of the white, five-story building, stood a few people with hurricane badges.

Garen was about to walk over, but he stopped short, standing at the back side of the of the building.

"Now I’ll have no choice."Garen waited outside the building for a while, he soon saw two young nurses walking out of the hospital building.

One of them was 14-15 years old. It was indeed the nurse who got her lunch.

He suddenly had an idea. He waited until the nurse approached, and walked around the two of them to stop them.

"That.. Wei Xi!" Garen stopped in front of them, loudly screaming that sentence.

The two nurses were just chatting softly suddenly heard themselves being called. They lifted their heads and got scared so badly, their faces paled.

A bald, browless, beardless scary man blocked their path, this man had a perverted smile as he stared at them, his mouth had hints of violence and cunningness.

Garen did not expect that his kind smile have scared the two brats this badly… he quickly reduced his smile, trying his best to show a peaceful look.

"Wei Xi, I am the guy whom you sent lunch to, remember?"

Wei Xi immediately recalled this patient who left strong impression, she stood in front of her friend.

"You…. You need anything?" her tongue tied. She’s motivated.

"Could you help me out?" Garen smiled, scaring the girls that she shuddered.

Two minutes later, Garen looked at the silhouettes walk into the hospital, his heart calmed.

He turned around, and caught three Hurricane people blocking his rear, quietly staring at him. On the opposite side of the left street, one man wearing a white hat with golden bezel walked towards him, on his chest was the same black-white hurricane badge.

On the man’s badge was two silver horizontal lines.

"Form 2?" Garen suddenly understood the meaning of the horizontal lines.

"Good eyesight.."the young man walked within five meters from Garen, stopped his movements, and picked up a cigarette from his shirt pocket. He slowly lit the cigarette and took a puff.

"Honestly, you ran really quickly. If I wasn’t guarding here coincidentally, I may not have necessarily been able to catch you. Nice to meet you, the name’s Casey."

"I’m just a nobody." Garen smirked and laughed. He just realized that on the roof, not far from him, stood a sparrow. It’s eyes had a hint of silver.

Alright, no more bullshit. I am here to align our verbal records." The young man Casey said calmly, "This time’s mission, only our Hurricane group and your panther group survived, there were two other groups who died inside. I don’t know what happened inside, but to get any mission reward, our records have to be aligned, understood?"

"What do you mean?" the smile on Garen’s face calmed down.

"The moment you received the reward, send it to this address, you can keep one third of it." Casey puffed a smoke, spewing a white smoke ring, his eyes seemed calm. "Think of it as the reward for us Hurricane group for protecting you.

"The mission was completed by us."

Garen said calmly, quietly looking at the other party.

"You completed it?" Casey shook his head, "I was the one who exploded the white totem bombs, I killed the only form 2 totem user, you said you completed it? What are you?"

"Haha." Garen only laughed.

"Laughing? You’re happy?" Casey looked angry. "I’ll make you laugh!" His slap swiped towards Garen.

"Pap!"

Suddenly, Casey’s hand was caught.

"You’re so full of yourself, brat." A red silhouette came flying, a man wearing a ref bib stood in front of Garen, facing Casey with a bright smile.

"Let go!" Casey’s face turned dark.

"Nope."

"I said, let go!"Casey screamed. His face twitched,, obviously he was angered to the brink.

"I don’t wanna let go, hit me if you can." Goth smiled snarkily, pushing his face towards Casey.

"You are seeking death!" Casey finally burst into anger, one tight slap flung towards Goth.

Pap!

A burst of harsh crisp sound was heard.

Garen was stunned as he looked at where the two were. Although he already noticed the arrival of Goth and the team, but he did not realize that Goth, who had a wire loose in his head, would ever use this method.

Casey was seen holding his face, filled with disbelief, as he stared at Goth.

"Hit me, come one, hit me!!" Goth had a face that was asking for a beating. He pointed at his hips, twerking his buttocks "Here! Kick here, use some force!!"

"Fuck!!" Casey is incredibly angry, and rushed forward to get a good kick.

Ouch!!!

A painful scream was hurt.

Casey knelt down to the ground, his body shining with an inconsistent light film, but this layer of light is clearly was not able to stop this fatal blow.

Chapter 282: Future 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

Andy shook his head and walked over, standing alongside Garen.

"Poor thing… There would be no reason to provoke anyone else, much less Goth. You okay, Garen?"

"I’m fine." Garen had already realised the oncoming presence of the two other people much earlier. Thus, he allowed the Hurricane squad members to do as they pleased. He never expected that it would turn out so well.

As for the three remaining Hurricane squad members, the moment they saw their leader collapse, a terrified look appeared on their faces at once, and they didn’t know whether to advance or to escape.

"Go! We’re leaving!" Casey yelled loudly, looking at Goth as if he were a monster, with his face all twisted like that.

"You dare think of leaving?!" Goth spat as he rubbed his hands together, rushing forward in a fit of rage.

"They stole the reward for the task we completed!" Garen quickly reminded him at this crucial moment. "They impersonated us!"

His words enraged Goth even more. Every one of his slaps that landed on Casey’s face brought on rays of black light that caused a prickly sensation, making it seem as if countless sharp thorns had grown on his body.

These sharp thorns pierced through Casey’s totem light easily. Furthermore, Goth’s speed and strength had grown to the point where it was now terrifying to others.

Garen watched Goth’s movements. The speed at which Goth rotated his arm and pushed it downwards always made Garen’s heart jump slightly.

It seemed like this guy had already achieved the strength and speed he was only supposed to possess after his successfully using his Godlike Accomplishment skill.

Although he had known from the beginning that certain appraisal geniuses could get an increase in strength from their core totems, he never expected Goth’s improvements to be of such great magnitude.

Moreover, Goth had only recently awakened his potential, and had not fully released it yet. Before his full release, there was no telling how more powerful he would be in his final stage.

"No wonder he was able to reach the level of single-handedly winning a fight." Garen was still in shock. He had practiced his Secret Technique just to achieve the Godlike Accomplishment skill, and had gone through many difficulties and hard times such as having to kill others in order to reach his goal.

Apart from his fighting skills, Goth’s physical body and fitness levels were also vastly different from before as well.

In Garen’s mind, everything seemed somewhat unbalanced.

Casey and the other three members of the Hurricane squad were beaten up and forced to the ground by Goth. He had easily thrown them against the wall as if they were merely objects. The scene frightened off the passersby on the street and they ran away quickly, worried that they might become casualties in this fight.

As Casey looked over at Goth, his own expression changed from embarrassment and fury into fear and dread. He was certain that his opponent’s strength surpassed that of a regular Form 2 totem user. Ultimately, he had no choice but to release his own totem and fight to the death. But the moment he released it, his plan was foiled instantly. Goth would eventually destroy his totem, completely ruining his many years of hard work in the process. Without a Form 2 totem, he wouldn’t be able to defend the Hurricane squad for long.

If his opponent possessed the ability to break through a totem user’s totem light, judging from the current state of his totem’s defenses, wrecking his totem would be a piece of cake.

In the end, Casey could only endure Goth’s vicious attacks silently. He wrapped his arms around his head and crouched into a ball as he was too afraid to retaliate.

In the corner of the street, the both of them looked like a couple of gangsters. Goth single-handedly beat the three of them up without having to put up much of a fight, then forced Casey to return both of the White Dragonhawk rewards. He also made him pay compensation in the form of a mental loss fee, safety threat fee, loss of reputation fee as well as a series of other payments totalling to 820,000 silver rumbs.

Both parties signed a contract and stamped their fingerprints with a blood seal. Casey finally understood that this man, Goth, had truly possessed a strength that would be able to defeat Form 2 totem users. If someone provoked him again with the outskirts of the city currently in a state of chaos, so long as he found a desolate place to intercept them, his enemies could call on the whole world for help, but no one would be able to save them.

Once Casey and his group had left, Goth wiped his hands and hid the contract in his clothes carefully, and patted his pocket.

"Let’s go. We’ll find somewhere we can sit."

"Yes," nodded Andy. "According to what I’ve heard, we should leave this place quickly since we’ve already completed the task. We should also follow the rules while we’re at it."

Garen nodded as well.

The three of them turned the street corner and came across a coffee shop where they found a table against the wall and sat there, before ordering a cup of milk coffee each.

The atmosphere inside the coffee shop was calm, as there were only five or six other customers, sitting around in different spots. Everyone spoke in hushed voices when they conversed.

There was a white piano in front, where a man dressed in white played the soothing melody of an unknown song.

On the left corner of the wall where the three men were seated, the latest edition of the calendar had been hung up, and all the dates which had passed were ticked off with a little red check mark. The last unmarked date was the 24th of the second month.

"We’re entering spring already," said Garen before he lifted his coffee cup and drank from it. "This year’s winter hardly seemed as cold as the years before."

"I kind of agree. It still felt like autumn to me, I hardly felt any difference," nodded Andy. "The situation at the guild has been worsening recently. One of my acquaintances came to see me recently and I asked him about it. Two of the largest employment squads in the Luminarist guild, Black Light and Blue Leaf, encountered great difficulties in completed their most recent task, and the Black Light squad even lost two of their members. They were Iron Tank City’s strongest totem user employment squad! Both the captain and vice captain are Form 3 final stage totem users, yet they still lost 2 members. The current situation is really dire."

"When I went to the guild, I noticed that there were less people inside as well," said Garen quietly.

"My friend is in charge of preparing the statistic reports, and according to him, there are about eighty to a hundred lower rank squads like ours in the guild. But in the most recent month, a lot of the smaller squads left and never returned. Some of them were even middle range squads with one or two Form 2 totem users, and even they suffered serious injuries. Currently five guild points have become significantly quieter."

"Don’t worry. You guys still have me, remember? I’ll protect you," said Goth lazily, as he drank the remainder of his coffee in a few gulps.

Both of them shook their heads and flat-out ignored him.

Andy continued, saying: "The casualties sustained by the guild in the previous year is still higher, but the ratio would never be more than ten to one, meaning one death would occur in ten tasks on average. Meanwhile this year, the ratio had already risen to five to one. I assume that the higher ups in the guild would have taken the necessary measures already. Right now, I’d suggest that we nurse of our wounds for the time being. Once our bodies have healed properly, we can absorb this task’s reward, and by then, the situation would be pretty much clearer. Whether or not we continue accept tasks after that will depend on how we feel in the future. How about that?"

Garen nodded quietly. He understood what Andy was thinking. They were only trying to earn a quick buck, and train themselves while they were at it. They weren’t trying to place their lives on the line, so there was no need for them to accept tasks that were unnecessarily dangerous. Even if a totem user merely decided to join a security organization, their livelihoods would still be at least three times better than that of an average person. They would be able to lead a good and simple life. Those who undertook tasks from the guild were mostly thrill seekers that wanted to improve themselves at the same time.

"These are important national matters. As long as the higher ups are worried about it, it’s none of our business," said Andy as he sighed in relief. He smiled and continued, saying: "No matter what, Goth, this time both Jessica and I owe you our lives. If you ever need any help in the future, just feel free to say it without holding back!" He patted Goth’s shoulder as he said.

It was rare for Goth to be quiet, and now a look of concentration had appeared on his face. "Actually, I just want a simple life. As long as I have good food and drink, and a gentle girlfriend, all I’d have to do is to work hard so that all the other bastards will not look down on me anymore. Then we could leave our homes just like we’re doing now, and I could still lead a happy life. After that I’d want to have two sons, and name one of them Andy, and the other one Garen."

"Why you little!" Andy could not stop himself from punching him. "But my old man has already ordered me to never return to the guild again because of the scars on Jessica’s face, which made my mother cry for two whole days. After this… After this, I don’t think it’s likely that I’d be able to accept tasks anymore," he said as his voice grew softer. "I’ve gained almost enough experience, and since I’ve gotten the proof of my mission from the guild, once I’ve applied for a position in the national institution, my well being will increase significantly. Who knows, I might even get a job as a junior officer."

His words were tinged with a sense of parting.

The three of them became quiet for a moment.

"Since you already have the qualifications from the last two tasks, what department are you thinking of joining? Just choose one, and I’ll submit the application for you. Any department will do. There’s a Mercenary’s Guild in every part of the East Continent, and with your qualifications, you’d get a good position even if you were sent to the imperial family," said Andy with a smile. "Or if you’d prefer, you could go to a college or somewhere like that and work as a security officer, or even a specialized speaker. There are tons of beautiful girls in the school, you know."

Goth lowered his head, and stopped speaking for a short while.

"I’ll do it at my own pace…" he replied quietly. "What about you, Garen? Any plans?"

"I don’t even have a home to return to, what plans could someone like me have?" said Garen as he shrugged. "I’m planning to wait and see. I don’t even have any plans or arrangements on my mind at the moment."

"You’re 21 years old already, right? You aren’t young anymore, you should be making plans for your future by now. Why don’t I introduce you to a girl, but definitely not someone who lives a promiscuous life on her own," said Andy earnestly. "Start your own household earlier, then you’ll finally have someone to depend on in your heart. You’ll also have a goal to fight for."

"We’ll see," Garen shook his head. "I’m not thinking of that at the moment." He was certain that not long from now, the city would be filled with danger and trouble. Goth and the others would have no choice but to contribute by joining the movement to get rid of the surrounding dangerous creatures.

Almost all of the totem users would not be able to rest during that time.

Obscuro Society’s major course of action was about to begin soon. This peaceful period of life would only last for a few more days.

He was unlike the two others because he wasn’t a local in this world, he was merely a passerby. His goal was actually to find the secret that he had brought over with him. This whole time he had been trying to control his fate.

Life was hard and short, and after about a hundred and ten short years, in order to continue living, one would need to have something of value to pursue.

A vague idea began pounding at the back of Garen’s mind. He no longer wanted to just go with the flow. In his personal experience, he had too many doubts that he wanted to understand.

In this universe, what could truly be considered eternal…

"Don’t think too much about that," said Andy as he patted his shoulder.

Before Garen, Andy, and Goth went their separate ways, they made sure to exchange contact information and addresses.

Garen left the coffee shop on his own, and walked down the lane for a distance, before stretching his arm out and hailing a passing horse carriage.

"To the trade area," he said as he got onto the carriage.

The coachman was a middle-aged man with a short beard.

"The trade area huh… That’s quite a distance from here. We’ll have to exit this area, sir. And distances further than ten kilometers require additional charges as well. Which part of the trade area are you heading towards?"

Garen nodded, showing the man that he knew the price. "To Wellington Street. Do you know where that is?"

"I need to go deeper into the area if it’s Wellington. Are you perhaps going to the pet market, sir?" asked the coachman in an experienced voice.

"That’s the place."

"How’s eight silver rumbs?"

"That’s fine," answered Garen at once.

Once he had seated himself inside, he leaned against the right side of the carriage and felt as if the front of the carriage had fallen off. Moments later, it hobbled forward and off they went.

Outside the window, the roads rolled past continuously, and out of the rows of white living quarters, shops could occasionally be seen.

As the carriage galloped towards the trade area, the roads outside the carriage gradually became dirtier. They began to pass by an increasing number of horse carriages, including a beautifully built one at one point. Ox carts that sold fruits also passed them by on the lane, but were quickly overtaken by the carriage.

Calming his emotions, Garen began to look forward to the types of wild animals he would be able to purchase soon.

As long as there were no accidents, Goth would not need the White Dragonhawk. He was currently undergoing his power explosion stage, and would definitely be faced with an abundance of stronger totems in the future. However, the same did not apply to himself. He had already waited until the eleventh hour. He needed to decide on his core totem as soon as possible, and then evolve it quickly. If he failed in doing so, he would not be able to fight in the upcoming Great War.

Garen finally had a plan in his heart. His next step was to decide on which creature to evolve as his second totem. He also needed to increase his strength to the best of his abilities, so that he could hunt more totem users in the Great War, and attain more potential points.

Chapter 283: Market 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

The Pet Market.

On both sides of the road, pet cages were arranged and packed closely together. There were rows of them in various heights, sizes, and colours. Most of them were either light coloured or white.

A few elegantly dressed ladies and young female aristocrats shielded themselves with white parasols as they strolled through the market, observing and purchasing the pets that were for sale.

Horse drawn carriages stopped beside the entrance along the lane as new customers alighted and entered the market.

A bald man walked out leisurely from one of the black carriages. He had no hair on his head, no beard, and no eyebrows, making his face seem like a freshly carved white wax figure. There wasn’t a single strand of hair on his face, and his whole head was completely bare. His peculiar look caused the surrounding passersby to look over at him with curious glances.

This man handed the transport fee to the coachman, before tidying the white casual garments he wore.

"Sir, do you need a scarf? It’s only five copper rumbs," said a child as he rushed over to sell a sun-shading scarf to the man.

The man bought the scarf and wrapped it around his head.

Starting from the the left side of the market, he observed the animals as he strolled through the street slowly.

A man in grey clothes carried a grey owl on his hand and spoke loudly but slightly inarticulately, attempting to promote his wares to two aristocratic women. The owl on his arm would turn its head occasionally, a sign that it was in reasonably good spirits.

Up ahead, a plump man wearing a turban with a white gemstone patted the large metal cage beside him and began to introduce the clouded leopard pacing inside. It was obvious that the lynx was feeling restless because of the heat.

Further in front, a group of upper class women gathered around a little pet shop that sold rabbits and squirrels, giggling softly from time to time.

Garen inched forward slowly as his line of sight grazed over the various cages. His mind was constantly filled with thoughts.

"Empowered totems cannot be kept inside storage tools, but must be left outside. They also need to consume food and excrete. Could these things empower human beings as well?" the thought crossed his mind suddenly.

His face remained expressionless, as Garen continued to move forward and look at every single one of the cages.

Eagles, cheetahs, wildcats, hounds, pythons, and spiders were among the many other pets that could be found here.

Suddenly, his feet stopped moving. He stood in front of a large aquarium.

Inside the blue water tank, a large great white shark swam around nonchalantly.

"Sir, are you interested in buying this great white shark? If you purchase it now, I’ll also throw in a gift. Every great white shark purchase comes with a free aquarium," said a friendly, thin man who smelled like the ocean.

"I have other kinds of aquatic creatures here in my shop, and a few types of amphibians as well. You can feel free to have a look. Crocodiles, wolf fish, decorative goldfish, black-headed prawns, cylindrical snails, and jellyfish. Anything you want, we’ll catch it for you!"

"Oh?" Garen declined to comment. "I’d like to see the crocodiles."

"Please come inside, sir," said the slim man as he enthusiastically led Garen into the dark, damp part of the shop. He had opened his shop here a long time ago, initially thinking that the rich lords and ladies would have an affinity towards strange aquatic creatures. He never expected his business to flop the entire time. It was rare enough for him to come across a customer who was actually interested in buying something, thus it was only natural for him not to let this chance escape.

Garen entered the shop. He saw a deep pit in the left side of the shop, where two short-tailed crocs were crawling around lazily. One of the crocodiles stretched its mouth wide open, as its sharp teeth snapped at a flock of little white birds.

"On its own, the crocodile has a strong defensive armor. If it was empowered into a Silver Totem, I’m not sure how much stronger my Totem Light would become because of that." Garen wanted to buy the crocodile for its full body of tough armor. Even if he decided to just raise it at home, the Totem Light that he would gain from the crocodile was probably more than what he would gain from most living creatures.

"I’d like a crocodile, so how much would that cost?"

"Just thirty thousand, thirty thousand silver rumbs. Hehe," The skinny man was happier beyond his wildest expectations. He never thought that he’d be able to seal a deal for a pet with a customer that just walked in.

"Done. Please send it to this address later." Garen took out a pen, and was about to write down the hotel’s address, before stopping himself abruptly. "Hold on. I’ll come back later and confirm the location with you. Here’s the deposit."

Garen took out a thousand silver rumbs and counted them for the skinny shopkeeper, before leaving his name and informing the man that he would return later.

After leaving the aquatic pet shop, Garen continued journeying forwards and took his time looking around.

In a short while, he decided upon three giant desert monitor lizards from a different pet shop. All three of them were lizards with dark blue coloured backs, and had each grown to be more than one meter in length. Their skin felt like a kind of rough cloth when touched.

Garen pressed his finger against the giant lizard’s skin and realised that it was actually quite tough.

These three giant desert monitor lizards had only cost Garen ten thousand silver rumbs. However, it was rumoured that these creatures could be used to form a blood relation with the legendary dragon. Garen was interested to try this out, to see if it was possible to evolve them into a similar type of living totem.

But of course, everything depended on the requirements for the core totem’s foundation to be met first.

This kind of blue back lizard excelled in drilling holes and possessed swift movements. Furthermore, they also had highly poisonous glands that could cause paralysis. They were extremely unsuitable as domesticated pets. A moment of negligence would allow them an opportunity to drill holes and escape. Thus, the shop owner was unable to sell them for their full price, which caused their value to decrease rapidly. Never had he expected a customer like Garen, someone who was so entranced by these creatures. This shop owner was also delighted beyond expectation, and decided to sell all three of his giant lizards to Garen.

Next, Garen also purchased three grey feathered hawks. These hawks were extremely fierce despite their small stature. This particular female hawk was especially impressive, as it was often found with leopards in the northern highlands. This was another creature that was superb even at its foundation level.

One short-tailed croc, three grey feathered hawks, and three giant desert monitor lizards. A total of seven animals, and when Garen’s current howling wererabbit was added to the list, that brought the grand total to eight. Garen still planned to leave two empty spots in case there were better choices for him to substitute later.

These creatures cost him a total of seventy thousand silver rumbs.

He decided to give up on a getting custom-made totem. Custom-made totems were definitely more suited to totem users compared to standard totems, and the better suited a totem was to its totem user, the easier it was to evolve it. However, Garen had already acquired excellent abilities, making it redundant for him to pay the exorbitant fees just for a custom-made totem.

After paying the deposit, Garen followed the crowd into a different street.

He looked at the relaxed aristocrats that passed by him, every one of them oblivious to the upcoming chaos.

Most of these people were unaware of the existence of Luminarists. They lived in a fabricated world of pretend, naively believing that the cavalry, archers, patrol guards, swordsmen, and musketeers were all there was to war. Unbeknownst to them, the real war was the one that was fought by totem users and Luminarists, and they were in charge of the actual decision-making.

Totems were banned from meddling in wars between normal people, and this was a rule. But people who were the slightest bit knowledgeable were already aware of the importance of totem users. Both war and peace were controlled by the hands of these few people.

"General Wellan recently led Anita’s third legion of nearly a hundred thousand men out to battle, who knows how long it will take before the war ends. My husband is part of that army as their logistics officer," said an upper class lady with an anxious look on her face, holding a white rabbit in her arms. "I don’t even know if he’s taking care of himself properly while he’s out there."

"Don’t worry. Brother-in-law will be fine. He’s a man. Big sister, look at my squirrel. Isn’t it cute?" Nearby, a red-headed young lady stroked the squirrel in her palm happily.

Garen passed by the two ladies, and heard bits and pieces of their conversation.

In the eyes of the average person, General Wellan had led one hundred thousand soldiers out to battle, and had three of the bravest and fiercest army captains under his command.

However, the people who truly decided the outcome of the battle were not these hundred thousand men, but the other thousand over totem users who had left a long time ago, but whose whereabouts and statuses remained unknown.

The wars of totem users and normal people were vastly different, and they always selected their battle sites individually. The moment one sector of totem users was defeated, their commander would automatically declare their surrender.

The majority of totem users would not slaughter normal people, but this resulted in a lot of predetermined outcomes, many of which concluded with the weak beating the strong. The difference in soldier numbers resulted in a wide disparity between both sides, but this was ultimately caused by the totem users’ unanimous surrender when defeated in battle.

Garen’s train of thought began to deviate, so he waved down a horse-drawn carriage and headed towards the outskirts of the city quickly.

He needed to find a house that would solely belong to him, or else it would be impossible for him to house this many Silver Totems.

He returned to his hotel and packed his belongings, before rushing off to the nearest home rental center.

In the home rental center, he chose a house with a big courtyard on the outskirts of the city, which included a lake and man-made grassy mountains, which amounted to its huge perimeter. The house was somewhat decrepit, but the rental was only required to be paid once every two years, and each payment was twenty thousand silver rumbs.

This was a considerably cheap price.

Currently, Garen did not have much money left, and once he had totalled his remaining bits of money, after the purchase of his pets, he was left with less than three hundred thousand silver rumbs. At the request of the landlord, he was led outside and brought to see the courtyard. After that, he paid the two-year rental fee in one payment.

Next, Garen went to the pet market street again, and gave his new address to the shop keepers.

He had no plans to visit other pet markets. To be honest, most animals could already be found here, the remaining ones were merely lions, tigers, bears and other ferocious beasts. He hardly cared about these common creatures, because as far as their defense was concerned, lions and tigers did not have the armor the crocodile possessed. The most important factor was that for large carnivorous animals, one was definitely enough. If you empowered more than one, their daily meat intake would definitely increase to an insane amount.

Once the Great War broke out, there would definitely not be enough meat to sustain all these creatures.

**************

On the outskirts of Iron Tank City where people were scarce, a few courtyards stood spaciously away from one another.

One of the courtyards was surrounded by a grey fence, and on the green grass stood a mountain shaped double-storey building. The little building had white floors and black sides, and looked somewhat unkempt on first glance. Certain parts of the windows had wilted yellow vines growing all over them.

A gust of wind blew over, blowing the grass and causing the yellowed leaves to roll away.

Garen alighted the carriage, and stood in front of the gates of the courtyard.

He turned his head and looked in the opposite direction and saw a similar looking courtyard, except that there were flowering fruit trees growing in the other courtyard, and a young woman who was holding a watering can and watering the flowers.

The girl also noticed Garen standing opposite her, and her face immediately broke out into a friendly smile.

Garen smiled back at her too.

Garen looked for the key and unlocked the latch on the fence, before walking into the courtyard that he had just rented for himself.

Woof woof!

The sound of a dog barking could be heard from the courtyard on the opposite side.

"Teller! Damn you, don’t you dare pee there! Do you hear me?!" The girl yelled loudly from the opposing courtyard. "Teller! Teller!!!" She threw her watering can down and chase a golden retriever into the back of the house.

Garen turned to look in her direction, before removing the key from his pocket. He stuck it into the keyhole of his front door and turned the handle.

Ka-chak.

The door creaked when it was pulled open towards the outside, as a mouldy smell that came from inside the house began to waft towards him.

Chapter 284: Market 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

"Cough cough," Garen muffled his nose as he walked inside.

The first floor was completely empty as all the furniture had been moved out. In the hall on the first floor, there was a corridor on the left side which led to the backyard, kitchen, and other rooms. There was a wooden spiral staircase on the right side which led to the second floor. The red paint on the staircase had mostly faded, making it obvious that this place had aged.

Garen opened all the windows and doors, and noticed that the place was covered in dust.

He coughed as he walked out of the house, before coming across an advertisement on the wall for cleaning services.

Immediately, he left the house for a short while, and came back with four middle aged women holding cleaning supplies behind him.

The four women entered the house and began cleaning noisily, while Garen stood at the side with his arms folded across his chest, waiting patiently.

Once everything settled down and his pets had arrived, he would then be able to begin the totem empowerment process. After a few days, until the White Dragonhawk finally returned, and once he had obtained his core totem, he would finally be able to go to the War Guild to begin hunting. As for the grains that he was currently hoarding, it would only be a matter of time before he would profit greatly from that.

He mentally counted the days until the arrival of the Great War. Everything had been arranged accordingly, and he only had to make sure that he followed his plan step-by-step to ensure that it would go smoothly.

"Hey."

A young woman’s voice called out behind him.

Garen turned around and saw the woman who lived in the opposite house walking towards him, carrying a golden retriever.

"Hey there, I just moved in today, and I’ll be living here from now on," said Garen with a smile and an outstretched palm. "Garen. Garen Lombard."

"Alice. Alice Weller," said the girl as she reached her hand out and shook hands with Garen. "Are you renting or…"

"Renting. But I might be buying," said Garen, smiling. "How long have you been living here, Alice?"

"This is my grandfather’s house, and I like reading books and relaxing here. I’ve been living here for almost three years," Alice recalled. "The environment here is not bad, and it’s pretty far from the city area. No one else is living in the surrounding courtyards either, and it seems like both our courtyards are the only ones with tenants. Many years have passed while these houses remained empty. There are a total of twenty-three courtyards in the Yellow Wind district, and it was once filled with people, but currently it seems as if there are only five households living here."

She shrugged her shoulders as a restless expression appeared on her face. "Did you know, that the distance between this place and the city is unnecessarily far? It’s extremely inconvenient when you need to go out to buy groceries or vegetables, and the only water supplied to us comes from a few deep wells nearby.

"But it’s quiet enough," Garen added, "This was the criteria I was looking at when I decided to move here. My job on its own is noisy enough, and I wouldn’t be able to handle it if my living space was noisy as well."

"True enough," agreed Alice as she nodded her head. This young girl, who looked no more than twenty years of age, definitely possessed certain intellectual abilities. She wore a white top and a matching pair of white trousers, making her seem like a simple but generous person. Her long blonde hair was tied in a ponytail, and her figure was not perfect, but not bad either. She didn’t have a gorgeous face and was better described as average. However, she had an unusually sharp mind and a mature sense of understanding.

She didn’t seem the slightest bit afraid of Garen’s lack of eyebrows, beard, or hair. When she noticed Garen’s doubtful gaze, she smiled and started to explain.

"My grandfather used to look just like you. A big fire burned off his eyebrows, beard, and even half of the hair on his head. Thus, the moment I laid my eyes on you, I knew that you were just like him. When I look closely, I can see that you’re actually quite handsome."

"Thank you for your compliments. I guess I should be thanking your grandfather as well, as he helped me avoid scaring you," said Garen with a laugh.

"Okay, I’ll head off first. There are still some things over there that I’ve yet to finish,"

"Alright."

Garen watched Alice turn around and walk back into her own courtyard before turning his gaze away. He continued to wait as the cleaners finished their work.

The four women went to take water from the deep well nearby and washed the courtyard. The trouble they went through to get the water ended up costing Garen an extra five silver rumbs.

The sun had started to set before the courtyard was finally cleaned.

Garen arranged the wooden mailbox outside the courtyard properly and noted down the address and house number written there, before visiting the district’s post office and registering his new residence.

He went out and hired a horse drawn carriage before piling various kinds of everyday items into his house. Next, he wrote letters to Andy, Jessica, and Goth respectively to inform them about his new address.

Dinner consisted of breadsticks dipped in strawberry jam.

Once everything had been arranged properly, it was already late at night.

Before long, the shop keepers from the pet stores arrived with his pets. The pet market was run by a single management, thus various sellers from the market helped move seven metal cages from the ox cart into Garen’s house, one at a time.

Standing in the garden, Garen held a glass lamp and watched the ox cart from the pet market leave, disappearing from his field of vision almost instantly.

He turned and walked towards the garden behind him.

Seven different pets were waiting to be empowered by him.

After checking his surroundings carefully, Garen realised that this place was just as Alice had described it. It was very quiet, and the closest house in the vicinity was at least a hundred meters away.

He stood in front of the seven differently sized cages. He stretched his arm outwards and picked up the first cage, before walking towards the back door.

He closed the door and hung the glass lamp from the right door handle.

Garen lifted the black cloth on the cage, and looked at the blue back lizard that was crawling around inside.

He placed the cage on the floor and carefully took out a red crystal ball from the inner parts of his cloth bag. The crystal ball was a palm-sized Derivator.

Gingerly, he placed the Derivator next to the metal cage.

The crystal ball began to glow, and a red light illuminated his face. A line of words began to float up from it.

‘Are you empowering the nearby creature?’

"Yes."

The blue back lizard became restless immediately, and started to pace around in its cage, as if it was trying to avoid the red light shining on its body, but to no avail.

The crystal ball slowly changed the colour of its light to a silver hue, as the silver light began to envelop the giant lizard. The lizard seemed as if it was paralysed when it stopped moving suddenly, and remained in its original position.

Tch!

A ray of silver light shot out of the crystal ball and landed on the giant lizard’s head.

Exactly five seconds later, the silver light disappeared quickly, and the crystal ball became red once again.

"Empowerment completed. The creature’s appearance is being recorded. The main body is being linked and transferred… Please do not move," announced the crystal ball suddenly as it shot a ray of red light towards Garen.

Just as before, a warm, pleasant feeling could be felt on the areas that were illuminated by the red light.

A 3D icon of the new totem also appeared in the skill pane in the bottom of his field of vision.

‘Blue back lizard: First form living totem, can be upgraded. Evolution success rate: 66% (The smaller the size, the higher the success rate). Potential points consumption: 300%.

Abilities: Venom, drilling.’

"Three points, huh… This thing apparently consumes three points…" said Garen as he furrowed his brows.

He let the giant lizard out of its cage and repeated the earlier process. He brought all of the cages into his house and used the Derivator to empower every one of them.

Three blue back lizards, three grey feathered hawks, one short-tailed croc, as well as the howling wererabbit. A total of eight Silver Totems.

Garen stood on the walkway at the back of his house and lifted his arms, looking at the endless blue, grey, and black Totem Lights that covered his hands.

The three colours finally merged together into a blue-black colour.

He held the crystal ball Derivator and looked at the message that was displayed there.

‘Your Excellency Garen, your current Totem Light ranking is: Form 2 normal. Your Totem Light consists of eight different types of Silver Totems that have been overlaid with one another.

"I’ve achieved Form 2 Totem Light already?" Garen’s heart was overjoyed. Although he had yet to learn the ways of a Form 2 totem user, and did not have the multitude of special abilities of an average Form 2 totem user, but the fact that his defence level had reached Form 2 was reason enough for him to celebrate.

The pets that he selected, other than the howling wererabbit, were all creatures that excelled at defence. The blue back lizard had skin that was highly resistant to corrosion, and the grey-feathered hawk had feathers that would naturally take the blow when it was bitten or attacked. Meanwhile, the short-tailed croc had a full body of armor, and was unusually strong. All these aspects were factors that Garen had already thought about earlier.

He clenched and unclenched his fists, feeling the Totem Light cover his entire body. It felt like he had put on a thick layer of clothes that was still unexpectedly airy and not restrictive at all.

He looked at the skill pane at the bottom of his field of vision, observing the two different types of icons that had automatically appeared there.

The evolution success rate of the grey-feathered hawk was also about sixty percent, and its abilities were flight and eagle-vision.

The short-tail croc’s evolution success rate was slightly lower at only fifty-something percent, and its abilities were biting and camouflage.

On the newly bought sofa on the first floor, Garen sat there with a grey-feathered hawk on his head and one on each shoulder, while a short-tailed croc crawled near his feet. There were also three blue back lizards on the couch next to him, constantly sticking their red tongues out.

He felt like a lion tamer in the circus.

Wordlessly, Garen let the Silver Totems leave his side, as he contemplated what to do with the new powers in his hands.

Silver Totems and regular totems were different, because they could not be kept inside storage tools. The ones that could be brought around were only limited to the three grey feathered hawks. The short-tailed croc required water and constant care, while the giant lizard’s hunting abilities were only sub-par, making them redundant when taken outside. Only the grey feathered hawk, a type of predatory bird, could be carried around easily, as well as participate in the hunt.

"Now I’ll just have to wait for the White Dragonhawk to become mine. In the meantime, I’ll just go collect some potential points for now."

A grey-feathered hawk was perched on Garen’s shoulders, while the other two stood on each arm. He walked straight out of his house, and past the fence that was now darkened by the night sky. In the dimness of the night, he walked towards the city.

***************

War Guild

Garen held a glass of foamy alcohol but did not drink it. He merely sat in his usual spot and furrowed his brows at the quest scrolls in his hands.

The receptionist, a plump woman took a large bite of the chicken thigh in her hand while placing some quest scrolls on Garen’s table with her other hand.

"You can choose any of the quests here, they’re all form one. Your quest completion rate is not bad, keep up the good work," she said before she turned around to face the other customers.

Garen scanned his eyes across the quest list before him. All of them were form one quests, and their hunting targets were all form one totem users, with the majority being from Phantom Light.

These totem users who believed in the survival of the fittest were merely scum who killed others without batting an eye. They were extremely harsh with themselves, and possessed adept fighting skills. They could not be compared to the Seraph Light totem users of the past.

Garen had asked to look at so many form one quests because he was looking to find the most suitable one. He took a quest list and noticed that it said: Kill Therese Angel. This totem user is psychologically twisted, and fled from the north to Iron Tank City. Although she is only form one, she already possesses four different totems, and is very difficult to provoke.

"This is the one."

Garen decided on his quest, and stood up before walking towards the counter in the hall.

This opponent would be able to test his current strength properly, to finally decide whether Silver Totems or original totems were stronger.

Chapter 285: The Eve of Chaos 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

As he left the guild, Garen walked from the narrow street into an alley. Whore houses were abundant on both sides of this alley, and beautifully made-up women leaned against the doorways of shops, illuminated by red light, as they stroked their hair flirtatiously and exposed their legs to passersby from time to time.

A few guild members walked out from behind him, and stumbled drunkenly into one of the prostitution joints.

Garen picked up his pace and exited this street. From far away, he could see the high, white walls of Iron Tank City standing up straight in the distance.

He stood underneath one of the street lights to avoid blocking the people who were coming out from behind him. He began to recall the contents of his last quest.

"Looks like I’ll need to go back and return with some help. A totem user with four totems cannot be defeated easily."　　

He arranged his shirt collar properly, and began walking in the direction of his newly rented house.

It was located in the same location on the outskirts of the city, and the distance between here and there was not far away.

************

Two hours later.

Outside Iron Tank City, on a lane a few kilometers away from the city area.

Tch!

A bloody corpse was pressed against the ground underneath the claws of a Black Clouded Leopard. The Clouded Leopard was biting and tearing the skin off the corpse’s neck. Blood flowed out of the neck wound and hot white steam began to escape from it.

Moonlight fell on the clouded leopard’s fur, and reflected rays of pale, silvery light.

A voluptuous woman in red stood beside the clouded leopard, as she played with a frayed silver badge in her hands that had been stained red with streaks of blood.

"How many have there been?" she said softly, in somewhat incorrectly accented Kovitan language. "Why are there always so many who like sentencing themselves to death?"

"Sentencing themselves to death? Haha," said a black silhouette as he walked over slowly and stood in the moonlight, finally showing himself. This man was tall but his body seemed skinny and frail.

A White Python was coiled around his body, and it stuck its tongue out frequently.

Instantly, following his appearance, a few more human figures walked over from the side, and surrounded the woman. Alongside them were two Black Wolves, a Leopard and Brown Bear.

Howl!

The Brown Bear let out a low growl and eyed the Black Clouded Leopard by the woman’s side ferociously.

"Therese Angel, we’ve renounced your ranking," announced the person who was controlling the Brown Bear. She was a petite young woman with a strange sounding laugh.

"What a cute little girl. I’m going to rip you up into shreds and cook your flesh into soup for me to enjoy slowly later…" said Angel as she stuck her tongue out and licked her fingers.

"How repulsive," said the young woman as she removed her purple cloak and step backwards. "Go!"

Roar!

Two Black Wolves and the Leopard charged in front at the same time, but were dragged down in mid air by three Black Panthers. They rolled on the floor as they fought viciously.

The White Python and the Brown Bear charged forward at the Black Panther from two different directions respectively.

"Destroy her totem!" yelled the petite girl. Both her hands flew upwards at the same moment as she drew a shapeless gesture in the air. "Go!"

Suddenly a glowing grey dot flew from her fingertips and merged into the body of her Brown Bear.

The Brown Bear roared loudly and stood up on its hind legs. Its movements speeded up suddenly as it dashed towards the last Black Panther on the field.

"Grey light?" The black clothed woman looked slightly astonished, but did not show any signs of panic. Her slender fingers drew a line in the air at lightspeed, as a green flame ignited on her fingertips, and danced in the air like fire.

At the same moment, the claws of the four Black Panthers that she controlled also began to glow green as well.

Tch!

The Black Clouded Leopard used its claw and scratched a line across the White Python’s body, and the wound immediately began glowing green.

"Speed up the elimination. She has poisonous toxins!! The reports were false! Fall back!!" yelled the petite woman with a panicked expression on her face.

"Trying to escape?" The woman in black glanced at her lightly. "The War Guild here is apparently really weak."

Ten minutes later…

The ground was covered in severed limbs and bloodied flesh, as blood began to seep into the grass and ground and dyed them red.

The woman in black, Angel squatted in front of the girl’s dead body and stuck her hand into her collar and pulled out a pendant.

"One of the Duke’s people, huh? The nearby area must be the White Dragonhawk’s territory then, right…" she said as she knitted her eyebrows together.

She stood up suddenly and looked towards the forest that was not far away.

"More people from the War Guild again. You guys really have no fear of death, huh. I never expected that the central War Guild would be so weak. They don’t even make up half of the northern territory. Even if you guys aren’t bored yet, I sure am."

A man with a shining bald head walked out of the forest slowly. He removed his black cloak, and the contrast between the colour of his shawl and his milky white skin became very obvious.

"Is the central War Guild really that stupid? One dies, and two more arrive. Two more die, and the third one comes along," Angel mocked.

"I’m not the same as them,"

"The three people before you said that too," said Angel impatiently as she took a few steps forward. She continued to hold the pendant from earlier in her hand lightly. "Every one of the people I killed had the same kind of self-confidence. Unfortunately, they were all idiots. Do you know? In my eyes, you and the stupid pigs in your garden are one and the same. You’ve never seen the outside world, and you think you’re the greatest thing in your small town."

The bald man smiled, and reached his hand out.

A Black-nailed Crocodile crawled out slowly from behind him, while three Grey-feathered Hawks descended from the sky and began flying circles around him.

"The number of my totems are the same as yours, a perfect pair for each of them."

"Idiot," said Angel as she rolled her eyes. "Out of the totem users that I killed, five of them were so-called geniuses who had more than four totems each. If the number of totem keys were equivalent to the quality of totems, then everyone would just stockpile them and that would be it. Whatever, I don’t have time for your nonsense," she said as she took out a gold pocket watch and looked at the time. "We’re almost out of time."

"Almost out of time for what?" asked Garen as he looked at Angel curiously.

The thing that he was actually relying on was not the totems, but the Form one totem. Any stronger and it would not be a threat to the current him at all. As he currently possessed Form two defense strength, he was now standing in undefeatable territory for now. He had brought the totems along with him for a different purpose, to see if there was really a difference between primitive totems and Silver Totems if they both belonged to the Form one category.

"It’s the totem cooling-off period, you idiot!" Angel grinned. "Moments ago my quick-acting poison was still in its cooling-off stage, but since you didn’t make a move, I’m afraid it’s too late now."

Her fingertips were lighted with a green flame again, as she suddenly pointed towards Garen.

"Kill him!"

In a blink of an eye, the four Black Panthers beside her leaped upwards suddenly and became like four black lines that dashed towards Garen’s myriad of totems. Their speed was much faster than earlier, and they rushed towards him like arrows, bringing a hissing sound with them as they tore through the air.

"Bringing along a totem of no quality is like carrying a burden, idiot," Angel said as a mocking expression appeared on her face.

Suddenly, the Crocodile and the Clouded Leopard squared up against each other, while the three Grey-feathered Hawks went up against the three Black Panthers. One of the Grey Feathered-Hawks got scratched, and a big pile of feathers had now fallen unto the floor.

Garen scrunched his eyebrows together and attempted to speak. Suddenly, Angel’s expression changed and the green flame on her fingers lit up again, before the four Panthers leapt back to her side.

"Count yourself lucky today! If only…" She had yet to finish her sentence but cut herself off abruptly, before climbing onto the fastest Clouded Leopard and turning in the other direction.

Hum…

In the sky above his head, a strange noise began calling out in the air. It sounded like a cow’s moo, but at the same time felt as if something was quaking.

Garen lifted his head and looked at the giant white bird circling above his head.

"White Dragonhawk?" he said as he furrowed his eyebrows.

***************

Inside the forest, shards of moonlight scattered into pieces and fell unto the grass and the tree trunks.

Angel rode the Clouded Leopard and raced frantically through the forest. She was going at an incredible speed, and the trees on both sides of her had now become blobs of blurry black shadows. Nothing could be seen clearly, except for the scene before her that continued to grow bigger the nearer she came.

"I’ve gotten rid of him," said Angel when she finally felt as if the feeling of someone staring into the back of her head had disappeared. She sighed in relief.

Suddenly her eyes widened in shock. She stared at the trees surrounding her, and stopped her Clouded Leopard instantly.

Hiss!

The remaining three Black Leopards stopped as well, and deep skid marks appeared on the ground. They kept watch at her side, looking on vigilantly at the forest before them.

"What did you want to say just now?" Garen’s voice rang from in front, tinged with a sense of doubt.

"Although I don’t know how you managed to catch up to me, but it seems like you’re really looking to die… Apparently you didn’t even bring a single totem with you," said Angel in a low voice as she glared at the bald man in front of her.

"Go!!" Once again, the green flame lit up her fingertip.

The three Black Panthers sped up and formed three black lines that rushed towards Garen. Six pairs of sharp claws were pointed towards Garen’s throat.

After the three Black Panthers had undergone skill improvement, their venomous claws became a part of their totem Light defense. They were also able to use corrosive Totem Light, which would then increase the speed of their defenses.

Angel rode the Clouded Leopard to the field, and looked at Garen with a pitiful expression.

"I had originally planned to spare you, but you chose to die on your own…"

Bang!!

A dull crashing noise suddenly rang through the air.

Angel widened both of her eyes, and an unknown sense of fear began to grow in her mind. She stared dreamily at the figure before her with a shocked and dazed expression on her face.

Garen moved his right leg backwards as he looked at the two leaping Black Panthers. His right hand grabbed one of the Black Panthers by its throat, as if he was holding a little chick in mid air.

Ka… ka…

The Black Panther tried to escape by scratching at Garen’s arms wildly, but it was utterly useless.

"Its speed isn’t bad, and it almost caught up to me," said Garen, full of praise.

But before he finished speaking, he noticed that there was now no one in front of him.

************

Angel desperately commanded the Clouded Leopard she was riding to run faster. She kept turning back to look behind her, afraid that man had finally caught up once again.

Her forehead was dripping with sweat.

"Where did this monster come from?! A totem user who went up against a totem in direct combat! I’ve definitely just seen a ghost!"

In most cases, although a totem user possessed a Totem Light to protect themselves from getting injured by totems, their own speeds and strengths were greatly different from the totem’s own, and they were of a whole different level.

Of course, those who practiced martial arts may have been able to keep up, but since totem users were already racing against time to study and evolve their totems, who else had the time to study these low-levelled martial arts like wrestling?

Activities like wrestling were equivalent to sailing against the current, it was something that would not benefit you, but was more likely to push you backwards. In that sense, a totem user’s control of a totem and understanding of fighting skills also held the same principle of sailing against the tide, and was something that would result in regression if the totem user lacked concentration.

Only those who did not have Luminarist qualifications would practice wrestling. The rest were individuals who were not qualified, or those who came from poor families.

Angel frantically ordered the Clouded Leopard she was riding to run to the point where it reached its limits. Her mind continued to flash images of the scene she had just witnessed before. She was too afraid to believe what she had seen, and continued to speed up her Black Panther, worried that it would be sent flying or captured by the totem user from earlier.

"Skills of that degree would only belong to someone who was at least General-level! But how could a General-level totem user be that young? This world is starting to become insane…

Chapter 286: The Eve of Chaos 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

After guessing her the level of her opponent’s strength, Angel’s mind began to calm down slightly.

"General-level is still alright. As long as I use the right moves, I should be able to counter it. But how did he manage to do it exactly? Seeing that he wasn’t afraid of the toxins on the Black Panther’s claws at all?"

Thinking of this, her fingertips suddenly lit up with a green flame, as she quickly drew a gesture in the space in front of her.

"Shared Vision."

A smile appeared on her face, as she saw that there was still one Black Panther that had not been destroyed yet. Her vision immediately transferred to look through the creature’s eyes.

Suddenly, her face contorted into an extremely ugly expression.

Hiss!

The Clouded Leopard beneath her crotch stopped abruptly, its four claws scratching black marks into the grass below.

In front of the woman and the Panther stood a bald man who had both his hands stuffed inside his pockets, looking at her and smiling.

"Hey," he said as he rushed towards Angel and waved his hands at her.

"You forced me to do this!!" said Angel as she finally exploded with anger. She glared at her opponent’s legs as he stepped on her Black Panther. All ten of her fingers on both hands began dotting the air rapidly with spots of green light.

Immediately, thirty dots were placed together in close proximity, and began floating in mid air.

She clasped her hands together and combined all the dots, forming them into one gigantic ball of light.

"Triple Speed!! Go!" she said as her fingers pointed towards the only unharmed Clouded Leopard left.

The green dots of light rapidly shot inside the Clouded Leopard’s body.

Roar!

The black coloured Clouded Leopard howled loudly as every trace of it disappeared in a blink of an eye.

Bang!

Garen stretched his right hand outwards, barely blocking the Clouded Leopard’s black claws that were pointed straight at him. Between the claws and his palm, a blue-black light has begun to pierce through, and caused shards of black light to fall towards the ground.

Crash!

A black shadow surrounded Garen and attacked him from all sides, its speed exceeding the limits of a normal living creature. With every attack, the green claws began to rip out shards of black rays from the blue-black light.

Garen began to have trouble keeping up when the Totem Light on his body began to violently break into smaller pieces. But moments later, it seemed like he had gotten use to the black Clouded Leopard’s attack rhythm, elbow and fist movements, as well as the sweep of its legs, as the Clouded Leopard continuously rushed at him.

He decided to close his eyes and feel the Clouded Leopard’s rapid attacks carefully, as it hit against his Totem Light agitatedly. While in a trance, he felt something suddenly, and realised that if he took the initiative and accepted the attacks, the consumption of Totem Light would be significantly less than if he moved or attacked.

If he merely stood in his spot, it would take two minutes before the Totem Light on his body was completely broken through. However, if he came forward on his own to accept the attack, it would take at least two hours for his Totem Light to be depleted.

Furthermore, he could vaguely feel that under this high pressured attack, his Totem Light was beginning to elicit a tightening sensation around his body

"This feeling…" he said as he shut his eyes and concentrated on this rare sensation.

Suddenly, everything on the outside stopped, and the Clouded Leopard’s attacks faded away in a blink of an eye.

"Huh?"

Garen opened his eyes and looked at his surroundings, before noticing that the woman had escaped again.

*******************

Angel rode the weakened Clouded Leopard as it staggered through the forest.

"Die! Die! Die!" she cursed angrily. "The Triple Speed move… I’ve definitely just seen a ghost!! Even a mere totem user could withstand three minutes of the Triple Speed. That monster!!"

Three of her totems had been destroyed by that baldy, and now only one remained.

The other totems had cut off all communication from her. This also resulted in her Totem Light defense decreasing from Form two totem user’s level, to a Form one totem user’s level.

Once a totem was destroyed, it’s Totem Light would also fall apart instantly. She was only left with a layer of black totem light on her body.

For a totem to be killed by a totem user, this was definitely a strange phenomenon.

A totem user on their own was only capable of defense. Therefore, even if a human had undergone extra training, they could still never catch up to a totem that had already been equipped with extra moves, right? Besides that, a totem user’s attacks were considered as physical attacks, and were not supposed to be able to inflict serious harm on totems, much less destroy them.

Angel’s heart beat wildly inside her chest, she had been escaping the north for so many years and had encountered numerous powerful, prodigy Totem users during her killing sprees. However, she had never come across someone like this, who could match the speed and strength of an Improved Totem, and could even use his flesh body to kill a Silver Totem.

The time ticked away, and soon two hours had passed…

As she raced through, suddenly a yellow bonfire could be seen in front, where a caravan of people were sitting around two bonfires, cooking something to eat.

Beside the caravan, a young man and woman who looked like aristocrats were talking quietly to each other. Both of them had the totem user’s special short storage stick hung around their waists.

Angel’s face began to light up. There were so many people here, including Luminarists. According to the rules, the guy from earlier who worked for the War Guild was not allowed to start a fight where in a place with so many people.

Suddenly, she felt that something was wrong, and decided to climb back up unto the Clouded Leopard and turn tails.

Scratch…

The grass on the ground was torn up badly.

"Damn! You again!!" Angel’s face was extremely haggard, as she looked at the young man strolling out from the forest. In her eyes, the gentle smile on his face seemed as frightening as the devil himself.

"What are you trying to do?!!" said Angel in an exasperated voice. She was mentally and physically tired. No matter where she escaped, this person would always find her again in a matter of time.

"You have lots of experience, I would like to learn from you," said Garen, smiling.

"Like to learn, my ass!!" said Angel, sounding as if she was about to cry.

Bang!!

Garen’s fist landed against Angel’s small abdomen, as he forcefully propped her against the tree trunk behind him. Next, he swung his left arm, causing the Clouded Leopard that charged towards him to be sent flying.

He straightened his palm, allowing Angel to clearly see the side of his hand.

"My hand has been laced with my totem’s specialised poison and toxic powder. Therefore, I may not be able to hurt totems, but I can still catch up to them, and place the poison on their bodies. That’s how I got rid of three of your Black Panthers. Obviously, I’m going to do the same thing to you."

Angel was held tightly down. Her pale face glared at Garen.

Cough cough…

As she was let down from the tree trunk, her face began to turn blue, as if the symptoms of the poison were already starting to show. She hurriedly took a little black bottle out and opened it, before pouring some medicine into her mouth.

Seconds later, her bluish complexion began to become slightly better.

Garen returned to his original spot.

"To punish you for your potty mouth," he said with a wave of his hand.

A grey shadow descended with a hissing noise before violently scratching the body of the last Clouded Leopard.

Immediately, Angel felt the last layer of Totem Light on her body fall apart. She looked at the deep gash in the Clouded Leopard’s forehead as it turned into a pool of silver mercury, and an unknown sense of despair washed over her.

Bang!

Garen kicked up a stone, and it hit Angel’s right arm precisely.

A soft cracking sound could be heard. It was the sound of bones breaking. Angel let out a low moan as she held her right arm and crouched down.

Garen did not move again. He truly wanted to learn something from this woman.

From the acceleration tactic in the beginning, to the poison curing tactic, and finally to Triple Speed and Shared Vision.

This woman had grasped at least four different types of impressive tactics. Furthermore, out of all the totem users he had met, she was probably the strongest, aside from Goth.

"Don’t worry, I’m completely useless at tactics. I think that the tactics you use are extremely practical, and much better than the ones used by other totem users. That’s why I’m hoping that you’ll teach me," said Garen earnestly.

"You should have said so earlier…" said Angel as she leaned against the tree trunk and sat down, her emotions running wild. This was the first time she had encountered a totem user who could suppress her speed. She was currently facing what the totems users who fought against her in the past went through.

"Only when a person is in a state of serious danger, will they unleash their true potential. This is what I’ve believed all this while," said Garen as he walked over slowly. He moved his right arm and deflected the Black Panther that had snuck up behind him.

This Black Panther had been hiding all along, and was the fifth Black Panther in the pack. It rolled on the ground after being hit, and crashed into a tree trunk violently. The strange thing was that after it got hit, the supposedly unharmed Black Panther began to howl in pain, and after tumbling a few times on the ground, began to stand up with much difficulty, looking as it if was unnaturally weak.

Angel backtracked, and with moved a step backwards each time her opponent came closer. She noticed that on the surface of Garen’s Totem Light, there was a light layer of glowing blue dust, and within that layer hid pools of sticky green liquid. Apparently it was the poison and toxic dust that her opponent had spoken about earlier.

"I’ll give you all the tactics you want!! I stole all of them!" Frantically, she took out all the little scrolls that she had kept on herself and threw them at Garen.

"And how would I know that all these are authentic?" said Garen as he shook his head. "You still have substitute totems on you, right? Just take them all out."

"You want this too?" Angel swallowed her saliva and stared at Garen. Without saying anything else, she removed the little purse from her waist quickly, and threw it on the ground. "These are all of my assets that I have on hand. I have savings of up to twenty million stored in one of the Kovitan Empire’s banks. As long as you swear to let me go, I will give you the password for all this money."

"Twenty million…" Garen’s heart began to falter. This sum of money would be enough for him to do a lot of things. However, he was now worried that he had run of out time…

He stared at Angel who stood before him, and his heart wavered on whether or not to kill her.

"I still have three sets of totem orders at the Rafelia Workshop. The money has been paid in full, and as long as you promise to let me go, I’ll tell you the password to collect my orders! Or I could take you there to get them too!" Angel continued to sweeten the deal. She could tell that her opponent was hesitating.

"You have so many totems, and their Appraisal is definitely of the highest rank, but why have you not evolved even one of them into Form two?" Garen opened his mouth and asked suddenly.

Angel did not expect him to ask this question, and a confused look appeared on her face immediately. "I…"

"Have you heard of the Code of Elya?" Garen continued to ask.

"Code of Elya?" Angel looked dumbfounded. She stared at the man in front of her, her mind racing uncontrollably. "I’ve killed too many people already…"

Chapter 287: Chaos 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

"It’s alright; the favor can be returned soon." Garen grinned, seemingly able to understand Angel’s heart. "Being someone who controls four totems, with no lack of money, how can you not even have evolv one to second form? No, you actually can control five?"

As he abruptly lifted his arms, a blue ray of light emitted from behind his back, consolidating on his finger tips to become a blue butterfly the size of a basin. The butterfly steadily flapped its wings, glowing in blue fluorescence.

"You!!!!" Angel was finally moved completely. She looked cautiously at Garen, dumbfounded by the scene in front of her eyes. Including the previously summoned short-tailed croc and the three hawks, together with the neon butterfly, the person in front of her was also someone who could control five totems!

"This world is always unfair." Garen spoke faintly, "Geniuses like us have talent and wealth. But lacking inherited knowledge, there is no way for us to progress. While those mediocre, useless aristocrats can have it easy. With whole sets of evolution theories, there is no need for them to go around working and laboring for others."

Angel stayed silent, but there was solemness in her expression. What Garen said was spot on. Being born in a humble family, excluded in the association, without money and resources, she had to depend on herself for her own development. It was through hard work and labor that brought her to where she is today.

Seeing Garen, who could also control five totems standing in front of her, she instantly developed a strong sense of resonance.

"We are alike. Why should those low-aptitude trash get to enjoy everything without any effort? We are far better than them, yet have to laboriously struggle for what we have. Do you know how much effort i had to put in to be at the level I am today?" Garen roared defiantly. He was so into the act that it nearly warmed his heart.

Being an impulsive person, Angel clenched her fists tightly. As she heard Garen’s words, she remembered the humiliation and discrimination that she went through all these years.

"What is your plan?" She ask with a glimpse of hoarseness in her voice.

"Join me. Your appraisal is the best I’ve seen. Once you have a complete set of evolution theory, you would be able to step into the realm of a second form totem master. We have the same objective." Garen said sincerely.

"Do you think I’ll believe you?" Angel frigidly asked. "Sooner or later, I myself would be able to obtain the knowledge of cultivating a second form totem."

"Is that possible? Without basics, without a complete set of theories, and requiring special materials on top of that, do you really believe you can figure out second form evolution yourself? Perhaps it is possible. But how long would it take you? Two years? Five years? Ten? You are a murderer hunted by the Royal Alliance of Luminarists, not an innocent genius."

Garen was undoubtedly intending to gather some underlings for the next step of his scheme. In the upcoming chaos, individual ability will seem more and more insignificant, unless someone was with remarkable ability. However, he evidently knew that he was currently not at that level.

To elevate himself in the shortest time, the best way was to find a battle-tested veteran to understand the ins and outs of a totem user battle. At the same time, a group of helpers would surely increase the efficiency of hunting.

Moreover, regarding the war guild, Garen roughly knew a thing or two. In a war guild, with the existence of war chain and war hall, it could create a secure leader follower relationship.

Not to mention, dealing with the entire Obscuro Society on his own would be an impossible task.

Looking at Angel, he knew that although she looked innocent and impulsive, she was a ruthless girl. However, she possessed a strong understanding of tactics, and had immense potential as a totem user.

"What now? Have you made up your mind?" Garen calmed took a glance at the burning campfire behind him. "Do you plan to continue being hunted for the rest of your life? This time it was merely first form totem users, but it might not be that simple the next time. Rather than being hopelessly hunted, you might as well join my crusade. Let’s hunt other totem users together. You can repay your sins, while I have my own desires."

Angel crouched down. "My enemies are not just first form totem users. Are you sure you want get yourself into trouble?" She spoke harshly.

"It’s alright, I’m never afraid of problems." Garen snickered, "Essentially, my problems far surpass yours"

Angel bowed her head quietly. Garen wasn’t anxious, instead he patiently waited for her reply.

"According to the Elya Code, any convict can join the War Guild for a shot at redeeming himself. For every man killed, the same number of criminals have to be killed, as redemption. For the totem users that were hunting you, most likely it would have been because of this rule. Of course the premise would be someone has to refer you." Garen grinned, "This is nothing big to me. With my high mission completion rate, entering the war guild is a piece of cake. Once I’m in, I could refer you. That’s what many convicts do, relying on their comrades’ referrals to redeem their sins.

Angel closed her eyes. Her core totem had been obliterated, the three supporting totems had been destroyed, even the last summoned Black Panther was paralyzed by poison. It was evident that she was at an absolute disadvantage. Giving such an offer in this situation definitely showed sincerity.

Truly, as someone constantly being hunted, cooperating with him would be far more prospective.

"How could you be sure that I wouldn’t abandoned you after I’m free from danger?" She didn’t believe anyone would trust an enemy without a reason.

Garen walked towards a towering tree and leaned on the trunk.

"We are the same kind of people. Joining another group might put you back in the same spot as you were. Equality will only happen with like-minded people. I plan to gather people like us, combining our strengths. The strongest among us will become the leader. But it’s still too early to say these things. This ideology sounds similar to Phantom Light. Saying less would be better."

Angel fixed her eyes on Garen, gently nodded her head after some time.

"I promise you. With the war guild’s war chain and war hall, we will benefit together, share information with each other and reach a certain level of cooperation."

"Excellent. You are my first comrade." Garen extended his arm to pull her onto her feet. "Once I return I will apply to the war guild. To buy a war chain costs at least five million Rumbs, and that would be of the lowest grade. If we hunt together, should be able to earn it in a short time."

Angel nodded. She understood that cooperating with the man in front of her was the best path she could take.

The War Chain was a fixed, permanent solidifying tactic.

It was like a long chain, connecting the core totems of everyone participating together. Anyone who wanted to leave the chain would have to pay the price of losing their core totem. To a totem user, it was indeed a severe punishment. The higher the level of the totem user, the more painful it was to him. Totem users commonly devoted a lifetime of effort into their core totems.

Besides maintaining the stability of the alliance, the war chain brought other benefits.

A war chain was like a special totem, where it could be cultivated, and strengthened by embedding external components.

Angel pondered for a moment, and then whispered. "If a war chain without any additional abilities already costs five million, wouldn’t one with some abilities cost billions?"

Garen nodded. "After all, the abilities of the war chain perpetually affects every member. I haven’t seen other totems, but in Iron Tank City guild there is a chain with abilities called the Chain of Healing, which benefits the members. Any injuries sustained by all totem users in the chain would activate the minor healing abilities in the chain. The power of the tactic would then heal the injured totem user." He explained.

"Of course, we can only start from scratch. Once we obtain sufficient solidifying tactics, then the effectiveness of the war chain would be heightened."

"Easier said than done." Angel shook her head without saying much.

"The war hall instead is a platform of sharing evolution knowledge. We can transfer all the knowledge we loot, and this special totem allows equal exchange of knowledge. Of course, the knowledge learned by yourself can be included as well. Whether it is the exchange of knowledge, exchange of resources or using it increasing the effectiveness of the chain, all of these can be done through the war hall. However, it might take a long time for us to reach this stage." Garen lightheartedly explained. He could see that Angel wasn’t very familiar with the war guild structure.

Sure enough, Angel’s eyes brightened up with every word she heard. "Why are the guilds here much weaker than the ones in the North? Each one of them was swift and could easily track me. It doesn’t matter how far I left them behind, they would be able to catch up"

"There is a possibility that their war chain has a tracing ability. Compared to the Iron Tank City Guild, they are more aggressive and their chains have more varied effects. It is very normal." Garen nodded. "That’s it, it’s time to go. Next, I would go back to take up missions. Then I would inform, include you on the mission list, and apply to suspend the missions that hunt for you. As we collaborate to complete missions, our efficiency should be pretty decent.

Angel nodded.

As he returned to complete the formalities, Garen easily obtained the lowest level member certification, called Greyhawk. He was named after the grey hawk totem on his shoulder.

Through Garen, Angel paid a million Rumb’s bail, as proof that her kill-orders were suspended.

This amount of money could only buy her two days time, and Angel would be not be allowed to leave the boundaries of Iron Tank City. It would automatically lapse if she broke the rules. They had to complete at least one hunting mission in two days.

As for the two special totems in the war guild and war hall, the cost of tens of millions was not something they could afford at this stage.

****************

The sky was overcast.

Dense, grey clouds clumped together, tarring the sky. Droplets of rain began to fall and they looked like transparent thin lines in the wind.

On the vast green plains, a squadron of caravans was travelling leisurely on the carriageway, heading towards White Stream City.

Majority of the caravans were grey and yellow, while on some of the goods had white, coarse cloth as shading.

In the middle of the squadron, a double-black-horsed carriage slowed down. The side window of the splendorous carriage swung open, exposing the faces of two young, fair aristocratic girls.

One of them inquisitively fixated on the goods on the middle carriage.

"Is this the Palas Caravan? Lala." The young girl asked her companion.

"It should be, I think I’ve seen the emblem." The girl named Lala seemed disinterested. She held her chin with one of her hands, staring at fleeting horse hooves, appearing to be in a state of trance.

"Lala, Lala?" Her companion, Vecil’s voice seemed to be from afar.

"So boring…" Lala sighed in her heart, halfhearted replying her companion. Vecil was always bubbly and full of energy, never running out of things to say.

Lala vacantly stared at rain droplets falling on the caravan.

She was soon going to White Stream City to continue her legal education. Although she had no interest in the law, she had no reasons to decline.

This is the society she was in, being born, then study, work, get married, growing old and eventually death. Day in day out, year in year out.

The industrial revolution has begun, and everything was booming. New ideas and gadgets were popping out in the market everyday. The world was like a seedling, continuously growing and developing without a set direction.

Lala signed in her heart again. She was turning 18 this year, the year she comes of age. But looking at her same-aged playmates, they seemed extremely immature. She likened them to parameciums, lowly and ignorant.

"Ignorance is bliss…" Lala breathed a sigh of relief. Very quickly, Vecil’s voice was ringing in her ears again.

"I heard Uncle Cornell’s son is being enlisted in the military. I wonder how is it like?" The thought lingered in Vecil’s mind. "Some time ago, Cornell Jr invited you for a horse ride. Why didn’t you go? It was so obvious he wanted to confess to you before he left. "

"Aunt wouldn’t allow." Lala calmly stared out of the window. "Moreover, I do not want to think about these at this young age."

Chapter 288: Chaos 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

"My God, Lala you’re already 18! You could have a kid at the age of 18 in many places! Still too young?" Vecil made a fuss. "Maybe instead of Aunt Vera not allowing, she already has someone for you."

"That is not something i can accept." Lala frowned. "That is why i chose to go to White Stream City to study law. Perhaps becoming an imperial lawyer is not a bad option." At least i can make my own decisions this way. She commented in her heart.

"I really envy you. It’s a pity I do not have talents like yours…" Vecil groaned. Suddenly, there was a loud commotion coming from the forepart of the squadron.

"What happened?" "Don’t know?"

"It looks like some people are blocking the road ahead."

A group of men instantly came down from the caravan to investigate. The women and children beside the caravan looked ahead, murmuring among each other to guess what happened.

Finally, a sense of interest stirred up in Lala’s heart. "Wesley, what happened up front?" She roared at her coachman.

"Thousand apologies my lady, there are some people blocking the road, looks like we have to wait for a while." The voice of the elderly coachman sounded.

As the carriage continued to moved forward, in a brief moment, Lala could see the episode upfront.

Right in front of the squadron, on the greyish-white carriageway, there was a young man and a young girl sitting on the rocks and the roadside. They stood up and directly blocked off the squadron.

Both of them were dressed in long, grey robes, covering their whole body. The man was bald without an ounce of hair. His eyebrowless face left a bone-chilling impression on others.

The girl tied her gorgeous blonde hair into a ponytail, and had a good figure. There was a glimpse of coldness in her pretty face. She followed closely behind the guy, locking her eyes on the caravan squadron. In her eyes, the over hundred people in the squadron were like livestocks that were waiting to be slaughtered.

Seemingly noticing someone was peering at her, the girl switched her glare and caught Lala’s line of sight.

In that instance, a cold shiver ran down Lala’s spine. She fervently retracted her head, hiding herself in the carriage. She could feel droplets of cold sweat as she swept her fingers over her forehead.

In the split second their eyes met, she could feel an intense murder intent deep down in her counterpart’s soul.

"What’s wrong?" Garen gave Angel who was behind him a short glance.

"Nothing much." Angel shook her head. "What do you plan to do? With so many people present, war prison cannot be used. It is certain that the three totem users are hiding among these commoners, using war jail as a cover to escape Iron Tank City."

Garen laughed.

The crisp sound of hooves in the vicinity caught Garen’s attention as he looked towards the grass plains. A white-robed girl riding a beautiful white stallion was strolling on the plains, as if she so happened to bump into them. From the horseback, the girl ignorantly looked towards them, expressing curiosity on the happenings.

He returned his gaze towards the caravan.

"Since last night, how many have we killed?" He murmured to Angel.

"Maybe three…"Angel said with hesitation. "I can’t really remember."

"Forget it, lets go." Garen rushed forward, throwing out a black coin.

"Hey!" Angel was stunned. "Are you insane, there are so many people here!"

Cheehh!!!

As the coin landed on the ground, it emitted a transparent ripple which expanded instantaneously. It swallowed the whole caravan and everything within a hundred metre radius into the cocoon, forming a enormous dome-shaped cage.

"Soon we do not have to consider this anymore." Garen smirked, seeing three grey-robed figures rushing out from the flank of the caravan squadron. He pointed to the front with his right hand.

Whizzzz!!!

A few grey blurs shot out of his back continuously, heading directly to the three figures.

Angel dashed forward, pointing vigorously. Thiry luminous green dots instantly formed out of thin air.

"Three times speed!"

The thirty dots converged into one, abruptly turning into a ray of green light, blasting at the black panther leaping out from behind her.

Whizzzz!

The black panther became a black line in the blink of an eye, rushing towards the three figures.

The black blur overtook the grey blurs, throwing one of the figures onto the ground.

"No!!"

The tree grey blurs formed three grey hawks, swooping down to capture the black python of the fallen figure. Strangely, after the python struggled for a brief moment, it speedily came to a halt, then stiffly hanging on the sharp claws of the hawks. The three grey hawks pierced at the python with their beaks, forming three bowl sized-wounds. Eventually, the python became a pile of silver liquid, seeping into the ground.

As the python was obliterated, the black panther went right for the throat of the man on the ground. Within a split second, there was blood spluttered all over the ground.

The other two opponents turned pale when they saw the scene. They fell onto the ground and tried to scramble back.

"No...No!!! You cannot do this! The war guild has rules and there are so many commoners here! So many humans!" The girl on the left sobbed.

The guy on the right shivered as he tried to draw up an unknown tactic, but because of overwhelming fear, he failed after a few tries. Beads of cold sweat formed all over his face, eventually dripping from his chin.

"Weakling." Garren shook his head. He walk forward and grabbed the man by his collar. "A brat who just entered first form. Would catching him alive reap better rewards?"

"Why not think how to settle the matter at hand?" Angel pouted as she headed towards the carriage.

Garen looked at the caravan squadron.

Every merchant from the caravan were silent and the mouths of the kids were clutched to stop them from uttering any noise. The men held various kinds of weapons in their hands, while the women and children shut the curtains tightly as they retreated into their carriages. Around ten mercenaries nervously looked at each other as they drew their swords.

To them, looking at Garen and Angel was like looking at monsters.

Garen ignored them and lifted his head.

Whoooshhh….

Suddenly, a massive flock of blue birds flew towards them from the south.

The blue birds were like a bunch of pimples and their reflection appeared as large black spots onto the ground. The sound of their chirps continued to ring in the vicinity.

"It’s here… Finally…" Garen mildly breathed a breath of relief.

His heart skipped a beat.

A grey hawk darted up to catch one of the blue birds with its beak. Then it swooped down and landed on Garen’s shoulder.

Garen took the blue bird from the grey hawk’s beak, retrieved the note strapped to its leg and gently opened it.

"Emergency from the south! Agac City requesting for assistance!"

There was a stain of blood on the sides of the note.

"We have to go." Garen whispered. He lifted his hands, and all three grey hawks took flight, circling on the top of his head.

Unknowingly, one of the hawks picked up the black coin and held it in his beak.

"What should we do with these two?" Angel gave the two paralyzed totem users a glance. Their totems, a black wolf and a white hawk, was swiftly annihilated by the black panther in the fight.

Garen didn’t utter much, instead gave them a light kick on their thighs.

As a tremendous force instantly entered their chest,their heads snapped and blood started flowing out from their mouths, dying a quiet death.

"Let’s go."

"Garen looked at the attribute pane on the far bottom his vision, the potential bar has finally recovered to 15 points. He was initially left with only13 potential points after using them up on the howling wererabbit. But now with Angel as his aid, he no longer has to do much. Angel was the one dealing with enemy totem users, while he only had to deal the final blow.

Without lifting a finger, three totem users were killed in one night. Including this three, it would bring the total to six.

The potential points used on the wererabbit have been instantly recovered.

This time he returned, it would be the opportune time to try evolving the giant lizards. Garen was eager to see their evolved form.

"What are these blue messenger birds up to?" Angel had a gut feeling that something was wrong.

"Those are all distress messages. Most probably the southern kingdoms have fallen completely." Garen continued to withdraw the war prison without looking back.

"That's impossible! There are thousands of second form totem users under Ender Kingdom’s General Veron. All of them are elites!" Angel was struck with disbelief.

Meanwhile, Garen had already strutted to the front of the caravan squadron.

"We… We can afford to pay ransom!!" Their leader, a plump man pleaded with a shaky voice. "Do not kill us! Please…" He knelt on the ground.

"Both of you are hunters. The war guild does not allow the usage of the war prison amongst humans." A white-haired elder stood out among the crowd and spoke softly. He evidently knew a thing or two about the war guild.

"Laws are set by men. But they are no longer of use." Garen shrugged. "Heed my advice. Return to Iron Tank City instead of heading to White Stream City. Otherwise, there will be far worse things in store for you."

He was warning them out of kindness. The Silver Totem army of the Obscuro Soceity would be arriving any minute. As swarms of Silver Totem flood in, running into them in the open would a nightmare. If that happened, it would mean certain death for these commoners as even Garen himself wouldn’t dream of staying alive. Only a sturdy city would have the capacity to defend.

Among these Silver Totems were all kinds of strange creatures, like a rare creature exhibition. It was indeed a horrifying sight. These creatures, with high contamination abilities were the result of the Obscuro Society’s unsuccessful breeding. On top of that, they were empowered by the Phantom Light, which amplified their ability by many fold.

"Let’s go." As he spoke, Angel had chopped off the heads of the three convicts, wrapping them with some cloth.

Two of them, one after the other, hurried towards Iron Tank City.

The people in the squadron could finally breathe a sigh of relief. Most of them were baffled, and ignored Garen’s advice. A minority of them who could see that Garen was speaking the truth, were willing to follow his words and leave.

"Go! Wesley, let’s turn back!" Lala, sitting in her carriage, was flushed with in inexplicable excitement and passion. There was finally some spark in her boring life. She believed her judgment, as she always did.

The bald man didn’t have a trace of lying. She believed his words.

"My lady…"The elderly carriageman hesitated.

"Turn around!" Lala raised her voice.

"Okay." Wesley helplessly agreed, slowly leaving the carriageway, making a turn on the grass plains.

"Lala are you mad? Do you really believe a word the weirdo said?" Vecil finally dared to speak again. She covered her head, hid at the bottom of the carriage, afraid that she would be noticed by others. As she lifted her head, her voice was as soft as mosquitoes.

"I believe him, and the big sea of blue messenger birds." Lala nodded solemnly.

Suddenly, the sound of crisp horse hooves could be heard outside the carriage.

Lala pulled open the curtain and looked out. She saw the white-robed young girl on the white horse following the baldy and the ponytailed girl in hot pursuit.

Lala could see from the young girl’s face that they had the same adventurous expression.

"Hurry up! Let’s follow the two people upfront!" Lala yelled.

Chapter 289: The Outbreak of War 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

The sky was awash with shades of grey. Large clouds moved rapidly to form clusters, then dissipating into thin air.

The earth trembled. On the green, grassy plains, numerous black cysts surfaced, as if they were tumors of the earth. They were like the beating of a heart, like actual organs.

Whoooshhh...

A few white-golden giant hawks soared across the sky, carrying silver armor-laden riders on their backs. The riders who wielded huge, long spears, were stained with dried blood all over their body.

A grey apex hawk spread its wings, flying below one of giant hawks.

There was a faint silver glow in the grey hawk’s vision, as it clearly surveyed everything that was happening below.

On the plains below, each one of the black cysts started to squirm. They had four mouths full of sharp teeth located at their sides. As their mouths continuously opened and shut, they spat out full-black, single-horned creatures.

The creatures were built like giant crouching lizards, each with a single black fang-like horn on their foreheads, accompanied with a pair of humongous black wings.

They spread their wings, emitting peculiar noises. Shaking off the mucous on their bodies, they leapt into the air, heading right at the white-golden hawks.

The grey hawk silently flew away, diving towards the ground below.

As it flew over a dark green forest, observing from above, it could see a huge number of wild beasts battling with the giant, lizard-like abominations. The roars of the wolves and bears could be heard as they were torn apart by the giant lizards.

Crossing the forest, the grey hawk let out a light cry, gently flew towards the grey carriageway located at the other side of the forest.

On the carriageway, a bunch of grey-robed riders were dashing forward on their horses. A bald male in the front lifted up his hand, allowing to grey hawk to swoop down from the sky, landing on his arm.

Gah!!!

A series of weird noises could be heard in the distance, like the howling of beasts before their demise.

"It’s like a crow, but also like a bat. Disgusting indeed" The grey-robed girl behind the baldy frowned as she spoke. "Garen, are we returning to the war guild immediately?"

The baldy shaked his head.

"There’s no time. We absolutely should not return now to avoid being recruited as guards to defend the city, which would limit our freedom. Let’s go to my place. The guards won’t be able to defend for long."

"How about the three brats behind us?" Angel turned her head to look at the girl on the white horse, and the luxurious carriage following closely behind. The curtains swayed open to reveal the faces of two young girls.

"Let them be. We do not have the responsibility to protect them." Garen muttered.

Their two black stallions galloped swiftly on the path, but the white horse and horse carriage did not fall behind, easily keeping up with them.

Woo!!!

The lengthy cry sound a horn could be heard in the distance.

Garen’s expression changed slightly. He slowed down abruptly and looked far ahead.

"It’s the city’s horn! Let’s go this way!"

He tugged tightly at the reins and headed to the right. Angel followed closely, but the girl on the white horse continued to stare into the distance, in the direction of the sound of the horn. Worry and doubt was evident in her expression.

Garen continued riding, disregarding the two parties behind him. He bent his body to lie on the back of his horse, being extra vigilant towards his surroundings.

Suddenly, a glimpse of darkness flashed over his head. A black shadow passed him, landing instantly on the path ahead of him.

Bang!!!

A three-metre long, unihorn lizard landed on the ground, flapping its bat-like wings. He roared at Garen, emitting air flow from its flared nostrils.

The startled horses raised their front hooves in fear, giving off sharp cries.

"What kind of abomination is this!!?" Angel tried her best to stable the horses. She made a futile attempt by applying pressure on the horse’s belly, while uttering comfort sounds.

Before the voices came to a stop, Garen sprung into action. He leapt from the horseback into the air, right at the giant lizard.

His right hand instantly transformed into a reddish, translucent texture. It looked like slow motion, but in fact he pressed his palm onto the lizard’s forehead in light-speed.

Bang!

Garen somersaulted onto the back of his horse.

"Move!" He tugged on the reins, passed the lizard and continued forward.

Angel hesitated for a moment, but continued to keep up. The white horse and horse carriage initially had some doubts, but were too afraid to stay away from Garen and Angel. They passed the lizard and hurried forward.

The unihorn lizard lay still in the middle of the road, its whole body enveloped with hints of blue. Evidently, it had been paralyzed by poison.

　　*************

Suburbs, At the edge of the City

At a deserted courtyard in the district, a few unihorn lizards swept across the sky. They headed towards the location with the most people, leaving dark shadows on the ground wherever they went.

A handful of riders scurried into the courtyard. The gently slowed down, comforting the frightened horses.

The riders quickly stopped at a premise in the middle of the courtyard.

The bald man who was leading got down from his horse.　

"Give me a moment Angel, let me grab something. Then we can clean up the unihorn lizards in the vicinity."

"I’ll wait for you outside." Angel nodded, rewearing two black rings. These two rings represented two new black panthers, different from the ones that were destroyed by Garen. These two panthers were her back ups.

Garen took a glance at the girl in the white horse and the carriage who have just arrived.

The white-robed girl came down from her horse and approached the two girls from the carriage. They had a combination of hopelessness, doubt, fear and worry written on their faces. Only the elderly carriageman was standing by their side, comforting them.

"Angel, let them enter the city by themselves. I have no energy to protect them."

"Leave it to me. I will talk to them." Angel lightly nodded.

Garen dipped his head, turned his back and entered his yard.

He opened the door with a key. Everything seemed safe and sound, just like it was when he left. Three blue-back giant lizards lazily crouched on the counter, trying to pose as statues.

Garen shut the door and heaved a sigh of relief.

"I must strengthen myself as soon as possible."

He stood at the door, watching the three blue-back lizards leisurely crawling towards him.

"Let’s try. I’m going to give evolving these creatures a shot." He was distinct from other totem users. The rest of them relied on external stimuli to evolve their totems, while he could use his potential points, which is a unique ability, to evolve his totems.

He wasn’t aware of the difference between these two evolution methods. But his gut told him there would a substantial difference between evolving with potential points and the usual methods.

He examined the attribute pane just below his vision.

The short-tailed croc and blue-back lizards both needed 3 potential points to evolve. The only difference was that the blue-back lizards had a higher probability than the short-tailed croc.

He had 15 potential points left.

"As I need something that can be of use right away, I shall start with the short-tailed croc."

He looked at the skill pane, finding the short-tailed croc’s icon among a myriad of other totem icons.

"Short-tailed Croc; First Form: live totem, can be upgraded. Success Rate: 54% (The weaker the totem, the higher the probability of success). Potential Points Consumption: 300%.

Abilities: Bite, Guise."

"54%, still acceptable." Garen’s heart skipped a beat as a black-armored crocodile crawled out from his bedroom. At one glance, it might be mistaken as a long, black plank.

His gaze fixated on the short-tailed croc for around three seconds.

At that instant, the white-tailed croc’s icon turned blurry, turning into a ball of red light. Consequently, the accompanying explanation signs blurred out as well.

For the attribute pane, the potential points dropped from 1522%, all the way down to 1222%.

As the adjustment of the potential points took place, the short-tailed croc started having shivers all over his body.

His figure expanded rapidly, growing longer and bigger.

From two to three metres, it grew to exceeding five metres, almost filling up the whole hall on the first floor.

As the crocodile’s hide on it's back grew dark and darker, a line of black, sharp spikes started forming in the middle.

The giant crocodile opened it's jaw, emitting a horrible stench.

Within ten seconds, its size grew from two, three metres to exceeding five metres. Other than that, there weren't much changes to it's appearance.

All of a sudden, Garen noticed something peculiar. The giant crocodile opened it's big jaw, as if it wanted to show him something.

He peered into the crocodile’s mouth. It startled him when he saw a red, snake-like tongue. On the top of the tongue was a needle-like, meaty organ.

"What is this?"

Garen muttered to himself. He looked straight at the skill pane where the totem icons were located.

"Deep Swamp Croc; Evolved form of Short-tailed Croc, Second form live totem, can be upgraded. Success Rate: 24%. Potential Points Consumption: 500%"

Abilities: Explosive Strike, Iron Hide, Parasitism."

"Parasitism?" Garen examined the final ability. At his gaze, an explanation sign appeared behind it.

"Parasitism: The deep swamp crocs in the olden days contained a huge amount of various parasite larvae in their body. Once an enemy is bitten, the larvae can be injected into its body. In a short span of time, the enemy will experience excruciating torture, which will eventually lead to death. After dying, a swamp parasite will emerge from the corpse to fight for the crocs. Note: A deep swamp croc can only cultivate three parasites per day."

Garen was delighted. The parasite was like buying one for three. Just by looking at its size, a croc evolving to this stage, is an immensely strong presence. Without considering the totem light, the physique of the totem creatures was a huge factor in battles. The physique determines strength and speed, and even lethality.

Of course this is without considering the totems special abilities. A good example would be the most sought after black wolf. After evolving into it second form - the fire wolf, it could generate vigorous, scorching flames.

Chapter 290: The Outbreak of War 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

The deep swamp croc swayed its tail gently, dragged it's heavy body across the floor quietly, and quickly crawled out from an open window. Garen was dumbfounded by the fact that it did not make any noise.

He grabbed his necessities, and some things that might be of use, stuffed them into the leather bag he brought, then hid it under the bed. Then, he made his way out of the house.

On the path outside, Angel crouched beside the corpse of a unihorn lizard, attentively examining the abomination.

The lizard, who wasn't there when Garen entered the house, was obviously destroyed by her.

"What's up? What's it's strength like?" Garen went over and crouched beside her.

"Troublesome." Angel said with a solemn expression. "I initially thought it's a common, mutated creature. But in fact, it had totem light. If I didn't use accelerate, I’m not that sure if my panther could handle it. It should be at the level of an elite first form totem."

"Be careful." Garen patted her shoulder. He valued this companion who worked well with him.

He glanced at the trembling horse carriage on the other side. The three girls seemed like they wanted to come closer, but it was evident that they were a little afraid.

"Sir." The elderly carriageman carefully walked over and stood in front of Garen with some hesitation. "I guess both of you should be completing some form of mission? I'm wondering whether we could temporarily hire you to send us into the city. We can pay you some wages!"

"Wage? How much can you pay?" Garen muttered. He didn't think they could offer much. When totem users speak about money, usually tens of thousands of Rumbs. To a normal human, it would already be their lifetime savings.

"A hundred thousand!" The elderly carriageman blurted out a figure. "A hundred thousand Rumbs!"

"Barely acceptable." Garen nodded. "Angel, send them into the city. Then meet me at the war guild." He looked at a silver pocket-watch that he had just retrieved from his pocket. "It is 1.15pm now, let's meet after lunch at 4pm. Okay?"

Angel nodded and said: "No problem. A hundred thousand just for a trip is not a bad deal. Let's go ladies." She shouted at the three girls as she mounted her black stallion.

"I got to check on how my friend is doing." Garen casually mentioned. "There might be a possibility…." he suddenly grinned.

At the attribute pane at the bottom of his vision, there was a sudden jolt in potential points.

The potential points spiked from 1222% to 1287%, then quickly spiked again to 1356%. The two consecutive spikes surprised Garen.

It was the deep swap croc! It suddenly came to his realization. He had just released the newly evolved croc to hunt the unihorn lizards. He did not expect the effects to take place so soon. Even more out of his expectation was that killing the unihorn lizards could lead to an increase in potential points.

From the figures, it was evident that the deep swamp croc was single handedly battling and defeating two unihorn lizards. That should be the reason for the two spikes.

After sending off Angel’s party, Garen stood silently on the path, looking at his yard. Inside, the deep swamp croc was silently crawling past the fence into the yard. It was holding one of the lizards in his jaw, obviously as a snack and parasite for itself.

Garen noticed that there was a fresh, bleeding wound on the forelimbs of the deep swamp croc, seemingly sustained during the clash. Garen shuddered.

The deep swamp croc as a second form totem, could actually be harmed by two first form unihorn lizards.

"Now it's only a first form totem. There would certainly be stronger creatures in the nest that have not revealed themselves. No wonder the Obscuro Society dared to go against the whole world. With powerful bioweapons like that, they wouldn't have to worry about military strength.

He pondered for a moment, suddenly felt something and he turned to look at the yard across his own.

The yard of his blonde female neighbour was peaceful, except the window curtains which were swaying slightly. It was clear that someone was spying on him.

Garen was about to leave when the door from the yard opposite the street flung open.

"Sir Garen!" The blonde neighbour yelled. Her haggard and deeply trouble expression showed that she was struck with terror. A big, strong, young man followed behind her. As they had similar looks, it seemed that they could be twins.

"Sir Garen, can you help sending us into the city?" His neighbour looked frightened. She looked at Garen pitifully.

Gahhhh!!

An array of unihorn lizard cries could be heard in the distance.

Garen looked at his pocket watch and frowned. "It’s easy to enter the city. But since we’re neighbours, I want to warn you that the situation is very different now. The city might be worse off. If you are willing, stay in your own home. My baby is currently cleaning up the creatures in the vicinity. As the population here is small and sparse, it won’t draw the creature’s line of sight. Should be safe."

At that instance, she let out an expression of hopelessness and doubt. 　

"What do we now? When can the Royal Alliance drive away the creatures!" She was like most of the population, placing all their hope on the Royal Alliance. They viewed the current situation as a one off, incidental, regional turmoil.

Garen shook his head.

"I’m not sure. You decide yourself."

"Then we still want to enter the city." The girl muttered after hesitating.

"I’ll give you both ten minutes. We will leave immediately after that." Garen directly responded.

　　***************

General Veron’s Third Battalion, Wiped Out.

Through the blue messenger birds, the news spread to hundreds of countries throughout the East Continent.

At the same instant, newspapers all over the world reported the news of unknown creatures attacking human cities. But soon, people would gradually not be able to purchase these papers..

The blue messenger birds started constantly falling from the sky. Other than the unihorn lizards, there were various flying creatures who occupying the sky, which was the channel of communication between cities.

Iron Tank City

War Guild Mission Hall

As Garen stepped into the hall, he saw injured people all over the hall. Some of them had even lost their limbs. They pale faces indicated severe loss of blood.

"Garen, how are you unscathed?" A strong man with a single sheepy eye stood up astonishingly. "Right. You are considered one of the strongest in the first form mission hall." He immediately took a seat.

"Thomas? Aren’t you alright as well?" Garen walked over and sat in front of the man. "The situation seems dire." He asked as he scanned the area around him.

"It’s tough out there. Bounty is growing daily but nobody dares to accept jobs. The monsters are everywhere." One-eyed thomas whispered.

At this time, from the reception room of the main hall, walked out a squad of brown-robed men and women. The leader was burly man with short hair. There was a blood-reddish scar on his right cheek, looking like a savage.

The man held a silver helmet in his arms, quickly scanning through the rest of the people in the hall.

A white-haired elderly man holding a red staff followed behind. Closely after them were two perfect-figured women in black robes.

"It’s the Galileo Squad. They should be taking up the two toughest missions." One-eyed Thomas stared at the party as he whispered to Garen.

He wasn’t the only one. Everyone in the hall fixated their eyes on this party.

Garen was familiar with the Galileo Squad. Its leader, Galileo, was an elite second form totem users, while all the members were second form totem users. They even had a totem smith in their squad. With this elite line-up, they completed several challenging missions, gaining fame in Iron Tank City.

There were there strong squads in Iron Tank City which frequented the war guild for years. Only the ace of the Galileo Squad was a second form totem user, while the leaders of the other two squads had third form ultimate totems under their command.

The Galileo Squad left the hall, quickly disappearing on the path outside the door.

Garen retrieved his gaze, listening to Thomas' gentle words of adoration.

"If only I could be as strong as the Galileo Squad."

"You should forget it. Their most basic prerequisite is to have two second form totems." A bald, plump man laughed.

Garen and Thomas chatted for a moment. He was waiting for someone. After sending his female neighbour into the city, he directly headed here to check out the situation.

The situation was indeed dire. The war guild must have given up a fair bit to incentify the top squads.

The first form mission hall was the most crowded area for a small town like the Iron Tank City. For the second form and third form halls, it was just furnishings. As a place where only a select elite could enter, there were simply no exchanges going on.

Soon, their shift ended. Garen stood up and walked towards the mission counter. He took out the previously completed mission list and handed it in.

"Completed once again? That fast?" The guy receiving the list was a sinister looking middle-aged man. He and Garen were familiar with each other as the last few mission lists were distributed by him.

"Bounties should have multiplied by a few fold recently, isn’t it?" Garen asked softly.

"You are smart." The middle-aged man nodded. "All of them have multiplied, you are just in time. Also, the governor’s mansion has just released a large batch of inactive totems. Would you like to have a look?" He spoke softly, with a sense of allurement in his voice. "There seems to a fair amount of decent core totems."

"Is it specially distributed?" Garen raised his brow.

"Of course, besides us, the war guild, where else can you find such elite firepower? If we do not provide support, wouldn’t we be just waiting for doom?"The middle-aged man answered surely.

"Is there a white dragonhawk?"

"Certainly. Although it is powerful, it’s not cheap to train it."

"Show me the list."

Garen’s heart skipped a beat. Although the white dragonhawk is strong, it also means it has been researched thoroughly, with many strategies to counter it.

He was different from other totem users. With the existence of potential points, he could rely on them for direct evolution, although the probability wasn’t high. He could choose a less-researched, foundationally strong new totem as his final card.

Once the evolution succeeded, as no one would be familiar with the power of this new totem, it definitely would have a remarkable impact.

Chapter 291: Materials 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

The middle aged man behind the counter handed out a roll of yellowed paper.

After receiving it, Garen unrolled the paper and brought it aside to have a long look at it.

" The Iron Tank City Army emergency goods deployment list:

Spear of Agas x 5

Full body armor x 7

Battle horse armor x 7

Military crossbow x 15

Inactivated totems:

Red Dragonhawk x 3

White Dragonhawk x 3

White bear x 5. Brown bear x 5, Black wolf x 5. Snow sculpture x 33. Fanged hound x 33. Black eagle x 10. Northern snow lion x 1. Cape Verdean Wolf x 15.

Black striped white tiger x 1. Ground drilling rhino x 1, Giant rattlesnake x 1."

Garen straightened out the paper with a few light shakes, and knitted his brows together. He then waited for another man to finish up his business at the counter before heading over again.

"These totems at the top, the last three are new to me. What is the price?"

The middle aged man took a quick glance at him. "Since you are an official member of the guild, we offer a special price for insiders. 1 million per totem. I shall warn you beforehand, the last one was listed separately, which means it does not have a legacy. The absence of a legacy means that it will be incapable of evolving. Although it has a strong foundation, you must bear this in mind."

"Noted." Garen was absolutely clear.

Ground drilling rhino and Giant rattlesnake still had a sliver of hope when it came to evolving, as results of prior research done by other people point towards that, or so he had heard. Only the ways of raising a Black striped white tiger remained a mystery, as no researcher has managed to figure that out. This breed of genetically mutated tigers is extremely ferocious. Although there is only one type, its speed, strength and lethalness is comparable to that of a Dragonhawk – minus the possibility of evolution. Various academies have tried, failed, and given up.

Not only that, the remaining numbers are but a few; would have never thought of actually seeing one here.

" How much money do I have left in the treasury?"Garen presented his medal.

It was passed over the counter and inquiries were according to the serial number.

" 870,000. You still need a little more. Do you want to accept a few quests?" The middle aged man asked. He currently has a huge pile of unattended quests.

"It’s alright, I will come over in a bit. Remember to hold on to it for me." Garen covertly handed over a few one hundred silver sheets. The man quietly accepted it.

"Don’t worry, I will keep it for you for two days. Anyways, this is an item that many would not want to purchase, even if they could afford it. Who would want to spend a million on a totem that is incapable of evolving?

" Thanks , I am intend to have it as a secondary totem." Garen took a totem introduction leaflet that was handed to him over the counter and turned away to leave.

He only had a couple of tens of thousands on him at the moment, which was definitely not enough. However, the resources he had stashed up previously would be put in good use.

"This timing is just right, if I would have waited a little more, all the good items could have been used up and taken. Not only that, I still have to fork out another sum to purchase war shackles and war halls."

He decided to obtain the black striped white tiger first, as he was planning to use it as his core totem anyways. The information on the black striped white tiger was fairly brief, Garen found the line describing the black striped white tiger from the information on the totem introduction leaflet.

"Black striped white tiger: A type of basic totem, possesses extreme speed and lethality, its 6 centimeter sharp teeth can easily bite through any known defense a totem has. Originated 600 years ago from a remote academy called Taja Cannes. Power: Tail whip, Puncturing Crunch."

Leaving the guild, Garen boarded a horse carriage, heading straight towards the young grain storehouse that he bought.

Seated on the horse carriage, he looked out the carriage window – 5 out of 10 people on the streets were holding a gourd shaped container, lining up at the rice store, common goods store and bakery to purchase items. Several fruit and vegetable stalls were sold out and closed for the day.

A few wholesale stores that were of a larger scale placed signs that signify a limited stock supply, barely sustaining themselves.

From time to time, ox carts dragging along goods would pass by. The area of Iron Tank City was seemingly vacant of the noblemen and businessmen that were usually clothed luxuriously.

Garen estimated that the items he had stored up prior to this could be sold at a higher price, therefore a total sale of 3 million should not be a problem. Although so, the most cost effective way seemed to be setting aside a portion of basic living expenses while using the rest in exchange for expendable battle items.

If an exchange was done instead, he would be dealing with the guild directly, which means it is likely that he will only need half of his item storage in exchange for the Black striped white tiger. Garen believed that the guild had good taste, and was pretty sure he will be able to recognize the advantage of hoarding rare items for enormous profit.

If only he wasn’t in such dire need to evolve his core totem, Garen would have never thought of selling his items off so early.

The other half can be used to feed himself and occasionally purchase other items.

In no time, the horse carriage arrived at the area in Iron Tank where storehouses were specifically built.

Garen came down from the carriage, paid, and headed towards the deepest area on the left.

His storehouse was built at a secluded left corner.

He did not go far before realizing with a startle that something was wrong. Several grey ox carts were continuously dragging along young grains from the deeper part of the area, the cart drivers were servants clothed in grey cloth.

"The man in front, please halt!"

A short distance away a group of armed men on patrol rushed over.

"What are you doing? The area in front is a private property! You are not allowed to trespass." The leader of the group was a man with a mustache, and he was staring at Garen with stern gaze.

"Private property?" Garen’s face dropped. From the gaps in between the storehouses he could see the entrance of his storehouse, and ox carts were dragging young grains from inside.

He had completed so many quests, gone through life and death situations with Goth and the others, suffered heavy injuries just to have a small amount savings. The young grains he had purchased is now being towed away from his storehouse by one ox cart after another.

"Whose men are you?!" Garen’s face darkened. "This is my storehouse, and the young grains you are towing away happens to be mine!"

Moustache man frowned. "This is the private property of Quartermaster Griffith, if there are any issues please speak to our boss."

Garen’s face darkened again, forcefully pushing away one of the men who was blocking him, and walked towards his storehouse in huge strides.

"You stand right there!! Do you hear me!" The moustached man was furious. He chased up to Garen’s footsteps and grabbed his shoulders. His hands grabbed nothing but the air though, as Garen’s was much faster than he had imagined.

"Take him down!!"Moustache man shouted all of a sudden.

An army of men rushed up, those who had swords bore swords, those who were meant to obstruct his way, did so.

The ground underneath Garen’s feet shook, and a shapeless energy immediately threw the men off their feet, and they flew, hitting the ground with intensity.

Nearby, an ox cart moving goods was disturbed. The ox that was pulling the cart let out a series distressed moos, anxious to escape from the place.

The old man sitting in front of the storehouse that was tasked with administration felt things going horribly wrong, and sent out a blue messenger bird. He fell into his seat, face pale, plagued with fear as he stared at Garen.

"I am Quartermaster Griffith’s house keeper! You can’t touch me! You can’t touch me!" He muttered the last phrase repeatedly, the fear seemed to have paralyzed his senses.

"Quartermaster?" Garen narrowed his eyes, a spark of an idea brewing in his heart.

His hand reached out to grab the old man’s collar, lifting him towards himself.

"Just because he is a Quartermaster he is allowed to carelessly snatch away someone else’s private property? It seems like he got bored of living and wants a taste of death…"

"Master...I have nothing to do with this master!" The old man was sniveling with tears pouring out of his eyes, his whole body was shaking like a leaf, cold sweat plastering the hair near the temples of his face.

Garen hurled him aside carelessly and waited where he was. The blue bird the old man had sent earlier should have reached the Quartermaster, whatever or whoever that is; he should be here any minute now.

Without waiting for long, a black luxury car was driven into the storehouse area, and stopped a short distance away from the storehouse he was at.

Two sizeable men clothed in black military uniforms came down from the car and walked down.

The man who was walking slightly ahead had a nasty expression on his face, with traces of anger caused by humiliation and a slight urgency.

The other man’s face was immensely calm. His hands were mindlessly fiddling with a silver pocket watch, while his middle finger was embellished with a black gemstone ring.

" Type 2 totem user?" Garen’s gaze locked onto the man holding the pocket watch.

"I am Griffith , who dares to cause trouble here?!"The man who was ahead roared loudly, his eyes quickly fixed on Garen who was standing in front of the storehouse. " It is you I presume? Seems like after a long time of refraining myself, no one in the city knows the name of Griffith anymore."

" Griffith, is it? Who are you to carelessly invade and occupy the private property of citizens?" Garen faced both of them, raised his voice and spoke coldly. "I have previously purchased the young grains here as well as other items, now all of a sudden you own them. Do you not have the intention of giving an explanation?"

"You are the previous owner of this storehouse?" Griffith sneered, "Are you sure you are not mistaken about something? These young grains are items that the other shop owners and I have transported over earlier on – I have a contract with these shop owners as proof. Deeming others’ property as your own… from what I see, you are the one invading other people’s property!"

While speaking he thrusts out a stack of paperwork that he had obviously prepared, and waved it around at Garen. He had a mischievous look plastered on his face.

Garen frowned. To be honest, this was his biggest fear. Being a lone ranger without a background, to have a business that involved buying and selling as per what he was doing, encountering these types of trickery was what he was most afraid of. After all, the buying and selling business was not supported by the government, and you could only conduct it underground. Once a lack of power is realized by others, it was highly possible that one must absorb the bitter consequences.

The other party he guessed, had done a background check on him, which explained their unscrupulous behavior.

" Alright, now that everything is clear, we should figure out the compensation for injuring my guards. I am known to be ever so generous, all you need to pay is a small amount, and I won’t investigate the matter any further." Griffith said with a smile on his face.

He had already known the identity of the man in front of him. If it were not for the fact that he had entered the battle guild and was a member, he would have gotten his bodyguards to capture him.

But it is different now than it was then, for the war guild is the front line of the entire combat team of Iron Tank City. If he were to be caught, the guild will definitely conduct some questioning, and if it were to be blown out of proportion, sensitive issues such as invading one’s property was likely to bring about bad consequences, which might bring huge losses to both parties in an immense impact.

Which is why it is important to have a good control of the scale of the issue – to let the other party undergo a small loss while keeping the matter down low at the same time.

"Alright. We will leave the matter as so. As you are a member of the war guild, I will not look into the damage you have caused my soldiers." Griffith said with a smile.

Chapter 292: Materials 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

Garen squinted his eyes slightly, momentarily looking at the person in front of him.

"Fine...Excellent. Griffith, I’ll remember this name." It was impossible for him to act now due to the city being under heightened martial law. Anyone who challenged the military during this high tension period may be strongly repressed.

Regardless of reason, attacking an army official would be considered treason. Regardless of sufficient reasoning, the outcome is being hunted down by totem users all over the city. A serious offence might even bring you the wrath of the Governor’s Dragon Guard. The Dragon Guard was a squadron with terrifying strength, formed entirely by second form white dragonhawk totem users. Anyone one of them could take down a totem user of the same level.

Garen assessed himself. In his current, the most he could handle was a common second form totem user. Moreover, as he hasn't tested it in battle, extra caution was needed. Although he was confident in his abilities, his confidence was built on the evolved deep swamp croc. As his wildcard, it wasn't to be revealed easily.

Even by revealing it, whether it could deal with enemy second form totem users was a serious question of its own.

In actual fact, silver totems were still not on the level of original totems. Hence, it is very possible that the deep swamp croc would be slightly weaker than original second form totems.

Garen’s mind was overwhelmed with thoughts. Without saying a word, he tossed a stack of silver Rumb, then turned to leave the warehouse.

Behind him, Griffith and his men were so pleased that they burst into laughter instantly.

Garen suppressed the discontentment in his heart. If the enemy did not have a second form totem user in their midst, he might have took action.

As long as he did it cleanly, people may not notice anyway. They at most would have thought it would be the doings of the monsters outside of the city.

Griffith grinned and as he was about to reply, he suddenly felt something was off. It was as if he was the only person who heard a sound, while the second form totem users beside him did not feel anything at all.

Griffith’s laughter abruptly stopped. He unknowingly felt a faint shudder in his heart. Swiftly, he turned to look in the direction Garen left and he could not even see his shadow although merely a few seconds had passed.

"What’s going on?" Mecca, a second form totem user who was beside him asked.

"Didn’t you hear the sound?" There was a trace of uneasiness on Griffith’s face.

"Sound? What Sound?" Mecca frowned. The few soldiers beside looked at each other, feeling confused as well.

Griffith instantly panicked. For the first time, he secretly regretted finding fault with that guy.

"My heart still feels there is something wrong.." He wondered if he was hallucinating a moment ago.

　　****************

Feeling unappeased, Garen left the warehouse and headed towards the Mercenary Guild. In both his past life and current life, as a martial artist and a fighter, he was always a ruthless person. Meeting someone as reckless as this yet not being able to annihilate him, he got more and more disgruntled by the minute.

"Patience...Patience...I will get my chance soon.."He knew in his heart that a multitude of monsters will soon be laying siege to the city. In the face of overwhelming disaster, no one would notice the death of one or two quartermasters.

Looking at the progression outside, the large-scale siege would be happening soon.

At this moment, it is imperative that he gathered enough money to obtain the black-striped white tiger.

Once he reached the Mercenary Guild, he entered and sat in the corner of the hall, waiting for a few others to arrive.

He had lunch at the guild, and about 1pm, Andy and his sister entered the guild. With one glance, they noticed the bald Garen sitting in a corner. Both of them, in the usual grey robes, walked directly towards Garen and sat across him.

"Haven’t seen you for a few days. What have you been up to? How was the vacation?" Andy took off his robe as he sat in.

"I’m doing okay. Only a minor setback." Garen answered lightly. "At the end of the day, I shouldn’t take any chances."

"What happened? Spill it." Jessica murmured, "Maybe my brother can lend you a hand."

"Forget it, I’ll handle it myself." Garen grinned. "Let’s not talk about these. Thank God you guys are alright. There are hordes of monsters out there. If we didn’t just quit, I reckon we would be in big trouble."

At the mention of monsters, Andy and Jessica’s countenance sunk.

Andy quietly produced a folded piece of paper from his arms and passed it to Garen.

"What’s this?" Garen unfolded the paper. It was a newspaper extract.

The headlines were clearly printed with: Terrorist organization Obscuro Society claims, fighting to create a new, better world.

The details were stated below.

The Obscuro Society claims responsibility for the multiple uprisings. At the same time, they issued an ultimatum to the Royal Alliance.

"This newspaper was from two days before the creatures appeared." Andy whispered, "We can now be sure that the Obscuro Society is the culprit."

Soon, Goth made his entrance. He was wearing a brand new dungarees, looking fresh and energetic with his new crew cut. He sat down beside Garen, took up the pot of coffee and directly poured it into his mouth.

He gulped down the coffee, put the pot down heavily, and burped.

"What should we do now? Let’s take a vote!?"

"Chill. Help me guys, lend me some money." Garen mumbled. He initially wanted to borrow from Angel, but borrowing from the few people in front of him would be the same. With his eight hundred and twenty thousand, he only needed a hundred and eighty thousand to obtain the black-striped white tiger. It wasn’t much.

"Just say the amount you need. But let me clear, don’t mention anything about three hundred thousand." Andy generously waved his hand.

"Lend me a hundred and eighty thousand."

"No problem." Andy frankly replied, "Luckily you did not mention three hundred thousand. That is all that i have."

"Didn’t you say that you’ve finished your money?" Jessica whispered.

"Do I seem like that kind of person?" Andy laughed heartily.

"Jessica, I saw a nice scarf just now and I bought it for you as a gift." Goth took out a piece of folded cloth and passed it to Jessica. By his expression, even a fool could discern his intention.

Jessica’s cheeks turned red. She bowed her head sheepishly.

Andy and Garen stood up simultaneously and went to the Mercenary Guild’s counter. They withdrew a hundred and eighty million Rumb and packed it in a black pouch. Garen rushed off with the money, planning to obtain the black-striped white tiger as soon as possible. Otherwise, the price might have increased after a while.

After making a few turns in the alleys, he very quickly he arrived at the War Guild. The crowd was sparse, seemingly much quieter than before.

After entering the hall, Garen headed straight towards the counter and handed over the money to the middle-aged man.

"That fast?" The man, who was gobbling down a plate of pasta, was caught in disbelief.

"Please." Garen nodded.

"Follow me then." The middle-aged man stopped speaking, stood up and pulled open a side-door. Both of them entered a small room at the back.

Like the last time, they went across the room, crossing an alley and quickly arrived at a row of wooden doors.

The middle-aged man took out a key and unlocked the first door.

"Wait here." He went in for a moment and returned with a black box.

"This is what you've requested, the only one in Iron Tank City." He passed the black box to Garen.

Holding the black box in his hand, Garen have it a pinch. The box was light, like a small jewellery box.

He flipped open the box. Between the black velvet was a black crystal ring. The activation spell was carved was on the cover of the box.

He retrieved the ring and tried it on. In the end, it could only fit on his left ring finger.

"Check it out." The middle-aged man shut the door, leaned on it while staring at him.

Garen nodded and raised his left hand. He murmured the spell according to the words on the box.

"Gomola, ehado, cyatin.." A series of unusual words left Garen’s mouth. This was a phonic interpretation of the ancient language. He did not understand it, but uttered it according to the phonics.

He made some gestures with his index finger in the air, drawing the totem activation symbol.

With a bang, the ring’s crystal emitted a black ray of light. As the ray of light hit the floor, it expanded into a ball of light. Once the light dissipated, a black-striped, white-skinned tiger strolled to Garen’s side. It smacked its lips, revealing a tongue filled with hooks which could easily sever flesh.

Owww...

The white tiger let out a low howl as it crouched beside Garen.

His body was about four metres long, with black spots from the head to the tail. Its thick tail was like a curled bat.

Garen patted the white tiger on its head, while browsing the skill pane below his vision.

Unsurprisingly, the black-striped white tiger’s icon was already present.

"Black-striped white tiger: First form totem, can be upgraded. Success Rate: 11%. Potential Points Consumption: 700%.

Abilities: Tail whip, Puncturing Crunch."

"11% success rate…" Garen’s scalp went numb. Even the neon butterfly had a 21% success rate, but this black-striped white tiger’s was 11%. Considering this fact, he had to try 10 times to success once. One try would use up 7 potential points.

Since he had decided on it, there was no other option. Besides the neon butterfly, he could only have one more totem with low success rate. This was the limit. His mediocre talent determined that he could only control two totems.

As he left the guild, Garen withdrew the white tiger. He then arrived at a remote alley.

Ruthlessly, Garen gestured in the air and drew a complicated, oval symbol.

The symbol shrunk instantly into the size of a fist, then into the size of a fingernail. It then flew into the black crystal ring.

Very soon, he felt a sensation that was totally different compared to common totems. It felt like the black-striped white tiger was more intimate than others. The vague distance between them shrank a fair bit.

He looked at the black-striped white tiger’s icon below his vision.

Suddenly, it overtook all the other totems on the list and was positioned first. There was a note which popped out on the side: Core.

His body illuminated with a layer of white light that stuck to his skin.

"Core totem, finally!"

Garen heaved a sigh of relief.

"I should rendezvous with Goth and the gang, then examine the tactics that Angel obtained. I must get ready to take on Griffith."

If his calculations were accurate, within these few days, Iron Tank City would face its first siege. That would be an opportunity for him to act.

There was a flash of ferocity in his eyes. Whoever snatched his belongings must have had a deathwish!

Chapter 293: Payback 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

Minggg~~~~

The white dragonhawks circling the sky let out an attack warcry.

Among the crowd, Garen looked up, focusing on one particular white dragonhawk in the air.

He tugged at his grey hoodie as he squeezed through the crowd, bowing his head to hide his face.

He pulled out a piece of cloth from his right sleeve. There was a round tactic drawn in red ink. It seem unrefined, with traces of red ink on its side.

A tactic was like an ancient spell, with a faint mystical sense.

As he rolled the cloth, Garen hastened his steps. He quickly entered a narrow alley along the street and walked through it. In front of him was another clean and luxurious street, where there was a row of gorgeous bungalows across it. All of them had white-golden roofs, but they were all empty, without a trace of population.

Garen swept his gaze from left to right. His eyes eventually fixated on the third bungalow.

Yesterday, he made an appointment with Goth and the gang to complete missions together these couple of days, but the warcy has sounded. The real war was finally beginning.

Iron Tank City’s dragon stood no chance in resisting the countless unihorn lizards.

At this point, all he had to do was wait, until Iron Tank City mobilizes the resources they have accumulated over the years. Then in the midst of chaos, he would first take down that annoying quartermaster.

Through Garen's investigation, he found out that Quartermaster Griffith controlled a third of the warehouses in the city. All of the items stored in the warehouses were recorded. Other than himself, the private belongings of around ten other victims were confiscated in the name of military usage.

Garen knew from a familiar contact in the war guild, that other than himself, there were others waiting to find fault with the quartermaster. But the guy never leaves the side of Mecca, the second form totem master. There was completely no chance.

People from the War Guild and Assassin’s Guild also could not find a chance because of this.

Garen stood at the alley in his grey robe and hoodie. He was dressed alike with the majority of the hoodie wearers.

He abruptly stepping back, as if his sixth sense was telling him to hide in the shadows of the alley.

Suddenly, a blur flashed from the bungalow’s shade.

"Assassin's guild..?" Garen raised his eyebrows, holding his breath as he fixated his eyes on the shady region of the bungalow.

There was a quick blur, flashing among the shades and people’s blindspots, like a butterfly in the dark.

The man, who was athletically built, clenched a dagger in his mouth. He was actually a pale faced young man, seemingly not over 18 years of age.

"Interesting. Trying to assassinate Griffith with his own skills when he isn't even a totem master." Garen stood still, merely lifting his head to stare at the sky.

The sky was outcast. The clusters of grey clouds signalling a downpour was coming anytime.

Ming ~~~~!

It was another desolate horn cry.

Instantly, with the sound of the horn, throughout the whole Iron Tank City centre, surrounding the Rowen Tower, an enormous flock of white-golden hawks soared into the sky.

Hummm!!!

The howls of countless white dragonhawks came down from the sky. It was as if voices had weight.

Garen could not help but bow his body, feeling shaken by the sound. His face revealed an expression of dismay.

"Iron Tank! Iron Tank! Iron Tank!"

As the clashing sound between metallic armor and weapons came from the distance, batallions of soldiers marched orderly towards the city gates. Their loud, orderly march cries could even be heard in the city where Garen was standing.

"It has begun…" Garen sighed as he turned back to look at the city gates.

He thought for a moment, pressed both his palms lightly on the sides of the wall and crawled up the wall like a lizard. With a light somersaulted, he landed on the roof of a third level building on the right side.

As he stood in the wall, he gazed in the direction of the sound.

In the dark grey sky, countless of white dragonhawks surrounded the white-golden hawks as they flew out of the city, like a big cluster of clouds.

The dragonhawk riders were dressed in silver armor, armed with two to three metres long spears. The white-golden dragonhawk riders were clad in full golden body armor, even the hawks’ body were protected with golden armor.

In the horizon, black ink-like, dark clouds were spreading over here.

As the dark clouds drew closer, the countless strange, rattling sounds could be heard clearer and clearer.

The black giant lizards, equipped with black wings and fang like horns on their heads, were swaying their long tails as they headed directly towards Iron Tank City.

Garen stood on the rooftop. Like the countless of citizens in the city, he was staring at the two opposing clouds of forces closing on each other.

Bang!!

The white and dark cloud completely clashed into each other. In a split second, a large number of dark clouds fell from the sky.

The soldiers and citizens below let out a loud cheer.

"This is a war between totem users." Garen stared at the ground below, where soldiers were shooting with bows and guns in futile.

A huge array of arrows and bullets could only barely take down single digits of the unicorn lizards. Only a few totem users protected by soldiers, were summoning creatures to protect the safety of the commoners around.

Several lizards who were shot down rolled a few times on the floor, got back on their feet with only minor injuries. One of them picked up a swordsman beside with it's jaw and gobbled him up. With a casual fling of its paw, it tore several armored soldiers into pieces.

Human weapons were completely ineffective towards the lizards. Very soon, fear was like an epidemic, swiftly spreading amongst the crowd. As the soldiers collapse, more and more unihorn lizards pounce at the ground below, intending to annihilate the humans on the ground. The totem users in the city rose up to defend, barely forming a formation as the retreated to a corner.

Bang!!

A unihorn lizard leapt into the bungalow that Garen was in. In a split second, explosive noises and the roars of a lion could be heard from within.

In the following moments, the second, third and more unihorns descended quickly. They shrunk into balls like black meteorites, then spreading their wings as they landed and instantly started their killing.

Ahhh!!

From the bungalow came a scream, followed by the panicky cries of a girl. The door swung open with a bang, a middle-aged woman drenched in blood ran out, trying to escape. She only managed to crawl for a short distance, then could no longer move. Her lower body was snapped into two earlier, and she was only crawling on the ground with her upper body, leaving a blood trail behind.

Garen turned his gaze towards Griffith's bungalow.

There was a unihorn lizard that landed there, but very quickly became silent.

"Looks like this situation does not pose much of a threat to them.." Garen blinked his eyes.

The sound of the screams and shouts seemed to be going further away, signaling that the main resistance was moving further and further away.

Griffith’s bungalow stayed completely silent and still.

Bang!

A unihorn lizard landed on the roof behind Garen, rapidly spreading it's body from from the ball.

It open its jaw filled with sharp teeth, rushed towards Garen with a roar.

Sheesh!!

Garen frowned, gently shaking the black crystal ring on his right hand. A ray of black light shot out, and in the ray of light, leapt out the black-striped white tiger, colliding with the unihorn lizard. The two large creatures rolled in the boll, biting and slashing at each other.

Garen stood at the side, quietly watching without assisting.

"It's a good opportunity to see the black-striped white tiger’s overall strength."

The black-striped white tiger was swift indeed. After swiping at the lizard, it could evade the lizards counterattack, then pushing away it's head, appearing to be very agile. Moreover, every time it opened it's jaw, a bite from it would tear out a big piece of flesh.

After just three simple swipes, the black-striped white tiger launched forward, mercilessly pressing down the lizard. It bit into the lizard’s throat, gulping down the fresh blood.

Shriekkkk!

The lizard’s head was torn apart by the white tiger.

Awwww!!!

The white tiger let out a howl, stood up in it's blood-stained body and started to feed on the lizard’s corpse. It was only lightly scratched.

"No wonder there are people who are willing to choose this kind of totem even though it cannot be evolved. Those that can be passed down until today surely are not simple characters." Garen nodded his head in satisfaction. Suddenly, three black dots soared over his head. He quickly withdrew the white tiger, and jumped down the roof. After constantly prancing in the shadows with all his might, he disappeared into a blur and entered Griffith’s bungalow.

As he silently entered the bungalow, he heard the sound of an impatient argument going on from within. The sounds came and go with the wind.

".....ours….out, left….who is responsible…."

"Stay here….who...don’t leave…"

Garen sped up, silently approaching the three-story bungalow from the garden. As he quickly arrived at a Lily bush, he stopped abruptly and stared at the ground.

There was a circle or silver arcs on the ground, faintly shimmering in silver light.

The arcs stretched from two sides, like a setting surrounding the whole bungalow.

"Warning line?" Garen remembered from teacher Emin’s teachings. Only a luminarist with a complete heritage could perform such an act.

He followed the silver warning line to the back of the bungalow. The voices became clearer by the moment. There were two men voices debating about something and it was evident one of them was Griffith’s voice.

"....no confidence to hold Iron Tank City. They thought I couldn't see it if they kept it from me! If it wasn't for my men in the information department, I would have foolishly followed into battle. Now! Right now! We have to leave immediately! The unihorn lizards will increase, more and more!!" Griffith seemed very emotional and agitated.

The other male voice was abnormally calm. "Do not worry Griffith, the Grand Duke has took numerous elites to exterminate the lizard’s nest. As long the breeding nest is destroyed, at most the creatures can only cause minor damage."

"How many times do I have to say before you understand!" The sound of someone pacing back-and-forth heavily came from within. "Alright alright.. Mecca, we are brothers who grew up together. Let me tell you the truth. The situation now is dire, the creatures out there…" He lowered his voice.

A normal human probably couldn't even hear a single sound, worse if the other side lowered their voice. But Garen, with his abnormally clear senses, could easily hear Griffith's whisper.

"...there are at least 10 million of the creatures...This is the statistic calculated by the information department. My informant had just sent me a message. Even if the Grand Duke and his party could destroy the nests, this is not a number we can defend against!" Garen murmured.

Mecca, the second form totem user instantly ran out of words to say, breathing heavily.

"Who!!" Mecca roared loudly of a sudden.

Dang!!

The high-pitched sound of weapons clashing.

"Looking for death!!" Mecca coldly hummed.

From the bungalow came the sound of a man’s bored humming.

Very quickly, the peace resumed within.

Chapter 294: Payback 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

"Stop chasing! We currently don’t have the time to settle these things!" Griffith said loudly.

"There are still people outside!"Mecca said coldly. "Let’s go out and take a look!"

Garen felt it as well. Numerous men clothed in black had already reached the villa’s entrance.

"No one dares to steal my cousin’s property! Griffith, you are dead meat!" On the left, one of those clothed in black remarked darkly.

"Just a puny Quartermaster…"The leader of the black clad men had a harsh look plastered on his face, his body vaguely emitting a killer’s aura; it was pretty obvious that he often walked on the edge of life or death situations, a ruthless character.

A Unihorn lizard swooped down from above and landed on the ground, making plans to bite the men clad in black robe.

Shooooh!

Right next to the men in black, a dark shadow loomed forward abruptly, bit off the Unihorn lizard’s head in moments and left the now headless lizard crashing into the ground.

"Wilde!! The moment Mecca walked out and saw the men in black, he was momentarily stunned. Across his eyes flashed fear and horror.

Griffith came out a moment later and heard the name being called out. Immediately his pupils dilated. His face paled ever so slightly.

"Damn the information we received! Didn’t they say everything was checked and cleared? How is it that Wilde is involved now?"He muttered angrily.

Two men dressed in red officer uniforms, donning white curly wigs fancied by noblemen were surrounded with nothing but the absence of the people who were once there. Obviously, the people earlier were forced to disband.

"Wilde, our sides have never went against each other…What do you mean by this? I don’t think we stole anything of yours?"Mecca calmed down, lowering his voice while making solid eye contact.

The scar on Wilde’s chin gave a sinister touch to his smile.

"I changed my name and filled up a couple of hundred storehouses full with goodies, it was under one of my aliases. Who would have thought that in the area of Iron Tank City, there existed someone who had the guts to mess around with my property? Griffith …tsk tsk, I heard that you have a pretty fine looking cousin sister…it has been some time since I wanted to do things to her."

"I warn you! If you dare lay a single hand on my cousin, I will seek the death of your entire family!!"Griffith jumped up abruptly, like a tiger who just got provoked. "More than a hundred storehouses! I obtained all of them and the numbers barely even surpasses forty!"

"Wilde, this is considered blackmail, you have to think this through carefully. Blackmailing a Quartermaster will mean persecution by the Dragon Guards."Mecca stood in front of Griffith, blocking him while speaking in a low voice.

"Blackmail? That is absolutely what I intend to do!!"

The black shadow flashed.

Bang!!!

Mecca regressed two steps, in front of him a giant green furred wolf whimpered. All of a sudden the giant wolf could not open its eyes; the rim of his eyes continually spilled blood.

"You are letting the Dragon Guards after me? Oh no I am so afraid, so so afraid!!" Wilde mocked a frightened expression, "Oh beloved Dragon Guard! I have committed blackmail, come after me quick!"

"How is that? Why isn’t there anyone after me?"

Shooh!

Again, the black shadow flashed. A Giant lizard who intended to ambush the three was beheaded once again, headless body tumbling unto the ground with a loud crash.

Even his cousin brother and another man distanced themselves from Wilde in mild fear.

Mecca and Griffith’s face turned ugly.

Wilde gave a terrifying and hideous laugh, turning back to normal. His gaze turned towards the right side of villa’s garden.

"Friend, if you are not going to appear I will finish it myself eh?"

"We each get half."

A deep voice traveled from the garden. A bald and eyebrow-less man stepped out, quietly standing beside the flower bed. It was Garen who was hiding.

"A little more than forty storehouses, I want the ones valued most."

Wilde looked around, flipped the back of his hand towards his back and lightly sprinkled some silver powder. The silver powder disappeared as it touched the ground.

"Friend, isn’t your appetite a little large?"He chuckled deeply. "The ones valued the most? That would be Wilde’s property, an infringement of private property is a crime, the beloved Dragon Guards will come and catch you~~"

"There’s less manpower on my side, I can’t carry much, which is why I only chose what I was capable of bringing along with me."Garen replied emotionlessly. "Of course, you are free to reject." His voice was laced with a hint of menace.

"Yo!"Wilde stared at Garen and paused for a moment, his playful gaze turned serious. It seems like he was unable to get the effect he intended for.

"This fella here is about to kick the butts of your entire family!"

With a loud bang, the dark shadow flashed and sent Griffith flying into the wood of the door.

"Griffith, did you think that making a few less enemies could kill you? You caused me to split such a huge part of my property! The hell, do you know this is a violation of the security of my private property!! HUH?!" He appeared in front of Griffith in the split of a second, grabbing a dazed Griffith by the collar and thundered loudly.

In another split of a second, Wilde disappeared from where he was, returning to his previous position.

"Wilde! Are you not afraid of Lord Cepha pursuing this matter!!"Mecca was completely unable to react at all; his good friend was beaten up right in front of his eyes. His whole face was ashen, ghastly pale. He hurries to protect his good friend who was behind him.

Wilde didn’t even cast a look at him. Instead, he focused his field of vision towards Garen who was by the flower beds. He was the only one among the hidden ones that he could never truly understand. From his body oozed the smell of blood, which only stuck on to the bodies of ruthless killers who had killed too many. This unique aura could only be faintly differentiated by those who were similar in nature, such as himself.

Not only that, the poison powder from earlier on did nothing. He was left completely puzzled.

Garen narrowed his eyes slightly, his face never revealing a hint of change. He was clear, this was Wilde’s way of showcasing what he was capable of.

His gaze briefly swept across the bloodied body of Griffith who was holding a piece scarf tightly against his forehead, silenced by the pounding he had earlier received.

"If you have no other opinion, we should get moving as soon as possible."

Wilde looked deeply into Garen’s eyes.

"I do not have any. Should we start on everything?"

"Yep."Garen answered, void of any emotion.

Their gazes centered upon Mecca.

"To hell with this! Let’s go!"Mecca’s face changed; he violently grabbed Griffith and leaped, a giant green wolf held on to them by their backs and flew into the building quickly, in effort to escape.

Suddenly, behind Wilde and Garen a dark shadow sprang out, effortlessly catching up to Mecca, Griffith and the Wolf.

Sheeeh!

Two shadows retracted in a moment, one of them turned into a Black lion right behind Wilde, while the other one behind Garen turned into a Giant croc.

Two of the giant monsters stood tall at around 5 to 6 feet near their masters, their gazes intertwined with fury, letting out threatening growls. Below each of their paws is a Giant green wolf.

"Secondary Totem!?" Wilde and Gren both recognized the level of their totems at the same time.

Black Lion and Giant Croc were both Form 2 Totems. What both of them did not expect was, both of these totems were their secondary totems and not their core totems.

Wilde immediately pegged his opposition as a master of the same level. Even his secondary totem was a ruthless Form 2 totem; his core would definitely far surpass the norm. He himself was developing a similar style of thought.

At the same time, he could somewhat feel as if the opponent had a totem hidden secretly. The thought of that filled him with dread.

"You choose first, friend."All of sudden he plastered a harmonious smile unto his face.

"Thanks."Garen nodded and walked into the Villa boldly.

The scene welcoming them was of two men lying on the ground in the hall.

Mecca held on to Griffith, both bloodied and battered, squatting near the fireplace.

Beside Mecca was a green wolf far larger than the ones before, but both sides of its body had chunks of flesh bitten off, leaving gaping wounds that looked as if it were sliced open with a sharp blade.

Garen briefly took a look; the left side was a deep wound created by the Giant Deep Swamp Croc, and it was evident that the wound was lighter than that of the one Wilde’s totem had inflicted.

One of the many powers of the Deep Swamp Croc: Explosive strike, the power it has is still incomparable to the power of the opposition’s Form 2 totem.

"I remember you."Mecca stared at Garen’s face, recalling the scene that unfolded in front of the storehouses earlier on. His eyes were so bright it was practically blinding.

"Any other last words?"Garen walked to stand in front of him.

"Lord Cepha will avenge me." Mecca said in a low voice.

Whoop!

Behind Garen a huge mouth shot out, breaking Mecca into two with just one bite.

Click – Blood splattered all over the ground as a result of the impact.

Garen just nonchalantly dodged a few times, and was able to avoid the blood completely; there was no trace of splattered blood on his body.

On the other hand, Griffith was scared silly. He was left sitting on the ground blankly.

Seeing him this way, Garen lost the desire of torturing him any further.

With a wave of a hand, he turned around and headed up towards the second floor. Downstairs, came the roar of Wilde’s lion; followed by a short distressed scream.

Garen looked down from the second floor – The lion was savoring Griffith’s head. As its tongue licked from time to time, bloodied pieces of flesh from the face were scraped off.

"This is so unhygienic." Garen pulled a hand towel over his nose. The body was back to its peak; unlike his previous life, it seemed more difficult to adapt to unpleasant smells.

"There are guys outside who want to take advantage of the situation. Half each, what do you think? Wilde gave a huge grin in the direction of Garen.

"We’ll kill as we see them, too lazy to specifically hunt them down."Garen answered emotionlessly, "Right, who on earth is this Cepha?"

"Someone from the Dragon Guards. However, I think he should focus on taking care of himself first, hehehe…"Wilde laughed in glee.

Behind him, Garen and the Deep Swamp Croc were searching each room one by one.

Although so, he was always on high alert. At this point, any sign of abnormal activities should never be detected by Wilde, or the consequences would be dire.

When it came to a form 2 totem users like Mecca, escape was an option if worse came to worse. However, when it came to an explosive totem user such as Wilde, it was not a good idea to cross him as his core totem is definitely not of the norm.

Truthfully when it came to Mecca’s death, if it were not for the cooperation of Wilde, it would have been nearly impossible to heavily wound the Giant Wolf totem in such a short span of time. Mecca had already given up resistance from the start, and chose to run away.

It was too bad he completely made the wrong decision.

The difference between them was, Wilde’s attack was just a random blow, whereas Garen’s Deep Swamp Croc attacked at full capacity, and even used its ability: Explosive strike. The difference was pretty significant.

If Mecca had decided to break through the mini barricade by attacking Garen, he would have found out that Garen was just posing as a strong user, strong in appearance but weak in reality. He was absolutely not of the same par as Wilde.

Garen had succeeded in using his tough demeanor, gained through large amounts of manslaughter in his previous life, in addition to his pre-preparation of a glowing disc and blue back lizard poison to counter the opponent’s poison. These 3 points had helped erected a image of an opponent with the same skill level in Wilde’s heart.

Lastly, Deep Swamp Croc had used its ability the moment it pounced and tore flesh apart. It was comparatively a little weaker than the damage Wilde caused. This was when he was fully aware the difference in ability was not a baseless presumption.

Garen knows, at this moment he needed to present a tough exterior, as any sign of weakness would add him to the list of Wilde’s many hunting targets.

Chapter 295: Resources 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

Slow steps were made on the corridor of the second floor.

Garen continuously pushed open all of the room doors he passed by, his gaze swept across each of them, never stepping in personally.

Very quickly, he reached the end where there was a room on the left –the doors were already open. From the gap through the door he could see many book shelves.

Garen pushed open the door and walked in; there were two steaming cups of black tea placed on the coffee table. The windowpanes were covered with a layer of dense mist.

He glanced around, his gaze eventually settling on a black leather box placed at the corner of the study.

Walking towards the box and squatting down, he lightly pinched –the place where the keyhole was immediately turned into fine powder. He opened the box.

Inside divided two sections, right and left.

On the left were stacks of notes and books, all of them covered in red hard covers. Garen picked them up and flipped them open – precise blueprint, detailed surgical procedures, as well as some illegible records of experiments. At the bottom of it all was a poetry compilation by Isaiah.

He placed the book back in and started looking at the section on the right.

The right side of the box were some silver bank notes, some broken diamond pieces and a silver brick. At the top was a stack of cheques weighed down by a silver brick.

Garen took it out to have a look. On top, 10 pieces of bank deposit bills with an amount of one million written on each.

"This fella is pretty poor huh…he is worse off than angel."Garen shakes his head. "No wonder there was a desire to take over the storehouses."

Garen simply took up a book of precision blueprint and flipping around.

It was pretty obvious this was a version used by totem users, at the top were plenty of requests with a difficulty level below that of a luminarist’s . Garen’s master level precision blueprint can easily achieve the standard required at the top.

"A totem user, is so much less complex than being a luminarist..this item should be that book of Mecca’s.

Totem users only needed to learn an entrance level precision blueprint, but when it came to technique and skill, they are so much more powerful than luminarists and forgers. Their types are highly skilled in the area of totem control and totem manipulation.

Totem users, forgers and luminarists; truth be told, have different preferences. Luminarists are to be considered moderate among them, and when it comes to strengths, totem users are skilled in technique while forgers have strengths in the area of forging and maintenance.

Garen flipped to the section where totem users needed to use activation tactics, and was momentarily stunned by how much more complicated activation tactics were in comparison to being a luminarist.

"Seems like no matter which type, there’s no such thing as a shortcut…only the area of difficulty differs."

Totem user’s precision blueprint required of a lower standard, but the price to pay was that its activation tactics were extremely difficult. Activation tactics included a lot of mathematical and physical knowledge; if it were not for Garen’s prior experiences, he wouldn’t have been able to grasp it so quickly.

Precision blueprints leaned towards the main attack’s stability and precision, while activation tactic focuses on the basis of instantaneous force and physical principles. The first focuses on accumulation, while the latter on adaptability. This also signifies the different development lines luminarists and totem users have.

Luminarists get stronger as time accumulated increases; the more knowledge they have, the more they can accumulate their wealth and ascend themselves.

On the other hand, totem users rely on adaptability and instantaneous force. They start off strong, but as development progresses, are substantially weaker to that of a luminarist.

"Still have no idea when it comes to forgers, but they should be leaning towards the direction of luminarists. From their name, it can be assumed that they completely given up going in the direction of battle, focusing instead on scientific research, specifically totem forging.

Garen closed the box and stood up. He left the Deep swamp croc as a doorkeeper and proceeded to continue the search leisurely.

There wasn’t anything else he could find, but Garen was not greedy – as he had found a box full of wealth, all of this had been worth it.

He simply took hold of the box with one hand and leaped off the window sill of the second floor.

Behind him, Wilde and the others were still searching the first floor, a few of the men obviously reaped some harvest. Wilde himself stood guard at the door of the entrance, in his mouth was a lit cigarette. Both of his eyes looked half open, as if he was on the verge of nodding off.

As he heard the leap, he opened his eyes to see Garen and grinned at him.

"Have a safe journey, I won’t walk you." He glanced at the box in Garen’s hands, not saying anything.

"I don’t have enough manpower for the items in the storehouses, this box will be enough for me."Garen grinned. The value of this box, besides its physical wealth, would be the notes and books in regards to tactics; there would surely be an array of tactics used by this villa. Just this fact alone was able to compensate the storehouse of young grains stolen earlier on. Its value is definitely worth more than 10 million.

Garen took the box and accelerated towards the distance, Giant deep swamp croc shadowed closely behind. He felt unfamiliar gazes behind his back but they disappeared as the distance increased.

Only then did he breathe a sigh of relief. His movements became lighter and more agile, and sped into the alley. Sticking close to the shadows, he ran in the direction of the suburbs.

Wooo~~~!!!

The long sound of a horn reverberated throughout Iron Tank City.

Garen halted his steps abruptly; he noticed that the sound of the horn was grievous and bleak.

He stood in the shadows of the valley, lifted his head up and looked at the skies outside the city.

An army of Giant Unihorn lizards looking like a bunch of grey clouds, were encircling a group of white Dragonhawks, leaving a small group of white gold Dragonhawks to defend tirelessly. They left behind white gold lines as they circled the air, continuously battling a Giant lizard every few seconds, without the time to take a breather.

At the start they were able to send down a Giant lizard whenever they came into contact with one. Now, they could only bump them out of the way with great difficulty.

There were too many grey clouds.

Garen picked up speed, nearing the city walls.

The ground was filled with the bodies of Giant unihorn lizards; these bodies carried the characteristics of silver totems, and will not turn completely into puddles of liquid silver.

Besides the Giant lizard bodies, countless human bodies were also weaved in between them; some were complete while others were not. Everywhere you’d look, you’d see huge long guns that were broken in half, a mixture of liquid silver, blood and gore flowing along the earth slowly, coloring the ground with shades of scarlet and silver.

Garen took caution and retrieved his Giant deep swamp croc as well as his sword, carefully navigating his way by sticking close to the corners of the wall under the shadows.

As he was nearing the outskirts of the city, a large number of buildings had already been wrecked and destroyed, leaving behind pieces of rubble and broken walls.

Ssssssssssss!!

A slightly red skinned Giant Unihorn lizard took alarmingly loud steps across the streets filled with bodies. Its thick tail was swinging back and forth, casually knocking away the pile of bodies around its circumference.

Garen tightened and crouched behind a triangular shaped ruin. He slowly spread his aura; in the sensory of his surroundings, small prickly dots that felt like hives pierced into his consciousness.

"At least a few hundred."Garen did a brief calculation in his heart, afraid to make any large moves.

He was fully aware that with the present situation, the only way to escape the first wave of chaos is to diffuse current strategies, hide away in various discreet areas and then start over from zero. In was during this crisis that Iron Tank City got rid of a few dysfunctional noble leaders, establishing a new and more efficient leadership team.

A more crucial point was, although Obscuro society had released these monsters as a main force of disruption in the world, realistically speaking, they remain incapable of controlling these failed living experiments. The only thing they could do is to prevent themselves from being attacked by these monsters.

In other words, these monsters are under no one’s orders. They were only scouring around hunting based on their primal needs. If it were not for the Dragon Guards’wanton massacre that angered these monsters, I am afraid it wouldn’t have blown up into such a large scale attack, involving the whole city.

Garen waited for the giant red lizard to pass, tapped his feet once, and transported himself into another cluster of shadows in the speed of lightning. He kept on going so, continuously closing in towards the outskirts of the city.

On his way he passed by a family of 3 who were hidden in a house, but he could only protect himself, unable to bring along anyone else. The ability the secret weapon has only provided speed and strength for one, making it unable to hide anyone else.

Whenever he encountered an opening during his journey, he would dash across quickly; whenever he did not, he would use small stones to divert the attention of the monsters, revealing an opening.

Soon, as he progressed forward like so, he finally reached the battle guild’s mission hall.

The entire building which the guild was situated at was completely destroyed, leaving only a piece of broken ruins where the walls once were. The surroundings were deserted and quiet, only a few giant lizards crawled by.

The cold wind whistled, blowing up a piece of thin wood board and causing it to roll around with a clear flapping sound.

Garen released the giant deep swamp croc, made sure to be constantly alert of his surroundings and searched around the ruins of the hall alone.

"Hey! Here!" A weak voice floated along the wind.

Garen followed the voice and looked over, some distance away near the lid of the waterway, stood a bald middle aged man who was waving his hand at him.

"The guild moved underground."

Garen nodded his head, retrieved Giant deep swamp croc, dragged along the box and ran towards his side. Seeing as he crawled into the waterway, he followed suit, shutting the lid after him.

Two of them followed the iron ladder and eventually reached the ground.

Following a narrow and dark passage they moved on; after a few minutes, drilled a hole on the ground that was about 40 to 50 meters. Only then did the bald man speak.

"Okay, here’s safe."He suddenly halted his steps and pulled open a metal door the height of a person from the right side of the walls. Inside, a bright yellow light spilled out.

"Go in from here, inside you’ll find the new Guild hall. Young chap, you were lucky you found me, the others would not have been so kind hearted."

Garen smiled and handed him a few silver rumbs.

"Thanks brother."

The bald man took it from him and returned the smile.

Both men walked in the brightly-lit tunnel, this tunnel extends in all directions, from time to time it would branch out into more tunnels. In them were others who walked out one after another, both male and female–it was apparent this was not the only entrance.

It’s the first time Garen had seen so many people since the catastrophe. Catching the gaze of a few others, it was evident that they felt the same.

"Quick! Save him quick!"All of a sudden from the right passage in front, bursts out a group of people; they carried a stretcher, on it laid a young man who was clutching his abdomen. Blood was pouring out continuously from in between his fingers. Gasping for breath, his face was ghostly pale and his forehead plastered with sweat. It seemed as if he was not going to make it.

The stretcher was dashed into a corner of the passage ahead.

"He is almost gone!! Anesthesia quick!! Start the surgery now!! Henry!!"

"I am here! Everything is prepared, quickly lift him in!""Be careful of your actions!""Garisith! Disinfect him now!"

A series of hurried voices came from the front.

"It’s the people from the sacrificial mission team, all three teams were badly injured." "Even the Dragon Guards suffered a huge loss, if Iron Tank’s tactical ring formation was not started up, it seemed as if even the inner part of the city would have been completely compromised."

"Thank goodness the war guild has an emergency underground place."

Garen heard someone say. He looked around and felt surrounded with a bunch of strangers, all of them wearing unfamiliar faces.

"Garen!" All of a sudden a voice came from the back.

Chapter 296: Resources 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

Garen looked back and saw fake-eye Thomas rushing over from behind.

"Thomas? It’s so great to see you alive!"

Garen gave him a fierce hug. This guy had given him much help over the years, a very well-informed person; the timing was splendid, he can now learn what the current situation is from him.

"Let’s go, take a rest inside."Thomas dragged Garen forward for a distance; in no time, after going through a small door, impressively, was a quest hall exactly like it was above ground. The only difference was that 7 or 8 people were scattered around; a woman with one arm skillfully served everyone food, drinks and alcohol.

The atmosphere was dull and heavy, there were lots of people with low spirits – some lying on the table drunken, while some were polishing their silver knives with a cold and detached expression on their faces.

Thomas familiarly dragged Garen to a corner to sit down.

The outskirts of the city had been damaged, now our war guild base is the logistic point for our frontlines. What do you have in mind?" Thomas rushed to enquire as soon as he sat down."I would suggest you to go straight to the inner part of the city; the only ones brave enough to be left behind are masters. I am planning to go straight to the inner part of the city to participate in defense tasks, you should follow me."

"I have my own plans, no worries." Garen smiled,"What is the current situation in the city?"

"The Dragon Guards collapsed, if it were not for Grand Duke who came after to combat the monsters, I am afraid not one would have lived to defend the inner city." Thomas explained simply,"Now, half of those in the city have perished, leaving only a small portion of residents living in the inner city to avoid massacre. Those from the outskirts and suburbs have pretty much all perished. Perhaps there remains few who were hidden, but the numbers are definitely not large."

"How about the other places?"

"I have no idea, according to the guild’s last contact with foreign guilds which was the day before yesterday, the current skies have been completely saturated and blocked by the monsters. Guilds of different locations are being isolated." Thomas lowered his voice, " The heads of the guild seemed a little off."

" How about battle resources? It should be priced lower right?" Garen asked after thinking for a moment.

"Definitely, as the number of people decreased, the amount of people capable of using totems for battle is not enough. There is an oversupply, a lot of items have decreased in price.

Garen suddenly noticed his motive, it was true that he needed to stick to a group at this crucial time.

"I have companions, no worries." He shakes his head to refuse. "Let me settle my box first, some items valued higher when sold, will be given in exchange instead. Nothing is more important than life. Right?"

"No problem, look for me here when you are free, I usually hang around during noon."Thomas didn’t insist further and agreed with ease. During these times an extra friend meant an extra security blanket.

Garen dragged the box towards the counter in the hall.

He walked to the left window and knocked.

The girl inside went blank for a moment, visibly downcast shortly after.

"Sorry, this afternoon Mr. Jason had already…"

Jason’s heart sank. the middle aged man worked well with him when he was around, he’d have never thought he’d be gone so soon.

"How much are war shackles and a war hall? He asked in a low voice.

"20 million for all, if resources were used in exchange, even better."The girl snapped out of her daze and replied.

Garen placed the box on the counter, opened it and took out the books and notes. He then proceeded to put money and precious items such as diamonds and silver blocks through the window.

"Mind estimating the value for me?

"Alright." The girl took over the items and skillfully separated them into similar groups.

The estimation was soon given.

"Altogether 36 million or so, do you want me to record it in your badge or?"

"Give me a set of war shackles instead, keep the remaining in the badge."

"Okay, please wait for a moment."The girl rarely encountered war shackle related transactions, and was a little unfamiliar with it. She decided to seek help from people behind.

After Garen waited for a short while, a tall and slender young man walked out. In his hands was a silver cylinder.

"May I ask if it’s you who wanted war shackles?" He walked to the counter, replacing the girl’s position.

"Yes, is there a problem?"

What type of war shackles do you need? A blank one, or one with effects?"The young man solemnly asked. "A blank one." Garen answered concisely.

"In this case you would want to add a permanent tactic. Here we have two types of permanent tactic that can be added on, you should consider it. One deepens your damage, tearing the wound in a way that makes it harder to heal. The other is a paralytic toxin, a layer coated on totems would slightly interfere with the enemy’s attack.

"There’s no need, we have other considerations." Garen rejects him. These two permanent tactics are pretty useless. The guild would not bring out anything useful for sale, but would have taken it for themselves instead.

"It’s alright then." The young man quickly drew a tactic symbol on the silver cylinder, the symbol glowed red and vanished, disappearing into the surface of the cylinder. He then passed it to Gren.""Please take this, this is your blank shackle. This shackle is of the lowest level, with only two effects inset. Although so, you could choose to upgrade through a forger in the future; a high leveled forger is capable of transferring an inset permanent tactic into a new shackle. Of course, only forgers of our guild have the technique for it."

"Thank you." Garen took over the cylinder and noticed all of a sudden around him, greedy glances headed his way.

He looked back and glanced around, not minding a bit.

He opened the cylinder straight, plucking out a silver V shaped arrow from inside, it was a like a thin sheet of metal. The surface has an abnormal shine to it, only tilting towards the light showed a layer of colored light swirling in the internal alchemy.

Garen checked it in detail, and pressed the metal sheet into his left arm.

Ssssss…

The metal sheet accompanied by a sizzling sound melted into Garen’s skin. After a cloud of green smoke, it looked like a birthmark gotten since birth, completely natural. There was nothing that gave it away to being unnatural.

Under Garen’s field of vision, a horizontal bar appeared. Behind it were two pink boxes.

"War shackle: 2 permanent tactics can be added. Master the forger’s technique, and its ability will level up.

Effect: Could be used to connect companions, allowing both to benefit from the effect of Permanent tactics. As to how much effect one benefits, it can be controlled by the shackle’s owner."

"This is the one." Garen nodded his head in satisfaction. He had used up the War shackle without any hesitation, and the greedy glances started to mind their own business. A used War shackle is not of much value.

"Let’s see if it is possible to evolve the core totem." Garen looked at the potential points in the potential bar.

Killing Mecca, a Form 2 totem user, had increased his potential points to 1516%.

"15 points, we can try now."

Till now, he had reached the first stage of his ultimate goal –he managed to get his hands on the core totem. After this, the key would be combining potential points with Gothic and the rest.

The only thing is, Gothic had definitely participated in the defense tasks, and was bound to showcase jaw dropping abilities, attracting the attention of the Grand Duke. To follow in this footsteps of such genius…

Thomas disappeared again, so Garen went back to the hall alone to find a seat. If Angel did not live, he was planning to find a few people to establish a new team.

"Aska is here.."

"Resta as well."

Someone seated at the door muttered.

Not long after, two people emerged from the tunnel. One was in front of the other – The one leading had red hair, a good looking youth; his outfit was in a state, but he was unhurt.

"Aska, here."A red headed girl waved her hand from across the hall.

Garen recognized him. He was popularly known as a genius among the guild members – Aska Byzantium. According to popular belief, the moment he lighted up a totem, he shared the innate gift of black panthers –its speed. He then continuously controlled 3 different totems, benefiting from all 3 of them their dissimilar unique abilities.

Much earlier on, his second totem evolved into Form 2. He was an innately talented and excellent guy. His natural ability is the rare ability to power share, capable of casting the totem’s power unto himself; this ability helps the totem user to adapt to different situations easily. For example using the Fire Wolf’s fireball power, the polar bear’s ice attack and more.

Garen’s gaze falled upon the person behind Aska.

Resta, also a new found genius with natural golden curls. His ability is hardening. He can prepare all his totems with a tougher skin, protecting them from huge damage. He had also used a Form 1 totem to kill a Form 2 totem alive. Only 19 this year, Aska and him belonged to the Genius level.

But Resta was not someone of the War Guild, but a nobleman from the city, or so he heard.

Garen retracted his gaze.

He was not a genius, in comparison to these people, his only strength was his potential points. Although this ability grows stronger as development continues, in its earlier stages, its incomparable to these insane talents.

He was all in all one of a normal rank. His military strengths from his previous life was not obvious here.

Aska and Resta walked together towards the red haired lady at the corner, they were from the same circle; Resta obviously a friend of Aska. These people are either geniuses or elite machines. Their circle and other circles are of two separate worlds. In a small place such as Iron Tank City, they have even become the main force fighting against the monsters.

Garen sat on his seat, quietly waiting. If Angel did not die, she would have made the same decision as he did. During these times, the only way to be safe is to stick to a group, else they would be the object of bullying.

Now, Garen could possibly defeat a Form 2 totem user with great difficulty, but was definitely incapable of facing off two. He barely passed off as talented in the guild’s hierarchy.

Not long after, in the tunnel where many come in and go out from, a black robed lady walked in quickly. It was Angle. He left shadow was wrapped with thick bandage, blood stains were visible. As she saw Garen, she walked over and sat on the opposite side of him.

Chapter 297: Evolution 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

Although the two didn’t exactly trust each other, there wasn’t any conflict of interest, and they were both the same type of person. Garen had his pride as a member of the strong, and wouldn’t allow himself to find a weakling as a companion. He needed someone who could stand independently, a strong fighter who would not give up easily regardless of the dangers faced. He needed someone who could help him when needed, and not a weakling who would constantly need his help for every little thing.

Garen didn’t have much of an advantage here on this world. Compared to those prodigies, he only had his potential points to possibly bring him to the peak. But he had his pride, and the strong would remain strong however much their environments changed. It was just a matter of time accumulation.

Similarly, Angel had the same opinion, someone of the same level who could defeat her in direct confrontation, and the same type of person as she was. That made her acknowledge Garen all the more.

"I thought you died." She learned her back on the chair, wiping away the sweat on her forehead.

"I won’t die before you do." Garen smiled. "What’s wrong with you? Your shoulder."

"I was ambushed, someone tried to take my stuff. I got two of them, hehe." Angel licked her lips, smiling cruelly.

"I bought the War Chain, add yourself in for now." Garen stretched out his left arm, revealing that silver-white V-shaped arrow.

Angel wasn’t surprised either, as she reached out her hand and pressed down on the arrow.

Garen instantly saw Angel’s icon appear in the pane for the War Chain at the bottom of his vision. He seemed to be able to chase her out whenever he wanted to.

Bringing his gaze back, he said calmly,

"Right now there isn’t any effect at all. Do you have anything to contribute?"

"Do you think that’s possible? I may be good, but even if I’m good, I still haven’t reached Prodigy-level yet." Angel rolled her eyes at him.

"Oh yeah, you’ve met Prodigy-level totem users, right? Tell me what’s so different about them," Garen asked quietly.

"Prodigy-level? The difference between prodigies and the other people is very simple. The biggest difference is, it’s very hard for you to beat them," Angel said, reminiscing. "If you say our talent is at a human level, then they’re all inhuman. I know a few of their talents, it’s extremely over-powered."

"For example?" Garen was instantly interested.

"Ability sharing, that’s the one everyone knows about. If someone can have a Form 3 totem, or even the very peak, a Form 4 Aberration. When that happens, the totem user is the strongest, while the totem is just a tool to provide power. Totem users at the level are humanoid monsters." Angel sighed. "We can forget about that."

Garen can imagine how terrifying a totem user like that would be. Their defense would be impenetrable, even stronger than totems. And they had the power of totems too, which would basically make them moving fortresses.

"And then?"

"In truth, ability sharing can be divided into types. Some are suitable for wolves, others suitable for leopard, and yet others bears. If they used another type, it wouldn’t have that effect. Besides that, the other talent I heard of would be totem fusion. A few types of totems fused together have a certain chance of becoming a new totem, this is yet another ridiculously over-powered ability. Many of the new mutated totems were created when these guys messed around like that, such as the White Dragonhawk. And then there are those strengthening types, strengthening speed, power, defense, vitality - four in total. These are the most basic Prodigy talents. They’re slightly weaker than the previous two."

"In other words, there are three types, ability sharing, ability strengthening, and totem fusion, right?" Garen concluded.

"That’s right. Why are you suddenly asking." Angel was slightly curious.

"I just wanted to really know what level these Prodigies are at." Garen sighed.

"Don’t compare yourself to them, a lot of these Prodigy totem users evolve extremely quickly. They have different factions supporting them, it would be hard for them not to evolve quickly. Their rate of growth is far beyond normal people," Angel said helplessly. She glanced at Resta, Aska and the others nearby. "See Aska over there? He only took five months from the moment he lit and activated a totem to evolving his second Form 2 totem. His talent is ability sharing with the leopard totem, so I’ve been paying attention to him these past few days, because I use a leopard too."

"Five months…" Garen was rather speechless, only then did he understand how terrifying these Prodigies were. If he hadn’t gotten the Derivator, he would still barely be a Form One totem user now. Meanwhile the other guy had gotten his second Form Two totem step by step, and Garen still didn’t know what other trump cards he might have in addition to his ability to share a totem’s power.

"I need to hurry up and upgrade my core totem…" Garen decided to hurry up and hunt the Unihorn Lizard, and upgrade the Black-Striped White Tiger as soon as possible.

His gaze fell on the totem pane.

‘Black-Striped White Tiger: First Form Totem, upgradable. Probability of successful evolution: 11%. Potential point cost: 700%.

Abilities: Tail Whip, Puncturing Crunch.’

"I’ll just go with it!" He clenched his teeth, chatting idly with Angel on one hand, while his gaze fell on the Black-Striped White Tiger’s icon.

After three seconds, his potential points gave a jolt, and seven points disappeared in an instant, becoming 816%.

The Black-Striped White Tiger’s icon shook a little, and blurred for a moment, then became clear again, before growing still.

Garen waited for half a beat, but nothing else happened. Finally, he understood with painful regret, that the evolution had failed.

"11% chance… it’s too low…" He wiped his face, that was all his accumulated savings over all this time. "Even if I try again, the result will probably be the same. With chances like that, two tries are too few. Looks like I’ll still need to focus on upgrading one totem, and then hunt for potential points en masse."

He decided, his gaze falling onto the other totems.

Primitive totems: Neon Butterfly, Black-Striped White Tiger.

Silver totems: Howling Wererabbit (Form 2), Blue back Lizard, Grey-feathered Hawk, Deep Swamp Croc (Form 2).

Garen’s gaze fell on the Deep Swamp Croc.

‘Deep Swamp Croc: Short-Tailed Croc Form 2, Second Form Creature Totem. Upgradable, Probability of successful evolution: 24%. Potential point cost: 500%.

Abilities: Explosive Strike, Iron Hide, Parasitism.’

"Probability 24… it’s too low… I’ll give it a shot." His gaze fell on the Deep Swamp Croc, three seconds later.

The Croc’s icon gave a sudden shudder, and then became clear again. It didn’t move after that.

Smack!

Garen couldn’t help but smack his palm onto the table.

Now he understood why there were so few Form Three totems. This was basically burning money and resources. He was still okay because he had his potential points, but if he was taking the conventional route, to raise enough resources just once would require several tens of millions. After burning that kind of money a few times, many people went bankrupt. A few more times, and you could lose up to a billion.

"What’s wrong with you?"

"N-nothing, I just suddenly thought of something unpleasant." Garen resisted the rage burning within, and replied softly.

"I was talking about someone who wanted to take my things, I’m guessing her identity might be a bit troublesome. It should be…" Her question satisfied, Angel continued talking. She was completely unaware that Garen was currently distracted.

Garen finally looked at the potential points, 316%.

"I have only 3 points left, looks like I must look at the others." He hesitated, and his gaze instantly fell on the other Form Two, the Howling Wererabbit.

‘Howling Wererabbit: Iron Rabbit Form 2, Second Form Creature Totem. Upgradable, Probability of successful evolution: 54%. Potential point cost: 300%.

Abilities: Explosive Stomp, Plant Exterminator (Voracious Eater).’

"This one has a probability of 54, that’s considered very high. But this rabbit hasn’t reacted much up till now, I don’t know what its overall condition is like." Garen felt for the Howling Wererabbit’s movements. From the other end of his spiritual connection, he felt a sense of weakness, as though it was hurt.

"Forget it, it’s too far away, I don’t dare to go out and look for it. Even if I did evolve it, it would still be outside and surrounded." Garen’s gaze finally fell on the Blue back Lizard he had bought earlier. The Blue back Lizard’s poison and the Neon Butterfly had helped him a ton. Back then he bought three of them experimentally, but perhaps he could see how this type of lizard would change when evolved to Form Two.

He looked at the last three potential points, and felt for the condition over at the Blue back Lizard. It was still normal.

He had hidden the three Blue back Lizard at his residence outside the city. There were few people there, and it seemed that the Silver Totems didn’t attract Unihorn Lizards to attack either, instead making them treat the totems as part of their own.

"After a bit, I’ll go back and start attempting the evolution." Garen decided, and brought his gaze back to Angel opposite him. She was just reaching the important part.

"...In the end one managed to escape. I can guarantee that she’s hiding in some corner right now, observing me. She must have seen that we were talking. You be careful now, don’t get seduced and lose your life." Angel asked for a cup of black tea, and sipped at it carefully."

"When I kill someone, I don’t care whether they’re pretty or not," Garen smiled. "What level are you at now? Any news about the Legacy?"

"If a Legacy was so simple, would I still be a fugitive for so long?" Angel shook her head. "The only opportunity would be to join a guild or a party. I don’t have that qualification, but you do. I’m waiting for your promise, you know."

"This is what I have to contribute, when the time comes it’ll be part of the the War Guild’s shared resources." Garen thought it over, "Actually, I’m not very clear about the Guild’s structure."

He paused, and dipped his finger into the black tea, writing on the table,

"The Guild is controlled by the War Parliament, which consists of nobles and officials. As members of parliament, they can elect a president to oversee the guild’s affairs, as well directly appoint a Defense Minister.

The Vice President and the other ministers below are all appointed by the president. We’re now in a crisis, so it’ll probably be under the full control of the president and the other main ministers." Garen drew three dots, from top to bottom, to represent the three main powers.

Angel nodded, "I asked around before. The branch president, the defense minister, and the incumbent captain of the Headquarters’ Cleansing Division. These are the three factions in the Guild now, all three of them have complete knowledge of the legacy. That Aska for one is from the Cleansing Division."

"How powerful…" Garen nodded. "It’s too bad Jason, who was quite close to me, died. Otherwise, he was coincidentally part of the defense minister’s faction, and we could have went to him. They need manpower right now, so they would surely all be looking for the scattered firepower. But whether I join or not, right now I need a reason." He looked at Angel.

Angel knew what he was talking about. "Didn’t you swear to start a meritocratic organization? Are you giving up now?"

"To be precise, I’m not trying to up. I’m trying to get something, so I need to contribute something in return. It’s the same for both of us. If I contribute but you earn, that’s not fair to me," Garen replied simply.

"Simply put, we need a fixed long-term alliance. Is that what you’re trying to say?" Angel understood, leaning on the back of the chair as she heaved a sigh of relief. "You want the War Chain’s cover for core totems, right? I’ll give it to you."

"As long as you agree."

Only he could see the condition of members in the War Chain, but before Angel hadn’t given him the right to cover her core totem, which meant she didn’t add her core totem into the War Chain.

And now, after Angel agreed, an icon of a black panther slowly appeared behind Angel’s icon at the bottom of Garen’s field of vision.

‘Large Black Panther (brink of evolution): Angel’s core totem, sharing state: 0.’

Chapter 298: Evolution 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

Garen nodded, satisfied. Now that this Large Black Panther on the brink of evolution was connected to the War Chain, Angel would be reluctant to give up the Large Black Panther she had raised for so long even if she wanted to leave on her own. This way, their relationship was even more secure.

Garen briefly told Angel about what he knew about raising totems. When it came to skills on raising leopard-type totems, however, he didn’t have much to say. This required more detailed raising knowledge. Based on Aska, they were sure the War Guild in War Tank City had this sort of information.

The two of them sat in a corner, and soon enough, that one-armed waitress girl walked up to Garen’s table, clearing the table for them.

"Mr Garen, Mr Caddy asks if you’re willing to take Mr Jason’s position," she suddenly asked Garen softly. "If you are, you can go talk to Miss Mina at the counter."

There it was!

This was what Garen was waiting for. At a time like this, the Guild would never let go of any firepower that they might recruit. This Mr Caddy was actually part of the president’s faction.

Thomas’ invitation from before was very likely to have come from another faction, but Garen had rejected him.

He exchanged a glance with Angel, and stood up. Walking towards the counter, he figured his relationship with Jason was still pretty decent, so joining them wasn’t a bad path to take.

After the stout man buying medicines in front left, Garen walked to the counter, and rapped the tabletop.

"Come with me." The girl inside, Mina, glanced at him and smiled, then pulled open a small door from the left to allow Garen in.

Another young man took her place at the counter.

The two of them entered from a small door on the left, one after the other. Beyond the door there was a sizable tea room, with yellow wooden floors and walls, as well as similarly-hued tables, chairs, and lighting.

A middle-aged man with a goatie was writing something on his desk. Upon hearing footsteps, he lifted his head to lok over.

"You’ve come." He stood up and welcomed Garen, reaching out his hand to shake Garen’s.

"Hi, I’m Caddy. Right now I’m part of the Fourth Division, under the respected branch president. It’s both our fortunes that you would choose our side."

This person was all smiles, and looked very friendly.

"You’re too kind."

Garen shook hands with him, and the two of them sat at the table facing each other.

"Then, let’s discuss the benefits of joining us." Caddy pulled a sheet of paper out of the stack of documents on the table, and flicked it to make a crisp sound. "The conditions we can give you are very simple. Firstly: A sufficiently safe base, to protect all our assets from infiltration. Secondly: You can buy low grade Legacy knowledge. Of course, if you need a Form 2, that would require higher authority and enough money. Thirdly: We’ll give you prior access to better medicines, and higher quality equipment as well as facilities. Everyone can claim basic insurance rations every week: one set of medicine for external injuries, one set of medicine for stemming internal bleeding, one single-use defense tactic. One set of standardized nutrients. These are all free."

"Not bad at all. Tell me about my responsibilities." Garen knew that three sides had more or less the same conditions right now, at the most it would a difference in which resource they had more of, and would then emphasize.

"You only have two responsibilities." Caddy was very satisfied with Garen’s decisiveness. "Lord Engra has two divisions under his influence right now. I’m directly under the Discipline Division, and the other is the Self-defense Division. No matter which one you join, your responsibilities are, One: obey any urgent summons, and obey all rational orders. Two: complete your tasks and duties as your position requires."

Garen mused for a while, and started asking about the differences between working at the two divisions. The two of them discussed it for more than half an hour, and then Mina brought in the next person. Only then did Garen rise to leave.

Next would be his consideration on whether or not to join them, and their inspection of his identity and qualifications.

Upon leaving the room, the atmosphere in the Guild Quest Hall had gotten even rowdier. The hall was the size of a basketball court, and seated over a hundred people. There were people squeezed up to each other, making the place seem congested as there was a chaos of noise. The smell of blood mixed with the stench of sweat, wafting through the air.

Garen frowned.

His gaze swept over the hall, and realized that Angel had left. Thomas, Aska and the others were gone too, only unfamiliar faces remaining in the large hall.

Some young men and women dressed in black armor would occasionally go in and out of the entrance to the corridor, streaming through the hall.

These people in black armor walked through the hall and directly entered another corridor in the right, without even looking at the others in the hall.

Garen went out of the hall, and saw Angel in the corridor, leaning on a while.

"So, how?"

"Waiting for the news," Garen replied. "I have something to do, I’ll need to go back ahead. Are you alright on your own?" He could feel some gazes on Angel, sometimes there and sometimes not.

"It’s fine, just some punks with a death wish." Angel smiled.

Garen nodded and cast her out of his mind, walking straight down the corridor. After taking some more turns, he followed the wide network of underground tunnels and was soon back at the entrance where he had come in.

He left the tunnel exit, closed the cover behind him, and was back at the metal ladder that led into the sewers. With a light tap of his foot, he catapulted his body up to the very top of the ladder. Reaching out his hand to push up the metal cover, he tried his best not to make any noise.

Garen poked out his head, and looked out.

The sky was dark out, and there was the cooing of insects. It was all quiet, but there was the sound of footsteps in the distance.

Garen quietly crawled out of the well cover, and closed it behind him, standing in the debris of the Guild Hall as he looked around.

Everything was in ruins about him, and he could vaguely see some figures looting for things by the pile of corpses in the shadows.

Garen looked towards the shadow of a collapsed wall on his right. In the darkness, a huge piece of charred wood moved, and then abruptly opened its eyes. It was actually a Deep Swamp Croc in hiding.

"I’ll make a trip back, and then start a full-on hunt for the Unihorn Lizard, to rack up some potential points." Garen made the arrangements inwardly, and let the Deep Swamp Croc clear the way. He followed behind it, carefully vigilant of his surroundings.

The platinum-colored aura spread open soundlessly, stretching up to a hundred meters in radius.

Garen moved quickly, following outside the damaged city walls. Most of the buildings both inside and outside the city walls had been knocked down and collapsed.

After proceeding for a certain distance, in the distance ahead, a black silhouette darted out of a small ruined building. The shadow’s face met Garen’s at a distance, and both of them stopped.

Garen froze in his tracks, watching the other person dart into yet another clump of shadows, leaving quickly towards the right. Only then did he continue progressing.

The small area he lived in was towards the right on the outside of the city wall, and was surrounded by a smattering of other suburbs. There was even a small-scale produce market. That person had left in the direction of the market.

He didn’t linger long, going through the ruins of this area and quickly turning a few more corners before he saw his own suburban house up ahead.

It was all quiet in the suburbs, dead quiet, without any sound whatsoever.

Garen stuck close to shadow of the houses near the wall, soundlessly approaching the suburbs.

The whole suburban area was empty. This place was very far from the city, and barely anyone lived here. Most of the houses weren’t damaged. They just looked lonely and dead.

Garen carefully walked over, taking the pebbled path that led through the area. The white houses on both sides were eerily quiet, the windows like so many black holes, deep and dark.

Wah!

Suddenly there was a sound like a child’s crying in Garen’s ear. The noise was messy and grating, unusually piercing on the ears.

A wave of dizziness overcame him, and his reactions were instantly delayed by a beat. Then he saw the Deep Swamp Croc in front of him wave its tail to the left.

Bam!

A red shadow flew over like a shot, and rammed hard into the Deep Swamp Croc’s tail, making a dull sound.

The Deep Swamp Croc made a low roar, and was actually pushed back by two steps. That red shadow also flew backwards, tumbling onto the lawn of a villa on the left and revealing its shape.

Garen took a sharp intake of breath. The red shadow was a baby with reddish-purple skin, completely naked and with a mouth full of sharp, serrated black teeth. One of its eyes was spotted with furry blue mould, while the other had long since dried out.

"This is… Obscuro’s human experiments?!" Garen’s expression turned slightly tortured.

He willed the Deep Swamp Croc to wind around the dead baby, as he walked around and ran towards his own villa.

Behind him, the sound of the baby’s cries and the Croc’s roars never stopped.

He quickly arrived at the center of the suburbs, where it was unusually clean. Ahead of him, on the left, some rats were surrounding a human arm and chewing away at it. Hearing footsteps, these rats immediately raised their heads, revealing their ferocious red eyes.

Squeak-squeak-squeak!

The red-eyed rats actually pounced at Garen like bugs.

"These Unihorn Lizards actually brought viruses with them?" Garen’s expression became unpleasant. He was suddenly rather worried about his teacher, Emin, who was far away, as well as his cousin and Vanderman. Although Vanderman was only this body’s cheap father, but they had still spent a long time together, and the man’s concern for him was absolutely sincere.

He lightly jolted his foot, and a translucent circle of air spread open with a whoomph. The air went past the red-eyed rats, and the group of rats instantly fell to the ground, motionless.

Garen turned around and leapt over his own fence, took out the key and opened the door, then closed it behind him. The hall on the first floor was pitch-black, and some black shadows quickly pounced onto him.

Three Grey-feathered Hawks flew nimbly in circles around him, and three Blue Back Lizards climbed onto Garen’s feet, acting cuddly.

"Let me try evolving the Grey-feathered Hawk first." Garen walked to the sofa and sat down. Without lighting the lamp, he raised his right arm, and let a Grey-feathered Hawk perch on his arm.

A Grey-feathered Hawk leapt up and landed on Garen’s arm. Its beak was slightly longer compared to the other two, and its body slightly larger. When it stood, it was roughly a third of a person in height.

"It’ll be you, then." Garen touched this Grey-feathered Hawk’s head, his gaze falling onto this Grey-feathered Hawk’s icon.

Three seconds later.

His potential points leapt to 16%. Three potential points vanished.

And this Grey-feathered Hawk’s icon gave a jolt, slowly becoming blur.

Ba-thump, ba-thump…

The Grey-feathered Hawk flapped its wings, and took flight.

Its wings were growing longer, turning black, its body rapidly growing larger, expanding. Its two claws became sharper.

Squawk!!

At a speed that can be seen with the naked eye, this Grey-feathered Hawk grew from less than a meter to two whole meters. Even more strangely, its head actually rapidly grew, and tiny sharp teeth appeared in its sharp yellow beak. There was even a bright red sarcoma on his head, beating rhythmically like a heart.

In the dozen or seconds, this Grey-feathered Hawk directly went from a hawk into a huge, ferocious, monster bird. Standing on the floor of the hall, it furled up its wings, even taller than Garen was now.

Garen looked at the newly-changed icon of the Grey-feathered Hawk at the bottom of his vision.

Chapter 299: Ambush 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

‘Resonance Hawk (named according to ability): Second form of Grey-feathered Hawk, Form 2 evolution totem. Not upgradable.

Ability: Resonance Burst (the sarcoma on its head can induce the enemy’s heart to beat with it, increasing the burden on its heartbeat, and in extreme cases make it burst, causing death. Natural strength (it is very powerful)’

"Resonance Hawk?"

Garen closely observed the sarcoma on the Hawk’s head. The growth beat non-stop like a heart. He reached out his hand to touch it,, and felt that it was warm and with a sturdy quality like rubber. It didn’t feel as thin as it looked. When he sniffed it, he smelled the odor of eggs.

He straightened up and took a customary glance at the other Silver Totems around him. The other two Grey-feathered Hawks and the Blue Back Lizards were cowering in a corner, shivering, frightened away by the Resonance Hawk’s presence.

He swept the corners of the hall with his gaze. There was a pile of leftover bones there, a creature had probably be brought in here by these little pets and eaten up.

Garen walked up to the store room and used his key to open the door. Inside, there were many crates of different foods and drinks.

He had prepared these in advance, supplies enough for ten people to survive on for a year. This was also the reason he left his pets here.

Opening one of the boxes, he took out a hard loaf of young grain bread. This long piece of bread was extremely sturdy, and was nearly as hard as a baseball bat. Just a little bit would be enough to keep someone full for a day.

He pinched off a bit and stuffed it straight into his mouth. There was instantly a crunchy crackly sound of chewing, as though he was chewing wood. He then took a pre-filled bottle of clean water, twisting off the cap and chugging it down.

He then lifted the whole box of supplies and walked out of the storage room, closing the door behind him and returning to the hall on the first floor.

After putting the box onto the floor next to the sofa, he sat down on the sofa. Wiped his face with his hands.

He hadn’t had a proper chance to catch his breath all this time, so now that he finally had time to rest a little, Garen just sat on the sofa, and before he knew it he was lying down and fell asleep.

His consciousness a blur, he didn’t know how long had passed when Garen suddenly awoke from the darkness. There was the sound of the Deep Swamp Croc roaring from the yard outside, together with the sharp piercing sobs of a baby.

He sat up in an instant, sensing two more little dots in his detection that were moving together next to the Deep Swamp Croc.

"Could it be a parasite?" He stood up, feeling his brain was still slightly fuzzy, and massaged his temples. "After coming here, I wonder if I had ever completely relaxed and rested even once… It sure feels good."

As he sighed, he walked to the window and looked out.

In the yard of the villa outside the window, the Deep Swamp Croc just happened to be biting down on a dead baby, and then swallowed it down with a few cracking bites. It was surrounded by two black beetles, about half a person tall.

The beetles were glistening bright, their outer shells reflecting light like a mirror under the moonshine. Their heads didn’t have eyes or noses, but a large mouth full of sharp teeth, with a white snake’s tongue poking out from it intermittently.

They were just like two round balls. They pushed their bodies forward, letting their mouths chomp down on flesh and blood, pulling the food into their stomachs.

The two parasites actually worked together to take down a dead baby, their fighting power was formidable.

"So those are the Deep Swamp Croc’s parasites?" Garen carefully felt the Croc, and instantly discovered the minute connections between the Croc and the beetles.

Under the moonlight, Garen swept his gaze over the front yard.

The yard’s neat and orderly grass had been utterly destroyed, and only yellow dirt and dark red blood stains remained. The fencing around the yard had also been knocked over and damaged.

A few red-eyed rats would occasionally scuttle across the main road of the suburbs outside, and a couple of Unihorn Lizards also dropped down slowly, crawling over the streets. The two Lizards saw the Deep Swamp Croc and the parasites but didn’t attack them, treating them as one of their own, ignoring them and slowly passing by the front of the villa.

Garen let down the curtain, and ducked into the darkness of the villa.

Scree!!

There was occasionally the strange cry of the Unihorn Lizards from outside, as he hid alone in the villa, going up to the second floor by following the stairs.

After entering the study, he pulled out Angel’s little notebooks from his pocket.

He put the three pale yellow notebooks and lightly drew the curtains, using the matches on the table to light the oil lamp. Suddenly, the whole study was illuminated.

He was very confident in the safety of the villa. The Deep Swamp Croc was patrolling outside, together with its two parasites. Now this was number three.

He had observed a little just now, and concluded that the parasites were equal to a Form One totem, and a rather fiercer Form One totem at that. It was just slightly weaker than a Unihorn Lizard, and already made a decent guard.

"The Deep Swamp Croc can produce three a day at most, but without a suitable parasite, the parasitism would not work so easily. While I’m studying tactics, I might as well have it leave one parasite to watch the house, and take one out myself for hunting. That way it can be used as food, and it can catch other parasites."

Garen sat down, and gave the Deep Swamp Croc the order to go hunting on its own with the largest parasite.

The Croc in the villa’s yard instantly crawled out of the pitch black corner and soundlessly left the villa, crawling into the distance, followed by a small beetle behind it.

"Remember not to hurt anyone." Garen added an order. That was the benefit of Silver Totems, they had a specific level of simple intelligence, and could act on their own away from the main body. There was no need to worry about their loyalty either, as he could monitor their movements at all times, and control their lives at his will.

"Resonance Hawk, go stand watch." Garen gave the large hawk in the villa other orders.

Soundlessly, the hawk with a height of two to three meters and a wingspan of four to five meters took flight from the yard, landing on top of the villa before quietly furling its wings to perch there. The large hawk eyes swept the surroundings with a radius of several hundred meters at all times.

The two Grey-feathered Hawks followed it up there, and started to bring twigs and pieces of tree bark to build a nest on the roof. The Resonance Hawk, on the other hand, sprawled on the roof lazily, ordering its lackeys to build it a nest.

Garen decided to chase the three Blue Back Lizards out as well, so that they could patrol the yard at all times. He let them eat and stay outside, lest they stink up the inside of the villa with their unbearable odor.

"It’s too bad their intelligence is still too low, and they don’t know how to clean up." Garen sighed and shook his head, thinking that scattering his little pets around the villa would greatly increase its safety measures. In these almost apocalyptic times, he had a sense of safety.

"Right now, even Iron Tank City isn’t as safe as my place. After all, these monsters all consider the Silver Totems as their brethren, so they won’t start a large scale attack."

Garen straightened up and stacked the three notebooks on top of each other, flipping open the first one.

"Anglo Academy Secret Tactics: Sight Sharing"

The title of the book was written in a small line of delicate and graceful pale red letters, using the Kovistan standard language. As one of the strongest countries in the East Continent, the Kovistan language had very wide coverage. Many other countries were also fluent in this language, making it something of a lingua franca.

Garen flipped through it. This tactic required the continuous release of fifteen trascendent glyphs in a short window of time.

Transcendent glyphs were the figures written in the air using their natural ability.

This tactic required fifteen transcendent glyphs, all of different shapes with no repetition whatsoever. And the easiest one still required five strokes, while the hardest needed more than ten.

Garen referred to the necessary time limit at the top of the page: within 3 seconds.

He remembered when Angel released this tactic back then, it did seem like she used very few movements. But thinkng back closely, her hands did move extremely quickly, and there was a slight tremor to it. The tremor wasn’t involuntary, but well defined and rhythmic. It seemed to be the gestures needed to release an even higher level tactic.

Garen easily flipped through the whole notebook, and it remained fresh in his memory.

Satisfied, he glanced at his attribute pane.

‘Strength 2.66. Agility 2.72. Vitality 2.76. Intelligence 2.53.’

"My intelligence has been fully restored, returning to the peak level from my previous life." Garen’s gaze slid down, and he looked at the skill pane with a hint of anticipation.

There was still no movement there. Obviously tactics didn’t fulfill some requirement too become a skill, or rather that potential points had no effect on tactics.

Slightly disappointed, he pulled back his gaze and focused all his concentration on carefully researching this Sight Sharing tactic.

Time trickled past. The oil in the lamp gradually grew drier, and grew less.

Garen repeatedly memorised everything in the notebook, and then began to draw it out with one transcendent glyph at a time. Each successful etching would light a whitish flame on the tip of his finger.

That was how he knew if he succeeded or not.

Smack.

The flame of oil lamp burst a little, as though it had ignited some form of impurity.

Garen instantly awoke from his concentration.

With Master-level ability when it comes to precision blueprints, his hands were as steady as an intricate machine, but his speed was still not up to par. He could only complete three trascendent glyphs in three seconds.

Taking out his pocket watch to look at the time, he realized it was already four in the morning. More than three whole hours had passed

"If it’s this hard to progress for me, with Master-level precision blueprint steadiness, who knows how hard it must be for those who are weaker, at Intermediate-level, or Beginner-level."

Garen touched the sides of the notebook. It was full of wrinkles from being read too often over a long period of time. Be it the original owner or Angel, they must have read it countless times.

"I can’t make it a skill, so I’ll just have to practie non-stop the old fashioned way, with no shortcut to take." Garen quieted his heart. With his Divine Statue Technique, he had extraordinary endurance, and needed only three hours of rest per day to fulfill his biological needs.

Judging from this speed of progress, he would need at least a month or more before he can more or less grasp this tactic skill.

But this speed was all because of the micro-control needed for the secret techniques he had originally trained in, added together with his Master-level precision blueprint steadiness. If it was anyone else, they would need more than a year before they could even think about it. And yet the real result would more than likely be that they couldn’t quite accomplish it even with more than a year’s time.

The pale white sky quietly shone through the black cloth curtains.

Garen stretched, and finally brought his mind back from his training.

He glanced at the potential value in his attribute pane. It had jumped from that pathetic 16% to 132%.

"According to the previous comparisons, a Unihorn Lizard would equal to about 60% potential value, so now I have enough for two Unihorn Lizards. That sort of dead baby looked scary, but in truth it didn’t have that much potential value. I killed one on the way, killed another just now, and after the Croc went it at least killed another, and yet we only reached 132%."

Chapter 300: Ambush 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

Garen stood up from his desk. Blowing out the lamp, he walked to the window, and drew the curtains with a whoosh.

Looking down from there, he saw the corpse of yet another Unihorn Lizard in the shadows by the walls. The body lay face down, a large, basketball-sized red sarcoma on its abdomen.

Garen felt for their connection, and discovered that these were the Deep Swamp Croc parasites' eggs.

He looked at the parasite eggs carefully, and noticed that they were faintly growing bigger. Pulling his gaze back, he drew the curtains closed, turned around and left the study, stepping his way down to the first floor.

The first floor hall was wide and empty, and a window on the right had been broken. The cold air blew in through the hole, making the curtains rise and fall, rise and fall.

Clearing out the bones and body bits out of the corner, Garen brought a large bucket of water out of the store room, and started cleaning the house from top to bottom. He used a wet cloth to rub the furniture down, and used a mop to clean the floor, especially the place at the corner where they used to keep the bodies.

After cleaning everything once, using up several buckets of water, and spending half an hour of time, Garen finally called it a day.

"This will be my long-term base from now on." He breathed in the clean air, feeling satisfied. Without the rotting stench of bodies and the pets' foul breath, he felt instantly lighter.

"The stuff in the store room can last me several years, and then I can go out hunting for Unihorn Lizard every few days, and use that as my source of meat."

He was completely unbothered by the bacteria brought by these Silver mutants. With his body, he didn't need to worry at all about most bacteria. If any harmful substance entered his body, he would be able to sense it immediately, and then he could use his powerful blood chi to mass produce the relevant antibodies and white blood cells to swallow the bacteria right up.

Garen remembered clearly that this uproar had actually gone out of Obscuro's control, or perhaps they never intended to control it from the start. Stronger mutants kept appearing one after the other, the infections grew worse, and humanity's living space was constantly getting invaded, the population decreasing dramatically.

Perhaps this was the perfect world Obscuro wished for. Survival of the fittest, natural selection, the weak had no choice but to die. They discovered a power that even they couldn't control, and chose to release it, attaining their motive of destroying all existing order.

Throwing out all the miscellaneous rubbish, he made the Blue Back Lizards act as rubbish trucks, carrying the waste to a domestic trash landfill in the distance.

Garen took a relaxing bath, and then changed his clothes.

The Blue Back Lizards had the ability to dig into the ground, so he let the three Lizards dig from the floor of the kitchen itself. When one got tired the other would take its place, until they find an underground water source.

As for Garen himself, he did one round of secret technique training in the first floor hall, had breakfast, and then returned to the second floor to continue researching tactics.

The Deep Swamp Croc would occasionally go out hunting, bringing back Unihorn Lizards for food and parasitic purposes. Within three days, the parasites increased from two to five. If it weren't for the fact that two of them failed, it might even have been more.

The Resonance Hawk would fly out on its own once in a while. The gigantic bird with a wingspan of four, nearly five meters was like a fighter jet. It flew out here, and soon came back all covered in wounds, a Unihorn Lizard in its claws for food. It would even share with the other two Grey-feathered Hawks.

Every time it flew out, Garen could sense his potential points leaping twice or thrice. Evidently the Resonance Hawk directly faced off with two or three Unihorn Lizards at once. Unlike the Deep Swamp Croc that snuck out at night for stealth hunting, it fought head-on, and could actually succeed in its hunt when outnumbered. And its wounds weren't all that serious either, allowing it to recover very quickly.

This greatly increased Garen's approval of it.

In almost three days' worth of time, Garen's potential points had gone up by six whole points. He immediately put them all onto evolving the other two Grey-feathered Hawks. One of them succeeded, but the other unfortunately failed, wasting three potential points.

The two Resonance Hawks built a nest on top of the villa together, the second one still afraid of the first Resonance Hawk. Garen named the first one No. 1. It was the largest Resonance Hawk that also evolved the fastest, and its intelligence was equivalent to that of a two-year-old child, so it could even carry out some simple orders. Garen put it in charge of the other Resonance Hawk and the Grey-feathered Hawk. Together, they were in charge of surveilling the movements around the villa.

Garen didn't know what the situation was like in the inner city. He stayed safely in the villa, continuously working on his power. The Deep Swamp Croc and the Resonance Hawk kept on killing all the monsters around them, and his potential points could be continuously increased without any danger as well. As long as he didn't purposely reveal himself, he wouldn't attract a large scale attack from the monsters.

　**************

Afternoon

Garen sat quietly, eating the mashed potatoes he made as he stood by the wall of the villa's side yard.

In front of him, Resonance Hawk No. 1 was facing down the Deep Swamp Croc. The two beasts glared at each other ferociously, about to launch into a terrifying attack at any moment.

The Resonance Hawk stood on the ground, its wings flapping constantly and bringing up gusts of winds.

The Deep Swamp Croc tossed its tail, soundlessly sprawled onto the ground, waiting for an explosive strike.

Garen held his plate and spooned the mashed potato into his mouth, watching the battle quietly.

He had never observed the Resonance Hawk's abilities closely. This was the perfect opportunity, he planned to let the two beasts compare against each other, to see exactly how their true powers match up.

The two beasts stood off for a while, and then the Deep Swamp Croc suddenly pounced. It didn't open its mouth to bite, instead crashing into its opponent with brute force.

Bam!

The Deep Swamp Croc was actually knocked flat onto its back by the Resonance Hawk. It made a flip, revealing its white stomach. It tried to get up, but was immediately pressed down by the Resonance's Hawk sharp talons, trapped down to the ground hard.

The Resonance Hawk kept flapping its wings, generating a great force, keeping the Croc down and unable to turn over.

"What formidable strength." Garen narrowed his eyes, looking at the Resonance Hawk thoughtfully.

Among the Resonance Hawk's abilities, there was an icon for natural strength. This evidently manifested in its extraordinary strength. Even the Deep Swamp Croc was no match for it.

Garen began to understand. The Grey-feathered Hawk could only evolve to Form 3. As a creature whose original form was merely a wild animal, it wasn't one of those primitive totems that had been studied for a long time, and had extremely high evolution levels. Its evolution was more towards using the potential points to awaken its genetic potential, to find the strongest part of its genes and then strengthen and replicate it. In the end, it would be the strongest of its genes. This definition of strongest was evidently influenced by the direction the potential points took it in.

It might be a state that existed in the past, or a state it could evolve into in the future, anything was possible.

And within the Grey-feathered Hawk's genes, the strongest would probably be the Resonance Hawk's form.

The sound of the two beasts clashing quickly attracted the attention of a Unihorn Lizard to flew over. This Unihorn Lizard pounced down fiercely, directly grabbing for the giant Resonance Hawk.

This savage animal had a strange habit. They weren't afraid of dying, but they particularly liked tearing their prey into pieces. They enjoyed the sense of accomplishment from tearing prey into pieces, and instead focused less on hunting for food.

The Resonance Hawk's eyes went red, and it raised its head to face the Unihorn Lizard pouncing down from above, the sarcoma on its head expanding and beating.

Ba-thump! Ba-thump!!

The continuous heartbeat instantly spread, until even Garen could hear it from the side.

Ba-thump! Ba-thump! Ba-thump! Bump! Bump! Bumpbumpbumpbump…

The sarcoma beat faster and faster, faster and faster, until in the end it was almost a continuous sound, beating twice or thrice every second.

Bam!!

In the air, the Unihorn Lizard's eyes grew redder and redder, large bloody spots appearing all over the surface of its body. It fell head-first, landing heavily on the fence next to Garen and rolling onto the ground before it finally fell totally still.

Squawk!

The Resonance Hawk opened its beak and made a strange cry, walking over and biting down on the Unihorn Lizard, mercilessly pulling away a piece of flesh and began devouring it hungrily.

Garen also walked over to inspect the body. He just reached out his hand to pat it lightly, and judging from the echo, he could feel that something was wrong on the inside.

"Impressive! The heart burst due to the vibrations. No wonder the Resonance Hawk's first ability is called Resonance Burst. This is an instant kill!" Garen sighed inside. When facing such an ability, he believed he had a certain resistance to it. After all, this was a test of one's control over their own blood and organs. But if a few more Resonance Hawks showed up… His heart also gave a cold shiver.

He carefully observed the Resonance Hawk's state. This guy seemed rather down, and even the sarcoma on its head was dimmer, no longer the bright red it usually was. That meant it needed some time to recover.

Through their connection, he made it do another round of Resonance Burst, but the reply was weak, and he needed to wait for a reply.

Garen poured the mash into his stomach with a few gulps, put down the plate, and walked up to the Deep Swamp Croc.

This one was fully recovered, if still rather unhappy and hostile towards the Resonance Hawk.

Garen let it use Tackle on himself. The Deep Swamp Croc hesitated, and then performed the order.

It roared, and lowered its body, as though gathering power.

Whoomph!

It instantly turned into a black shadow, blowing up strong gusts of wind as it rammed into Garen, who stood still.

Garen steadied his feet. Just now the Resonance Hawk made it seem like this was very easy to dodge, so he wanted to see how strong his power was now compared to totems.

When he could really feel that unbelievably powerful wind blasting in his face, he mustered all the strength in his body, making it instantly grow up to two meters tall. The platinum aura instantaneously was absorbed back into his body, becoming a halo of platinum light around him.

"Red Jade!!" He pushed his hands out, his palms as clear as red jade, bringing an intense heat as he held it against the Croc's head.

Bam!!

The man and the beast both retreated two steps. Somewhat dazed, Garen pulled back his hands and stopped, at the same time motioning for the Croc to stop as well.

He looked at his hands, unharmed in the slightest due to the protection of the Totem Light. And because the Deep Swamp Croc also had a layer of Totem Light, carrying the same properties of a Totem Light attack, it managed to break through that layer of defense, and was only forced back by the pure momentum of it, remaining similarly unhurt.

But the black Totem Light on the surface of its skin was rippling non-stop, evidently the impact from that collision just now.

Such a collision actually had twice the impact of a one-sided attack on the relevant area.

Obviously, Garen's Totem Light was much stronger than that of the Deep Swamp Croc.

"It's too bad purely physical attacks would find it too hard to break through the Totem Light."

Garen did some calculations. He had finally returned to the very peak state of his previous life. If he used his body alone to face the strength of the Totem Light, and brought out everything he had, he could still only break past an elite Form 1 totem's Totem Light if he focused all his power on one spot for three attacks.

If he wanted to be a totem user using his secret techniques, he would still have a difficult journey ahead of him.

Chapter 301: Partner 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

Picking up the silver plate and fork on the ground, Garen was just about to return to the hall of the villa to continue practicing his tactics.

Suddenly he heard a loud explosion in the distance, together with the Unihorn Lizards’ strange cries and the dead babies’ wailing. He could even hear someone yelling and cursing.

With one leap Garen was on the roof of his own house, half-crouching in the giant hawk’s nest made of dead branches and dried leaves as he looked into the distance where the sounds were coming from.

In the area between the suburb and the produce market, a man and a woman were ordering around two brown bears and one black wolf, while they were surrounded by six or seven Unihorn Lizards. There was even a swarm of more than ten dead babies crawling towards them quickly.

These dead babies were evidently not really babies, otherwise there couldn’t possibly be so many of them.

Garen narrowed his eyes, wondering if he should go over to save them. Suddenly those two yelled out, and with a moment’s slip, a Unihorn Lizard bit through a brown bear’s neck, causing it to dissolve into a puddle of mercury. The two turned around and tried to run, but the dead babies soon caught up to them. The totems were finished off first, and then the two were also drowned in a flurry of dead babies’ chomping. Their limbs and heads were instantly torn into several pieces and shared around.

"So this is the fall of totem users, huh… If I didn’t have my Silver Totems, I would probably have ended up the same way. There’s no way I could have lasted that long outside." Garen sighed inwardly. As long as he was outside alone, he would bump into some monsters eventually. If he had released his primitive totems to fight, he would have soon attracted large groups of monsters. In the end, he would have been surrounded and killed.

The only way to guarantee his own safety would be to end the battle quickly, and then to pull himself out of it and leave.

Garen understood that the mistake just now was most likely because of the dead babies’ Dizziness Attack ability. He had encountered it before too, and even with his calibre he had been slightly dizzy before he could recover. These two stood no chance with their bodies.

Sliding down the roof quietly, he suddenly noticed that there were still letters in the letter box outside his villa.

He was rather surprised, but he didn’t go get them himself, sending a Blue Back Lizard to crawl over instead. It used its teeth to open the mailbox, and took the letters inside in its mouth as it ran back.

Standing in the hall on the first floor, Garen took the letters and then closed the door.

There were three letters. Two of them had stamps, and were notifications from the suburban’s community to pay management fees.

The third had no envelope, and was merely a folded piece of white paper.

Garen opened this one, and looked at it closely.

‘Garen, if you can see this message, please come find us at No. 128, Queen’s Side, in the inner city ASAP. I’m already here with Andy and Jessica. --Goth, 15 Aoril, night.’

"15 April? Wasn’t that just yesterday?" Garen was thoughtful.

That was the first line, there was still a second line after that.

‘Garen, if you’re still alive, then please inform us as soon as possible. It’s getting more and more dangerous here. The monsters are getting more concentrated. There seems to be some hidden danger in your house, so I don’t dare to go in carelessly. If anyone sees this message, if anyone knows anything about the owner of this house, please bring this letter to No. 128, Queen’s Side. Look for me, Goth, and we’ll give you a reward for your troubles.’ The ink of the words hadn’t dried yet. It had evidently just been added on.

Garen heaved a little sigh of relief. He didn’t think Goth would actually find his place stealthily. The past few days, he had been hiding in the house, and made the Deep Swamp Croc hide too while the Resonance Hawk lay in wait on the roof. The parasites were patrolling the area as well, no wonder Goth didn’t want to just come in.

But to think that under such circumstances, he was still thinking of Garen, and had come here twice continuously. Even Garen’s heart was slightly warmed by that.

Goth really was a decent friend. Once he recognized you, he would walk with you to the end.

Keeping the letter, Garen’s expression looked thoughtful.

"According to the original chain of events, now should be the time when Goth grows at an accelerated pace, and it was also in this period of time that he experienced some unbelievable things Should I or should I not go over and follow him…?"

He hesitated.

"Following Goth would be the fastest way to improve myself, but without a certain strength in hand, opportunity can become danger. I can’t improve as quickly as Goth, but so I will definitely face more dangers than he will."

He felt for the Silver Totems around the villa. As long as he stayed quietly outside, and kept himself out of the issues in the inner city, he could also grow continuously and inconspicuously, it’s just that he would not improve as fast as he would if he went with Goth.

"The fragments in my memory only indicate that this is when Goth grows rapidly, but it didn’t mention the details. That way, if I go in there and it causes the butterfly effect, I might even make it so that Goth can’t survive this period in one piece."

"Should I hunt on my own, or follow Goth into the heart of the storm…?" Garen hesitated. "My original goal was to get my hands on a decent core totem by following Goth, but to think I found a different path instead. And now that I got the Crystal Derivator, I have the chips I need to improve. It’s not worth it to join any more quests."

He held the door with his hand, looking at the grey sky in the distance. Under the layer of grey clouds, a large swarm of black dots were flying towards Iron Tank City. One enormous Unihorn Lizard was especially eye-catching, with black bone thorns growing from its head to its tail down it back. The whole row were of different lengths, and it was three times the size of a normal Lizard, reaching seven or eight meters.

This monster had been circling the inner city for many days. Garen saw many totem users come out of the inner city one by one, but none could defeat it, and it killed a few people instead.

And them the whole inner city shrunk into itself. It no longer expanded, and no one came out anymore.

Rawr!!

The BTL roared downwards, as though provoking them.

Right underneath it, a tall white tower with screw-like ridges was holding up a semicircular shield. The shield only appeared when it was being attacked, rippling with white light.

Garen looked at the screw-ridge tower from afar.

"Iron Tank City’s strongest combination of tactics for defense, impressive as expected. I just don’t know how long it will last."

He closed the door, and returned to the second floor study, continuing to study the Sight Sharing tactic.

After two more days staying in the villa, the Deep Swamp Croc ended up with a total of 7 parasites, distributed to patrol the villa surroundings separately. The potential points he had gotten at the same time were just enough to successfully evolve the last Grey-feathered Hawk.

All three Grey-feathered Hawks had evolved into Resonance Hawk. These giant birds with wingspans of more than four meters were unbelievably strong, like the most ferocious predators. With Garen’s villa as the center, they hunted non-stop in all directions. Any monsters or Lizards that entered their sight of vision were killed with their talons and brought back to the nest. Otherwise, they were used to make parasites for the Deep Swamp Croc, or to be eaten.

With such a strong force, Garen decided to return to the War Guild’s underground hall again. He should give an answer to the Guild on whether or not he was going to join. If he could get some evolution knowledge on how to rear a totem, it would be a decent help for the nurture of his little group.

Before he left, Garen ordered the totems he had to hunt on their own outside, it was okay as long as they didn’t hurt humans.

Many Unihorn Lizards and dead babies kept flooding into the outskirts of the city. Resonance Hawk no. 1, the Deep Swamp Croc and the others had more prey than they could hope for. They didn’t dare to touch those moving in droves, and could only work together to kill small groups of monsters.If there were more than ten, they wouldn’t attack.

The hunting proceeded uninhibited, and the Blue Back Lizard kept digging in the kitchen to look for a water source.

Everything seemed to be progressing in a good direction.

***************

"The world would eventually sink into darkness and shadow anyway. All of us need to unite, and worship the will of the God of Deject. The apocalypse is coming, and all believers as well as non-believers will face the judgment of the apocalypse! No one can escape! None! What we need to do is beg…"

Garen had just walked into the underground War Guild when he heard a man’s voice chanting something loudly, his emotions high and passionate.

In the dim hall, there were only two candlesticks lit on the counter, the pale yellow light making the atmosphere dark and heavy.

There was the smell of blood and disinfectant in the air, thick enough to make one nauseated.

Garen walked into the hall, glanced around it and saw five or six people scattered around and sitting on the chairs. It seemed unusually cold, most of the seats were empty.

On the blackboard hanging above the counter, there was a condensed name list of the dead.

Garen looked around on the list for a while, and couldn’t find neither Angel’s nor Thomas’ names. Only then did he walk up to the counter and knocked on it.

"Do you need a transfer map? Most of the people have transferred, to the underground guild in the north." The young lady at the counter said, looking exhausted.

"The north guild? What happened, I was outside these past two days." Garen frowned.

"You actually don’t know?" The girl said in surprise, "There are too many underground scavengers, we had no choice but to focus our energy to protect a limited area. We can’t defend this place for long. The only ones left here are loons with a death wish. I’m leaving tomorrow too."

"Underground scavengers…" Garen had never heard that monster’s name. "Forget it, how many underground spots do we still have in the outskirts."

"About four, I guess. Taking away this one, there are three in the other directions. I bet they’re all starting to shrink now. They’re all about the same scale as ours, you can forget about transferring to those spots, it’s useless," the girl said dejectedly. "See that fatty yelling on and one over there? That guy’s a devotee of the Church of the Apocalypse. Last time there was still someone to throw him out, but no one cares about him now. It doesn’t matter how much of a fuss he kicks up, no one has the energy anymore."

Garen looked at the fatty, who was still preaching loudly.

"Once chaos descends, people like this would always appear, it’s very normal. Does that mean that Mr Caddy and the rest have transferred too?"

"They left a few days ago. Look at the people in this hall, they’re mostly suicidals here to brave the danger, while two are waiting for someone else," the girl at the counter said mildly.

"Is there a way to contact people in the inner city?" Gare asked with a frown.

"Unfortunately." The girl shrugged.

Garen left the counter and walked to a place beside the wall where he sat down, quietly observing the few remaining people.

Other than the cult fatty, the ones remaining in the hall were all injured to some extent. Garen’s burnt eyebrows hadn’t grown back yet, so he still kind of fit in here amongst the deadbeats. The only odd part was that his clothes were too clean.

After sitting for some time there, he heard footsteps coming from the tunnel to the right of the hall. Soon enough a fair-skinned man walked out, looking at everyone in the hall with an expression of unease and panic.

"Can someone protect me during transfer? Ten million in fees! Ten million rumbs!!" he yelled loudly. "Is anyone willing?"

"Scram! Idiot!" A man with a long, untrimmed beard was evidently unhappy, as he stood up and smashed a beer mug at him.

Clang!

The metal mug hit the wall, making a crisp sound, and spilling the beer inside everywhere.

The fair-skinned man shirked a little, and returned to the tunnel, standing at the entrance and now too afraid to come back in again.

Garen looked at them coldly, sitting motionlessly at the side.

Sitting quietly in the guild, he occasionally looked at the potential points in his attribute pane increase slowly, while his pet subordinates hurried to continuously kill more of the surrounding monsters. He had just finished up his potential value, but now there were 4 points again, which made him more and more relaxed inside.

The number of parasites had also stabled at about seven. Some would die occasionally, and others would become successfully one at times.

Chapter 302: Partner 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

It was morning when he came down. He sat in the guild for a good three to four hours, when it is almost two, Angel finally came.

She was wearing a black mantle, covering herself tightly. She wore a veil over her face too, only revealing a pair of pale blue eyes.

She sat in front of Garen and tapped the table with her fingers, but there were no waiters to serve her, she could only sit around.

"You're not bad looking." Angel evaluated Garen. "Much better off than I am."

"Have you advanced?" Garen paid more attention as she looked at Angel, his eyes lighted up. "Looks like you don’t need my help anymore." He looked behind Angel, a group of three, Goth’s group slowly sat down, their gazed fixed upon Angel’s direction.

Angel waved her hands, much like saying her hellos.

"I guess I’m alright.", her hands were crossed and placed on the table.

"Now is the time where we need combat powers. When you were not around, Mr Caddy from the guild pulled me into the ranks of the branch president, the condition was to pardon my crimes, and also to give me a suitable complete evolutionary nurturing knowledge. Of course, this requires missions to be completed as a price.

"Then did you not convert along with them?" Garen calmly looked at Angel.

"Listen up, Garen. I, Angel, am not someone who forgets her roots!" Angel tightened her eyebrows, "If you had not give me a hand when I needed it most, I would never have the chance to be exposed to the War Guild. I would have probably died off at some god-only-knows what corner alone!

"I am just a form one totem user, you are a form two totem user, there’s is no future for you to follow me." Garen shook his head.

"Hey!" Angel perched forward suddenly, paying close attention to Garen, eye-to-eye. "In all my life, you were the first who truly treated me well. No matter what your reason could have been, whatever the motive, I, Angel am someone who may have killed countless people, but never one who forgets her benefactor. Whatever, let’s go, come with me, we will convert together."

At this moment, it was obvious that she was sincere when she wanted to bring Garen, perhaps the core totem evolved, the Shackles of War was one thing, but Angel had accumulated for far too much.

Garen could see, she hadn't just evolved the panther, she also had her talent fully utilized with sufficient resources and knowledge. Coupled with the previous totem nurturing experience, this explosion had propelled her like a rocket into sky.

Garen squinted at her, without immediate reply.

He was clear, even though Angel locked down her core totem with the Shackles of War, but it was thought that she had her totem confirmed for quite some years already. She should be able to change her core totem and not be limited by the Shackles of War.

"Follow me, I will protect you!" if you feel that your abilities aren’t strong enough and are unable to show off your manliness, that’s your own problem." Angel said, without much thought behind it.

"Thanks." Garen smiled lightly, "But i’m not the kind of man who lives under another’s protection.

"Why? Is it very embarrassing to be protected by a woman?" Angel sarcastically asked, "I’m telling you, Garen, I have triumphed over tens of hundreds of men under my feet! If i am not this victory-driven, I would not have survived to this point! I really do not understand why do you need to protect your ego? Does your dignity matter more than your life?

"It’s not about this." Garen exhaled. "I have reasons not to leave."

"Your pride is the reason!" Angel did not let go of any chance to tease, "Be the little man you are when you have no capabilities, being protected by women isn’t some shameful thing, at least you’re able to be protected by someone!"

"Alright, let’s not talk about this." Garen waved his hands "Look at me, do I look like someone who needs to be protected?"

"Whatever, you should hide more, don’t end up on the blackboard the next time i see you." Angel shook her head, stood up and walked to the trio behind him, said a few sentences softly.

The trio is two made and a female, all wearing black mantles. He could only roughly make up their genders based on their body sizes. Each of them had strong, bloodied scents emitting from their bodies. He was unsure of whether it was their blood or someone else’s.

After Angel talked to the three people, she turned around to greet Garen. The four of them then soon left the hall.

Garen sat on the table alone. The crystal derivator must never be exposed, and in turn so must the Silver Totems. There were no issues for him to control that many form 1 totems, but if that amount of form 2 totems appeared, then it will cause a racket, and attract unnecessary attention much like the Prodigy Aska. At this point where, he doesn't possess the strength to face off with Obscuro Society, Garen would like to avoid too much attention placed on him.

After sitting for a little while longer, he went to the counter to purchase a map of the Iron Tank City, and proceeded to leave the hall.

At the waterway outside.

Two male totem users were transporting creatures’ carcasses; the creatures have not died for too long, they were commanding two White Bears to move the creatures in piles inside a crater.

The two men had obvious fatigue on their faces, and were slightly shocked as they saw Garen walking out.

"Are you walking this way?" One of them asked.

"I need to go back to take some things." Garen answered simply.

"Better not go, there are more creatures sighted outside now."

"Why do you care so much about other people?" The other person interrupted.

Garen did not pay further attention, he climbed along the ladder up to the exit, slowly popping open the cover and exited the waterway.

The sky outside was gray with a hint of a drizzle.

Garen just came out, and rushed into the shadows of the castle walls with extraordinary speed, hiding his aura to avoid the creatures.

Above him was a swarm of Unihorn Lizards flying over slowly, they were packed densely to each other and there might have been be hundreds of them. Among the swarm, there was one red-skinned giant lizard, its size is evidently larger than the rest.

The swarm towered over Garen’s position, failing to recognize the human that was hiding there.

Still in the shadows, Garen took out his map.

Iron Tank city was a giant white round circle; on the circumference was a label: City castle wall.

Within and beyond the castle walls were large amounts of buildings and housing, densely packed like a giant white mushroom. In the centre was a small circle, with the label: Inner City Area.

In the middle of the Inner City Area was a white dot. The label on the dot says: Spiral Tower.

Coincidentally, on the lower right corner of the map’s castle wall line, and the place he stayed sat just beyond it. . The district was placed on the rightmost border of the cluster of buildings beyond the cluster wall, on the right side beyond the cluster was a large wasteland, abandoned and uninhabited.

Garen carefully walked along the direction heading back. Each time, he advanced by getting in and out of the cover of shade. Sometimes, he would bump into some death babies, but they were no match for his speed.

As he approached the position of his district, it should already have been been a deep territory with lairs of monsters. Garen ran into the staircase in the tilted tower, and suddenly heard the some soft sound of voices from within the tower.

He stopped his footsteps, looking into the dark black void of the staircase, a soft voice came out from the right room of the second floor.

"I can’t believe there would be survivors that would still be alive." He wasn’t interested in helping these people, and he couldn’t help them anyway, people who cannot hide their aura were only going to bring him trouble, luring many creatures.

He sped out of the corridor, ahead of him was the hunting ground for Resonance Hawk, should be slightly safer, without the creatures roaming freely, a bigger crowd of creatures will also be easily spotted and avoided.

Walking along the main path, on both sides was dense forest, deathly quiet. Intermittently, there were cries from a baby coming from afar, which sent chills to the heart.

As he walked to the neighbouring houses of his villa, Garen let out a sudden "eh", his gaze fixed upon this house’s bush at the front porch..

Garen looked to his left and right, a black stag beetle was rustling by from his back, patrolling the entire district. Parasites’ patrol radius have engulfed the entire parameter of the district.

Garen observed the skies around him carefully, there were no traces of large groups of creatures, only then did he approached the bush. He softly peered open the bush, and in front of him was a young girl, covered with wounds and blood stains.

"That girl who followed me home the other day?" Garen’s brows frowned. He recognized this person, she is one of the girls who had followed him and Angel on his road rushing back, on the same carriage, as he was guarding them into the city. He recalled that she had introduced herself before, her name was Lala.

He tapped that girl’s face, no response. He extended his arm nearer to her nostrils; there were some vague breathes.

On the girl was a black, pleated short skirt and a white satin shirt, under the skirt was a long black pantyhose that was full of holes, revealing wounds that had traces of blood. The skin of the black long boots that she was wearing were bruised and damaged, completely losing its exclusivity and elegance of the original little buffalo skin boots.

Pa Pa.

Garen slapped her with force

"Are you alive?" hs asked softly.

"Ugh…"

Lala weakly opened her eyes, with a very exhausted look. It seems as though she could not clearly see anything, both her irises didn't seem to be focused. She saw a blurry silhouette moving, the voice seemed so far away that he couldn’t hear clearly at all.

"He… Help.." she struggled to say the two words, then she tilted her head over, fainting once again.

Garen stood straight. He frowned. To be honest, he did not want to save anyone and add more burden to him, but coincidentally, he met someone he had met before, and by the looks of it, it seems like she ran out from the suburbs, going through hurdles to get here. If it weren't for Resonance Hawk’s patrol parameters, and the fact that this place was clear of free roaming creatures, plus that the larger crowds would not consider such a small meal, this girl would definitely not be alive.

"Screw it, count yourself lucky! I am lacking a janitor, in any case." Garen squatted and lifted her up, with one arm under her armpit, marching in big steps towards his villa.

This girl is just a normal person, and does not posses any threat to him; which is a key reason as to why he would save him.

Furthermore, if he were to stay alone for about a few months time, being completely alone was also not a feasible idea.

Chapter 303: Beginning 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

The window was splashed with falling rain.

Garen served up a hot cup of coffee, standing by the window.

On the large bed behind him, that girl called Lala was lying down on the bed massaging her head, not fully conscious.

"Are you awake?" Garen turned back to the bed, this Lala girl’s motive of coming here was obviously to get some form of protection from him. It’s just that he had his own agenda to accomplish, staying by his side is not that much safer compared to somewhere else.

The girl tried to get up. The clothes on her body had not been touched by Garen; they were still the original dirty attire from before.

The first thing she did was to check her body for traces of possible harassment. She relaxed herself . Following that, she placed her gaze upon Garen who is standing by the side of the window.

"Thank you, for saving me once again." her voice sounded sore, obviously she is having a flu. "If it wasn’t for you last time, we should be dead by the roadside outside the city."

"I always expect for returns when i do something, I have saved you twice, how do you intend to return the favor?" Garen looked at her calmly. "If there is a behaviour of wanting something, it is only natural to consider the price, there is nothing that can be gotten without paying a price in the world. Don’t you think?"

"I understand." Lala’s eyes shows that she seemed to understand, "I am but a weak lady, what else can i give you? Or rather, what do you intend to take from me?" Her speech is clear and without hidden meanings.

"The cleanliness of this house, the daily chores and housework, very simple requests. The condition is that I provide shelter and food, how’s that?" Garen answered coldly. "Also, as a man with normal sexuality, to be able to see a clean and cute lady at home, will improve my mood greatly too." He spoke straightforwardly.

Lala lowered her eyes: "Your demands are reasonable, I am willing to work in order to exchange for my safety and livelihood. Under this isolated environment, you are able to suppress your desires and stay respectful to a lady, you are a good man."

"Good Man?"

Garen laughed without voice. He extended both arms, looking at his clean, untainted palms. These arms, who knew how much blood had tainted these arms, innocent ones, sinful ones, or even just plain brawls, but such is life.

He snapped back into reality, laughing sarcastically.

"I’m glad to get to know a partner of an opposing gender which is rational, but I will remind you, there are many places in the house which are prohibited for you, you best not run around. If you wish to go out, leave me a note. I will arrange for it. The medications are placed by your pillow, and for your information, this is my first time taking care of someone outside my family."

"It is my pleasure." Lala relaxed and smiled. As she looked at garen calmly leave the room, she exhaled in relaxation. Aunty had already arrived in the city safely, in one night, her entire world collapsed, countless creatures killed people around her; the ones who she were familiar with, the ones who weren’t, too many lives have been taken away as she watched.

"Sufficient food, sufficient safety, warm blanket…" Lala had not had a moment where she thought of things she normally had to be a luxury.

Garen walked out of the guest room, tidied his collar and walked back to his master bedroom.

Standing in front of the mirror, he took a good look at himself.

His smooth bald had have a layer of short hair now. On the outside was a grey mantle, so long as he wore the hood and lowered his head, nobody will know who he is.

He pulled open his wardrobe. After some flipping through, he took out a greyish-white inner tee to be changed into and wore the pieces that would make up the complete leather armor he prepared previously.

Two round shoulder pads, forearm guards, knee guards, calf protectors, boots, and then a helm with a chest plate.

As he wore all of those, the person inside the mirror looked similar to the guards of Iron Tank city.

After giving it some thought, Garen took off the helm and wore the grey mantle again.

"Now this is much better." He satisfyingly said as he looked at himself.

The mantle covered the entirety of the armor, giving him a muscular look.

"Next, let's look at what my little babies are up to." he focused on the attribute pane.

"Strength 2.66. Agility 2.72, Vitality 2.76. Intelligence 2.53. Potential 632%. Possess the qualifications of a Luminarist "

6 points of Potential points.

Garen squinted his eyes, he glanced over the totem pane, the amount of parasites had dropped to five, which should be due to another battle happening.

"Let’s have the blue back lizard evolve instead, the success rate for third form evolution is too low."

He triggered a thought.

Soon, the doors were nudged open, and three blue back lizards slowly walked in. The last one closed the door under Garen’s control.

This kind of deep blue colored lizards normally inhabit the desert areas, so their survival abilities are really strong, with extreme tolerance to hunger and thirst.

Garen squatted in front of the three lizards and touched their heads.

"From now on, you're Number 3. Deep Swamp Croc will be Number 2. This will ease identifiability. I’ll have you evolve first."

His gaze placed on the blue back lizard’s icon, quickly, three points of potential points disappeared in a quick jump.

Number 2 blue back lizard shuddered for a moment,, and then started vibrating intensely, as if something were vibrating immensely inside its body.

Jiii…..

Number 2 let out a painful hiss. Its body rapidly grew from about a meter, quickly elongating to two meters, three meters, four meters, five meters!

Its height also grew from ten-odd centimeters, quickly to twenty centimeters, thirty centimeters, fifty centimeters, more than one meter!

Its skins started to show a bronze-like yellow tone, the teeth slowly grew out of its lips.

The entire lizard's body looked more and more like a crocodile

Between its four legs, it grew another pair of short legs, becoming a six-legged creature. Its back also spouted a row of dense spikes.

The most eye-opening aspect of the creature is its eyes. From the original jade green, it turned into a clear white, as though there were no irises in them.

This lizard’s evolution scared the other two lizards. They quickly hid, avoiding the quickly expanding Number 3 that was hissing in a scary manner.

Garen stood in front of the now evolved lizard, feeling that this fellow looked like the rumoured Komodo Dragon, one that could eat something that was its own size.

He looked at the totem icon within his vision. The blue back lizard changed its icon.

"Evolved Lizard( Unnamed): Blue Back Lizard’s second evolution form, Form 2 creature totem. Upgradable, evolution sucess rate: 34%. Potential point consumption: 500%.

Ability: Petrification (Any creatures making eye contact with it will be damaged by the Petrifiaction Light), Fast Tunneling."

"Petrification?" Garen noticed that this evolved lizard’s eyes had a hint of green light within its white eyes.

"Rename as Petrifying Lizard."

He changed the name on the totem, then only he carefully checked out the Petrifying lizard.

Petrifying Lizard laid on the floor, motionless, almost lazily, just like a bronze statue.

Garen took a turn around the lizard, extended his arms and touched its skin; very coarse and tough, like hardened leather, but with a hint of warmth.

He tried touching the spikes on the Petrifying Lizard’s back; also very tough, much like an awl, poking out of it skin one by one, forming a straight line from head to the tail.

"Go hunt something for me." Garen instructed as he opened the door

The lizard crawled slowly out of the door. Its movements are extremely slow, like an old grandpa at their seventies or eighties, the round belly was almost as good as being dragged on the floor. The six paws slammed the ground as it walked.

Garen shook his head, speechless.

"Stealth doesn’t work, use your fastest speed!" He ordered.

The Petrifying Lizard then increased its speed. It was apparent that it was trying its best; the six short limbs just struggled to move forward, but the speed was only comparable to a tortoise at best.

"This speed!..." Garen had a hidden impulse. "This is only a feeder during close quarters combat!"

Bringing the Petrifying lizard out of the villa, Garen came to the backyard, where there was leftover Unihorn Lizard carcass.

"Attack that carcass!" Garen ordered.

The yellow lizard struggled to crawl into a five meter rang of the carcass, both eyes glared at the carcass.

Without any visible movements, the carcass started turning into a greyish white rock-like form from the bottom to the top. Soft crackling sounds were heard as the rock spread.

Three seconds later, the carcass completely turned into a stone statue.

The Petrifying Lizard spat out a red core, it didn't seem a tad bit tired.

Only then, Garen felt consoled.

"Petrifying Lizards can only be used as a defense against ambushes, it basically could not keep up with other creatures’ speeds at all."

Ah!!!

A loud scream of a lady was heard from the main door.

Garen stomped once, and suddenly turning into a shadow, showing up at the front yard of the villa.

Lala was covering her mouth at the doorstep, staring at the large black beetles walking past the lawn in fright, the saw-like rows of teeth in the black beetle looked horrendous, scaring her pale. She was holding onto the doorframe as she felt weak in her knees.

Seeing Garen’s appearance, her voice was trembling while her fingers pointed at the beetles.

" Bug!! Monster!! There’s a monster!!"

"They're my little babies, don’t be afriad" Garen waved his hands so that the beetles left their field of vision.

After calming Lala’s emotions, Garen told her not to go out, otherwises it would easily attract the monsters into the house. Luckily there was the scent of the dead unihorn lizard lingering, completely suppressing the scent of Lala that was within the villa.

He looked at the remaining potential points and he felt that the three points spent on the Petrifying Lizard was not worth it. It didn't matter how strong the petrification was, it had to first land on the opponent. The remaining three points, he did not plan to spend it on the Blue Back Lizards.

The two blue back lizards have already dug out some underground water from the kitchen, or perhaps taking a turn underground for as they dig for underground water. To have a well near the the kitchen, it will be much easier to use water.

After settling Lala, Garen wore his grey mantle and hoodie, checking his body, "I should go into the city to check on the situation… so long as i’m cautious, I should be fine.

Chapter 304: Beginning 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

Inner City. Central Treetop District.

In the luxurious dark brown study room, a man with a golden beard stood next to the window, silently looking at the towering spiral tower. The tower felt like three spikes drilled out of the ground and intertwining each other.

The white light shining from the top of the spiral tower reflected upon the skin of his face, showing a hint of silver luster.

The forehead of the man showed a deep frown, and his face showed a maturity and vicissitudes brought upon by time. On his muscular body, flaunted a set of dark, golden body armor.

"No news from Leah?" The man asked in a deep tone.

Behind him were four men and women wearing luxuriously, standing quietly. No one dared to speak out.

"How long can the resources within the inner city last?" The man turned around and looked at his own four trusted subordinates.

"Lord Duke, the inner city has plenty of resources. It would suffice for a year or two, but with more and more creatures outside, I am afraid…" A fat aristocrat stood up to answer..

"The Governor Leah has gone missing for fifteen days, there may have be some meddling done by the Obscuro Society." A middle-aged woman said in a deep tone, "The key now, is that as long as the stationed General Tyrone and the Duke work together, defenses should be able to hold for a long time; enough to wait until the RAL’s reinforcements arrive. "

"I'm afraid the Royal Alliance is too busy saving themselves." A thin man gloomily said.

Suddenly a burst of footsteps came from outside the study room.

The door was opened without permission. Then entered the adjutant of the Duke, called Vignal, who has always been a matured middle-aged man who now looked pale and panicky.

He quickly walked to the side of the Grand Duke and whispered a few words in his ear.

Suddenly, the people saw that the appearance of the Grand Duke had also changed; his forehead frowned a lot more suddenly.

He glanced around his audience.

"Gentlemen, I'm afraid we're going to usher in a bad fight." His voice was heavy.

Boom! ! !

As the voice faded, the spiral tower on the left of a gorgeous courtyard, suddenly burst into a sky of flames.

The fire suddenly swept the entire area equivalent to the size of a football field, the entire white courtyard was engulfed. Crimson fire almost instantaneously engulfed the white light of the tower.

Everyone seemed to hear the roar of the air in the distance; anger, helplessness, hopelessness, sadness.

No one had ever known the roar of human beings alone could contain so much meaning.

Everyone unknowingly stood up.

"That's ... General Tyrone's mansion ...." The fat aristocrat only felt the dryness of his own voice.

***********

General Tyrone was assassinated by his own biological son and adjutant, and finally his totem exploded, bringing his son with him.

One of the three strong pillars in the city had fallen.

The news spread like a hurricane across the inner city, everyone heard the roar from the mansion. Such sadness, helpless, unbelievable consternation, served as a remembrance to everyone

Now, there was only the Grand Duke .....

At a white courtyard in the Queen’s District.

Goth was wearing a white bib as he sat in fornt of the white bed and looked at Jessica. This usually quiet girl suddenly looked pale, as if she was scared sick.

"Why were you so careless to catch a flu and not realise it until you catch a fever, and you say I don’t pay attention to my body." Goth held Jessica’s hand carefully, his eyes full of tenderness and affection.

So many days within the inner city defense corps, the two people shared their difficulties, and have established relations with each other.

Jessica shook her head, just laughing.

"Every time I say that, you gave me that look," Goth said, in dissatisfaction, "You're always disobedient."

Jessica put up a pouty smile. "As long as you accept your father's apologies, I will listen to you."

"Could you not mention this? So annoying." Goth scratched his head in distress, "Mom’s the same, you too. Didn’t I say, I'm not blaming the old man."

"Can you say you do not blame him with this attitude? You haven’t even called him father once." Jessica shook his head. "No matter what he had done to you, after all, he has since repented. He is your father, and no one can replace that."

"Can we stop talking about this?" Goth gently smiled, he was defeated. "Forget it, you rest first, I’ll go to back work."

He got up, covered the quilt for Jessica, kissed her on the cheek, and stepped out of the ward.

Upon closing the door, standing outside at the end of the corridor was Andy. He looked tired. His eyes were deep and he looked very gaunt.

Goth came to him and the atmosphere suddenly became heavy. No one first spoke, the both of them just stood there.

Andy took out a cigarette, lit it, only taking it down until the cigarette burned to the butt, he took a deep breath.

"How long can Jessica last with that illness?" Goth whispered.

"The doctor said she has only six months left," Andy said hoarsely.

The two fell silent again.

The scarlet red cigarette on Andy’s hand continued to release a faint white smoke.

"Is there any other way over there?" Goth whispered again. His face lost the relaxation and calmness that he had when he was with Jessica.

"My father searched all the doctors, the Luminarist, and the medicine professors." There was no such thing as ... "Andy lowered his head and said, "Stay with her. My father is waiting for me, I will go out first. "

He turned to exit the corridor.

Goth looked at his back. "There is a way," he said, "rest assured, she'll be fine."

Andy paused, moving on and quickly leaving the corridor.

Gothic pushed his back against the wall alone. What went through his mind was unknown, but the touch of loneliness and determination on his face was apparent.

****************

Outside the hospital, opposite the shadow of a white cylindrical building.

A tall man dressed in black robes was quietly looking at the exit of the hospital. He stood by as people walked past him. A team of patrol soldiers was constantly passing him by, and occasionally some totem users, but no one found his presence. People seemed to think of him as the air, no one gave him a second glance.

"Let's go ...." he whispered.

He gently stretched out his right index finger. A pale red light appeared on his fingertips; the ball of light slowly suspended, up and down.

Hiss!

With a soft spark, the man in black robe disappeared instantly from the place he stood.

Pa!!

Behind the original man in the black robe’s position, a silhouette in gray robe slowly came out. The face under the hood was indeed Garen.

He quietly looked at the location of the black robe that disappeared.

"Here ... finally ..."

He smiled at himself.

"Maybe Goth and then rest thought I was dead."

He saw the whereabouts of the black robed man just now. If he hadn't felt the presence of the other party, he estimated that, like the rest, he would have brushed it over.

He recognized the logo on that black robe. That was the Obscuro Society insignia; only they would wear black robes all year round in order to distinguish themselves from totem users of other organizations.

He did not intend to act directly with the Goth and others. With the help of his Secret Techniques, he was able to hide in the darkness, in a way that was not found by the people of Obscuro Society. This way, he could get the most benefit at this crucial time.

For example, if there is a clash between Goth and Obscuro Society, it would be the best opportunity for him to wait. If he followed Goth, not only there was there a chance he would be exposed, he may also be targeted for close surveillance. It was estimated that there was no way to get the most out of the situation.

Garen pulled his hood down and covered his face. He was not sure what motivated Goth to embark on the road to heroism, but now the tentacles of Obscuro Society had emerged.

He came out of the villa into the underground passage of the War Guild, going straight into the inner city. The objective was to use another method to keep up with Goth’s progress.

Standing in the shadows, Caldon quietly watched the hospital entrance and exit. Soon, Goth's figure came out from the exit. He looked calm, his eyes with a faint trace of anxiety.

Garen quietly kept up with him. Slowly releasing his Qi, closely following his tracks.

They quickly walked along the street; Goth quickly walked into a bistro. He came out shortly after, and walked directly toward the inner city’s border line.

On the frontier defense, there were dragon guards in the sky; the ground had dense frontier defense totems, each of them large black wolf-type totems patrolling back and forth.

.

Totem users guarded each exit, all black panthers totem users. They looked like they had amazing speed.

Gode took a white badge and showed it to the totem user guarding at the exit, took back the badge, and directly crossed the border line, walking into the tunnel within the castle walls. Both sides had rows of guard soldiers. They were unable to fight in the frontlines, but good military qualities made them great at detecting signs of danger.

Goth looked at the door. Garen was also following along, mixing within the people entering and leaving. He took out the badge from the War Guild to be shown to the totem users guarding the borders.

This man with a small white beard looked at the medal. The three lines marked on top showed this person’s rank in the guild was three. His face suddenly revealed the expression of respect.

"Sir, please keep your badge, are you going out hunting again?"

"Yeah." said Garen simply.

Most of the people coming in out were refugees who had been rescued, as well as those totem users who got rescued. Few people went out, and all the totem users who go out would be respected by many.

People who dare to go out in this environment were those who were willing to sacrifice themselves for the stability of the inner city. It was worth everyone's attention.

Garen walked in the door while he basked in everybody’s attention and respect.

The figure of the front of Goth was out of sight, but his spirit could detect his position. Garen picked up his pace and followed closely.

As he exited the doorway, the ground littered with carcasses of unihorn lizards, the pile of carcasses were surrounded by the stench of flies around them, the buzzing sound from the flies are very annoying.

Gallon quietly keep up with Goth. Along the way, he saw carcasses of new monsters appearing on the ground from time to time. There were dead babies, unihorn lizards, and also a kind of leopard monster who walked on two legs.

This monster was earthy yellow in color, like a shrunken version of the Tyrannosaurus Rex. There was a triangular cone on its head, while its forehead has a hole that sprayed acid.

Garen looked at this new monster, which had yellow acid on the edge of the round hole in its forehead. He dabbed the liquid with a small stone and a sour, smelly, yellow smoke suddenly appeared on the stones. The dabbed surface of the rock immediately showed a coke black burnt surface, popping up many small yellow bubbles.

Garen tossed the stone aside and continue to keep up with Goth.

He realized that the direction Goth was heading to was the most famous hospital in Iron Tank City - David Jones Hospital, who specialize in treatment of many rare diseases. However, it was now a dead zone.

"Jessica is ill, and he here to find medicine?" Garen had his doubts.

Within the deserted dead white city, the streets, Goth and Gaen advanced quietly forward, in front of the is a steeple-like building which seemed like a church.

The white spire church was not damaged at all, only darkness ensued from beyond the open door, constantly blowing bursts of chilly wind. In front of the stone floor were a few beaches of dried blood.

Goth, softly, suddenly hid behind a stone on the right.

A large group of unihorn lizards suddenly flew over the sky. These lizards were actually all red lizards, their body size was almost double the average, monstrously huge.

They glided across the ground, swept up a strong gust and rolled up a large swathes of yellow dust. Shadows flew past the shelter of Goth and Garen. Only when there was completely no movement, the two slowly come out from their hiding place.

Chapter 305: Following 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

On the desolate gray city streets, the pair were like two black spots on white cloth, speeding towards the steeple.

The wind howled across the street, and onto Goth's hair backwards constantly. His gaze turned up to the church door in front of him. He quickened his pace, and entered the church.

Garen, underneath the stairs at the church's entrance, hid behind a stone platform behind the steps, quietly releasing his Qi to scan the interior.

Inside the church

Goth stood by the door, glancing around the church, looking blankly, his body lit up with a gray-black totem, and a dark-feathered bird appeared slowly on his right shoulder.

"Come out," he cried aloud. "I know you're here!"

His voice constantly echoed off the walls, reverberating deep within the building.

Roar...

All of a sudden, behind a row of pews at the front, a black lizard emerged. It was much smaller than the normal giant lizard, only the size of a dog, the horn on his forehead flickered with silver light, its eyes were flashing with a bloodlust.

"I've been waiting for you for a long time." The silver horn lizard said. It slowly climbed to the front of Goth, two meters away.

"Have you made a decision? Join us, you'll get what you want." Its voice was like a hoarse middle-aged man.

"Is this your body? Or your totem?" Gode looked wary.

"Wouldn't you know when you try?" A smug, silver smile emerged at the corner of the silver-lined monitor lizard.

A dark shadow flashed by.

It suddenly disappeared from its original position and rushed towards Goth, still by the door.

In mid-air, its four claws turned into sharp spikes, slashing towards its adversary. The sharp edge missed, but the waves in its wake were too quick to avoid.

Chi Chi Chi!!

Goth suddenly took two steps back. Four spots of blood appeared on him, and a little bit of blood soaked through his clothes.

"Some reach you have!" His eyes bulged open, uncomprehending.

Silver horn lizard sneered and once again turned into a dark shadow, hurtling towards him.

Chi Chi!

Two more spots of blood emerged after the exchange..

"blackfield bird, go!" He completely unable to understand how he was being hurt, he stumbled toward the church walls, trying to rely on constantly changing positions to avoid the lizard's attacks.

"We know your secret ...." The silver horned lizard sneered and said, "Your totem, the blackfield bird, though powerful, is connected to your ontology. As long as the blackfield bird is hurt, you too will be injured. "

As it spoke, it raised his right claw and lunged forward.

Scoffing, the Blackfield bird rushed to avoid the attack, suddenly enlarging in midair. From the size of a palm, it grew rapidly into a giant three-meter bird.

It shrieked, hovering in the air within the church, before diving towards the lizard like a giant eagle after its prey. It sped downwards like a sharp arrow.

The huge blackfield bird body was suddenly inflicted with several deep gashes, and Goth finally understood.

"Iron Feather Volley !!" He was relentless as he sent a command to his bird.

Suddenly, the blackfield bird's feathers shot on end, aligning themselves below the silver horn lizard. The black feathers slowly glowed with a glimmer of silver light. The huge, black body of the bird quickly spread a distorted force field and enveloped the silver horn lizard.

The force field was formless, and the lizard was held in a vice grip as if being crushed by a gigantic fist.

The black bird shrieked, Chi Chi Chi!!

All its feathers are shot out like a volley of arrows, a dense shower flying towards the silver horn lizard.

Bang bang bang!! Unrelenting bangs could be heard as some feathers hit the lizard. Most of the feathers hit the ground, stirring up large amounts of dust and gravel.

After all the feathers were shot, they quickly flew back to the blackfield bird as if they were boomerangs, and regained their original form.

The blackfield bird shrunk back to its original size and flew back to perch on Goth's shoulders.

Dust clouded the church, leaving nothing to be seen. After a short while the dust gradually settled down, and Goth could finally see the situation of silver horn lizard.

The silver horn lizard was shot full of holes but it was still struggling to stand on the ground.

"What strong ability. The traction field does not allow the enemy to escape and the attacks used after the release could indiscriminately attack any target around the perimeter. The ability of the blackfield bird is indeed rare." The silver horn lizard was just distracted momentarily and sustained serious injuries. However, it remained calm with no signs of panic.

"Goth, your growth is really amazing."

The silver horn lizard replied, before quickly turned into a silver-colored light, shining into the dark spots within the church.

The silver light disappeared in the shadows, and out of it came a voluptuous woman with wavy hair. One of her hands was adorned with five black gem rings, while the other hand was twirling with her blonde hair, her demeanor relaxed. A black robe was draped fittingly to the body and outlined her bodily curves.

"Tell me where the medicine is!" Goth clenched his lip and said aloud.

"Want to save your little lover?" replied the blonde woman with a smirk, "we'll talk after you win."

She waved a single hand and five silver lights shot out suddenly, transforming into five similar silver horn lizards. The regiment completely surrounded Goth and the blackfield bird.

Roar!

A lizard suddenly arched its body and let out a low growl. The first lizard, initially gravely injured, had now returned to normal.

Goth had a sudden realization and his pupil contracted momentarily.

Suddenly, the five lizards lifted their right claws and hurled themselves towards him all at the same time. Five almost shapeless sharp waves came at him from unseen directions.

Boom!!!

*************

Garen's back was against the stone wall as he stood on the left, just below the stone steps. He was quietly observing the movements inside the church.

From the moment Goth entered, there had been constant bursts of roars, as if a fierce fight was going on.

Even now, the movements inside did not die down. Instead, they appeared to be growing bigger and bigger.

Garen kept practicing portrayals with both hands while listened quietly to the situation.

Chi!

An invisible sharp wave flew out from the church gate and ruthlessly split open the stone steps on the platform.

Without a sound, the stone platform's corner was cut off and the ground was left with crescent-shaped knife marks.

Garen squinted and walked gently to touch the knife marks. The cut was more than 10 cm into the stone slab, forming lines of black slits.

"Powerful," he praised, "surely, the person going against Goth is a Form 2 totem user, and is not a perverse player either."

*************

Inside the church.

Goth gasped as he supported his upper body on his knees. His forehead continued to shed streams of blood, leaving a stream of dark red along his right cheek.

The blackfield bird on the side had its feathers scattered, like a hairy little hen. One side of its wing looked broken and both its eyes looked dead, as it was barely standing on the ground. It looked gravely injured.

In front of the bird and the man were five silver horned lizards, lying on the ground, all of them decapitated, rapidly becoming mercury.

The blonde wavy-haired woman looked horrified, her gaze on the wall gazing steadily at Goth. Her arrogance vanished.

"You! You actually ....!"

"Where's the medicine?" Goth walked over, grabbed her collar and slammed her against the wall. "Tell me! The medicine! Where is it!" His bloodshot eyes betrayed the tendencies of a wild beast, just a sliver away from losing control. .

"I'll tell you! I'll tell you !!" The woman sputtered hastily, "The medicine is...."

Chi!!

An invisible wave instantly split blackfield bird's body in half.

Chi!!

With another squeal, the bird tumbled to the ground.

Goth also followed suit a muffled scream and doubled over. His chest collapsed, and his mouth spewed blood as he coughed..

"As for the medicine, I'll reveal that to your dead body," The woman's face was covered with a flirtatious smile, but all of a sudden, her face froze. "you!!"

Bam!

The blackfield bird swooped up once again and into Goth's body, turning into a dark shimmering layer, covering his whole body.

"This is!!" The woman's expression suddenly panicked, not mock panic, but a real, guttural panic pulled from the depths of her psyche

She turned to flee. The last silver-headed dragon lizard flew up and grabbed Goth, trying to stop him from chasing.

Suddenly, an invisible giant force field dispersed and shrouded her within.

Bang!!

A huge roar came from within the church, dust was kicked up and rows of chairs and tables were thrown in all directions. The dust settled to reveal a crater in the earth, more than 20 meters across.

The instant after the explosion, all was silent.

The remaining dust eventually dispersed into the air, and in the middle of the pit, Goth held the woman by the neck with one hand. His face was deathly pale, barely managing to hold the body.

"Tell me, where is the medicine?" He asked hoarsely. "Otherwise, I'll kill you!"

The woman kicked her feet as her face turned purple.

"I... I do not know.... the important things are kept with Lord Ansella! Don't kill me!"

Goth's expression was grim, his hold on the woman who had lost the power to resist. Suddenly he saw her struggling, begging and even actually crying outright as her tears flowed into two clear traces of water.

The totem user in front of him was not exactly that flirtatious enemy, but more like an ordinary young girl, at the age of only twenty at most.

"Don't kill me, please! Don't!!" The girl cried splinters.

Looked at her pleading eyes, Goth's heart softened, and gently put her down.

"Where's this Ansella you speak of?" He whispered.

"He's… He's behind the black wall in Copenhagen, in the place marked with the dark sun. Wait until night falls to find him!" The girl quickly told him what she knew, "we are under his leadership, he knows the most. It was on his request that I came in contact with you! It's not my fault!"

Goth sent silent for a while.

"Scram." His face was overcome with calm. Retracting the blackfield birds, he finally saw what was left of the girl's six silver horn monitor lizards. Not one survived, all turned into mercury. He then turned to exit the church.

The blonde girl looked at Goth's silhouette vanish, and her eyes flashed with hate.

"Well go then! Best you die while you're there! Then I can easily finish what I have to do!" She said, her heart cursing him fiercely.

Goth's figure disappeared out of the church, and the girl managed to get up and look at the five dark gemstone rings on her hand, and suddenly grit her teeth.

"Don't you want to save your little lover? If you manage to save them, my name will cease to be Sallora! And that Andy as well. We should have just killed them all!"

Her face was deeply resentful. Her five well-developed totems were destroyed; a devastating blow to any totem user.

Chapter 306: Following 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

"Now i need to go back and nurture them again... Fortunately, with my past experience, I still have one lizard to breed with, otherwise it would have been utter misery!" She walked into the depths of the church.

Suddenly there was another set rhythmic footsteps outside the church.

The woman suddenly turned around and looked to the church door.

A tall, burly gray-robed man walked in slowly. Apparently under the gray robes was a set of armor, with a subtle hint of his facial characteristics.

The man only had some golden hair on his head, his eyebrows very light, handsome face seemed a little dead, his expression unusually pale.

As soon as he entered the church, his gaze quickly locked onto the woman.

"A totem user with so many totems, pretty good luck."

"Who are you?" The woman suddenly became wary.

"It does not matter who I am, but what is important is how much of a surprise you can give me." The man grinned, and that white set of teeth reminded people of the sharks in the sea. "An elite Totem User who cannot fight at all, I'm really lucky."

"You !!" The woman still wanted to speak, but in the blink of an eye, the man instantly disappeared from where he was.

What followed was a blackout. She didn’t know anything after.

Garen stab the woman’s eyes with two fingers, his fingertips dug into the depths of her brain, feeling a warm, paste like texture.

He slowly pulled out his fingers, and gently flicked them. The brain pulp and blood dislodged by the force of inertia, falling on the ground in the distance.

Splat!

Woman croaked on the ground, her eyes were stabbed into two bloody holes, red blood slowly rolled down the cheeks to form two red lines.

At this time, Garen did not pay any attention to the movement of the body at all. Instead, he focused his attention on the properties pane below the field of view.

One of the potential value this time shot up like a rocket, the figures changed at an alarming speed!

An unexpected feeling of surprise suddenly poured into Garen’s heart.

A full 10 seconds later, the potential figure slowly stopped. At this point has reached an alarming value!

1344%! !

From the original remaining 3 points, it suddenly spiked to 13! Garen earned 10 potential points just from killing that female totem user.

"It's a lot more worth than the one I killed earlier!" Garen compared the form 2 totem user killed in the previous attacks, and they were simply not in the same league.

"Now with 13 potential points, I can focus on upgrading one totem, and see how it goes after my strength increases."

Garon squatted down and searched the girl for a while to find a dark booklet and a leather bag with items. He glanced at the five gemstone rings between the fingers of the girl, hesitating, but did not take them off in the end.

If Obscuro Society attached tracking signals in these, it will be very troublesome. Better be safe than sorry.

After looting, Garen quickly left from the side of the church. He dashed out from a broken window, his speed was utilised to the maximum, and he quickly disappeared into the shadow of the city.

Following Goth back all the way into the inner city, Garen looked at Goth walk into his own residence to recuperate, and he quietly left. Then, he proceeded to the inner city war headquarters.

Headquarter’s basic buildup pattern is similar to the branch, but the venue was much larger. Hanging on the wall were a lot of skulls of the freshly hunted unihorn lizards.

Garen found a corner to sit down and ordered a cup of unexpectedly expensive coffee. He slowly drank the dark liquid alone.

People walked in and out of the guild. The wounded were continually rushed in, pulled out, then rushed toward the hospital in the city. They were brought in from the underpass and were injured on their line of duty.

He sat alone in the corner, using his gray robe to cover himself tightly. His gaze fell on the totem pane.

This time he was prepared to focus his potential points to evolve the Deep Swamp Croc. The ability of the parasites of the Deep Swamp Croc was a great addition to his overall strength. Although in contrast to its ontology, it was not tough enough, but this parasitic ability is enough to make up for everything.

Parasitic beetle was simply the perfect cannon fodder, used to amass numbers and for reconnaissance, were quite cost-effective.

"Just that, the chances of evolution to form 3 is too low." Garen's brow furrowed as he looked at the Deep Swamp Croc at the totem pane.

'Deep Swamp Croc: Second evolution of the short tail croc, form 2 creature totem. Can be improved, evolution success rate of 24%. Potential consumption point: 500%.

Ability: explosive ambush, steel armor plating, parasitism. '

"One in four chance. I'll try my luck." Garen made his mind, his gaze set on Deep Swamp Croc icon.

The potential points went fuzzy for a while, and decreased by 5 points.

The Deep Swamp Croc icon also blurred for a while, and a few seconds later, cleared up once again, and nothing else happened.

"There's still another chance!" Garon looked calm and tense, and he was mentally prepared. This low probability made it likely to fail many times, it might not necessarily get evolved even once out of four times.

The second time.

His gaze once again condensed on the icon.

The potential points got blurry again, and the Deep Swamp Croc’s icon did the same.

The icon cleared up, and was still the original Deep Swamp Croc icon.

"Failed again..." Garen took a deep breath, "no matter, following Goth will yield more chances for more potential to be credited in the due time. Form 3 totems are never common, how many totem users have failed to advance their totems after so many years of cultivation? if it was that simple, there will be many form 3 by now.

He was very aware of his own advantage. Unlike a typical totem user, he did not need to make the careful use of resources and money, to be able to succeed in evolution, and neither did each failure result in the destruction of the totem as well.

When evolution using potential points failed, the totem would remain the same as before, this was his greatest advantage. Even though potential points were difficult to gain.

Standing up, he walked to the guild counter in front of the council. From a total of five windows, he chose the furthest of the left-most windows with the words 'Enquiry Counter'.

He lined up as he slowly waited for his turn.

In front of people queuing up, they took turns to choose the information listed above. All the information held by the headquarters of the guild was listed down, and one could attain their desired piece without a word. The catch was that you couldn't ask for further details.

Soon, the red shirted lady in front of him left the counter with a gloomy expression. It seemed that she got some bad news.

Garen walked up and looked back to the eyes of the people behind, showing them a gaze which warned them not to get too close. The man in white behind him smiled, and then stood farther away.

Garen turned back to the counter, and looked inside the selection of items.

There was a black desktop with five options; five words are round boxes.

From left to right, they were: tracing, resources, monsters, routes.

Garen pressed on the resources boxes. The employee inside gave out a list.

He took over and looked at the top of the rows of resources and treasures, all of which were listed in detail.

'Rice - Location: Southern City District warehouse points, the estimated reserve of ten people a year. Intelligence price: two hundred thousand silver sheets. '

'Soy sauce - Location: Whitewing Chamber of Commerce warehouse, estimated reserve of 10 people for three years. Intelligence Price: 900,000 silver sheets. '

'Potato - Location: Whitewing Chamber of Commerce warehouse, estimated reserves of ten people in January. Information is valid: two months, priced at 50000 silver sheets. '

.......

....

....

Rows of various dietary resources were all listed. Garen looked from top to bottom, and soon his gaze fell on the totem resources.

Among the totem resources listed in the outskirts, there were inactivated totems, maintenance tools, unit factories, totem notes, and tactical notes, at the end. He actually saw an intelligence on permanent tactic.

For twenty thousand silver sheets, you could get them.

Obviously that was not very difficult. That is, there were other reasons which made it hard to pick up.

Garen roughly swept his eyes across. The permanent tactic, although he wanted it, he did not have the strength. Bought some intelligence on the creatures, took a thin booklet and he sat back in position and looked up.

After sitting in the guild for a while, Garen went back to the counter receptionist to buy a copy of the latest Insider briefings, along with some essential anti-fever and anti-inflammatory drugs. Then left a message to Angel, and then he walked into the underground passage, toward the direction of the outer city back.

Goth was seriously injured, he need to at least to rest for a period of time to recover. He happened to go back and visit. Now that his power had expanded considerably, he could go out to search for the resources needed, and also hunt more potential points on the side.

From the briefing, Garen saw the latest mission completion forms, with Angel leading the team in sixth place and among the top dozen of teams. It was unusually eye-catching.

This also made Garen extremely satisfied with his own standards. Angel's friendship, and the shackles of war as a link, did serve some function.

As long as Angel does not give up the core totem and strengthened it, when a the strength of the totem reaches a certain threshold, she would definitely be unwilling to give up the core easily, and this side of the link will become closer and closer.

From now on, the shackles of war did not reflect Angel’s signs of replacement of the core totem.

Going back to the underground passage and taking advantage of the emptiness inside it, Garen took out all the things that he looted; a booklet, and a bag.

These are the things that a form 2 totem user of Obscuro Society carries around. That guy's ability was very hard to handle. It belonged to a type of air compression cutting, and was very powerful.

With more totems under their control, without tactics but to purely relying on the totems, its power is very powerful already.

Garen looked back at such an encounter, the winner would be the one who attacked first. If he had attacked first, he would rely on ambush tactics. The resonance hawk’s attack was still very powerful, provided he was able to determine the location of the other totem users.

If his opponent attacked first, the invisible sharp edge of the blades combined with their speed, the resonance hawk and other totems may not be able to dodge, it was likely to be a disadvantage.

In fact, during simulations, the opponents’ winning percentage was much higher. That kind of speed, and it's very sharp air edge slash from the silver horn lizard is very tough to deal with.

If it wasn’t because of Goth’s core totem was destroyed, Garen did not dare to appear in the final minute to loot. Especially when the last outbreak of Goth, the air explosion that produced, it was never clear if Goth had caused it or that woman, but whatever that did, the crater it left was really terrifying..

Chapter 307: Adventure 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

Back at the War Guild Office in the outskirts of the city, there was almost no one else left, except for two guards who had stayed back to change shifts. As they watched Garen walk out, a surprised expression appeared on both of their faces, but they remained silent.

As he walked back calmly to his own villa in the suburbs, Garen realised that the entire area had become a paradise for his pets. All of the monsters that were scattered around here had been taken care of already, and only a few clusters of them remained in the surroundings. There were no solitary monsters left to be hunted.

Light rain began to drizzle down from the sky, as dark grey clouds began to appear. 　

As Garen walked into his courtyard, two Parasitic Beetles that had been keeping watch earlier now crawled towards him from both directions and climbed unto his body. The Giant Hawk and Resonance Hawk that were perched on the roof, stood up from their nests and let out a crisp whistling noise.

After taking out his keys and opening the front door, Garen walked inside, and closed the door with the back of his hand. Clad in a maid’s outfit, Lala walked towards Garen and, without being told, took his grey robe from him, and hung it on the clothes rack on the side.

"You’ve had a long day," Lala said softly.

"And you’ve adapted really quickly," said Garen teasingly.

He walked towards the sofa and sat down, as Lala attended to him and helped him change into a pair of clean slippers. Next, he brought the freshly made cup of black tea to his lips and sipped slowly.

"The tea has become cold."

"Forgive me, although we still have water in the house, we’re almost out of firewood, and I didn’t want to use it carelessly," said Lala as she stood on the other side of the room.

"This is a problem," nodded Garen. "I’ll think of a way to sort it out. The smoke from the burning fire where we warm ourselves will definitely catch people’s attention. Try and see if there are other ways to solve this."

"I will," nodded Lala in a hesitant manner.

Garen drank his black tea slowly as he leaned against the sofa and closed his eyes. A few moments later, he noticed that Lala had not left, and was still lingering at the side. He opened his eyes again.

"Is there anything else?"

Lala tugged at her white apron hesitantly.

"Although I’ve already troubled you greatly, but there is still something I would like to know.. How my family is doing in the inner city? As well as my friend, my only good friend Biz."

"The number of people entering the city are far too many, and they have been spread out messily. It would be very troublesome to find specific people," said Garen as he furrowed his eyebrows. "I have a lot of things on my mind, so in exchange, think wisely about the reward you will give me. If it is suitable, I will proceed to deal with this matter with my own hands."

"Yes, sir," nodded Lala. "I’m extremely fortunate to have met an employer like yourself."

"You’re welcome."

Garen lifted his cup of black tea and finished it in one gulp, before looking around the hall and noticing that the whole place was now spotlessly clean. He smiled with satisfaction.

"I’ll be going upstairs now. Unless there’s an important matter, please don’t disturb me. Right until dinner time."

"Alright."

Garen walked into his study room and locked the door.

The windows of the study room had not been closed, and the wind lifted the curtains up, allowing some moisture to creep into the room.

He walked over and closed the glass window, before sitting in front of the desk.

Once again, he took out the items he had gotten from the blonde woman, and spread them out on the table.

There was a leather bag and a little notebook.

The brown leather bag was the size of a fist, but no one knew what it was that was hidden inside to cause it to bulge.

Garen opened the knot on the bag, and poured out the contents with a crash.

The items that fell out onto the table were apparently a huge pile of various gemstone jewelry. There were rings, red rubies, diamonds, as well as the most expensive amethyst.

A surprised expression appeared on Garen’s face.

"Could it actually be that?" said Garen as he recognized the effects of the gemstones and jewelry.

"Evolving gemstones… Various Key Primers required when evolving Totems. Red represents the direction of the flame, purple represents directions that are currently unknown, while diamonds represent natural evolution. There really is an abundance of them here."

Garen’s mouth spread into a satisfied smile.

"I won’t be able to use these things, but other Totem users will surely find them to be of much help. The amethyst is a Evolution Primer required by many Totems. While using other sources during to nurture totems, high quality gemstones are needed as Primers during the Key Evolution period, in order to result in the desired result. If these criteria are not met, it will result in a chaotic evolution, as well as certain totems being evolved without any powers at all. These things can be exchanged with others for great returns."

He kept the gemstones as well as the women’s jewelry. Garen’s gaze then fell onto a different item.

A black leather little notebook.

He opened the front page of the notebook carefully. There were tightly packed scribbles inside, written in messy handwriting, with the order all mixed up. It was obvious that this was an essay of sorts.

Garen flipped through the notebook for a while, and skimmed over the words he could recognize.

"Eh?" he said as he sat up straighter, his gaze focusing suddenly, as he stared at one of the pages in the little notebook.

He took the quill from the pen holder and opened the bottle of ink, before dipping the pen into it.

He copied a line of words from the book onto a piece of white paper.

‘15th March, truly an interesting time. A man who was an old wealthy business man on the surface, turned out to be a strong Totem user in secret. Once the quest has been completed, find someone to get rid of him. Advanced skills like Solidifying Tactics are not things that can be easily protected by old men like himself.

Garen copied down the name of the place from the back of the notebook. The words in the notebook were slightly blurry and messy, which made them quite difficult to differentiate. Even though the contents were written in the Ender language, he still understood them, except for a few crookedly written characters that were hard to distinguish. However, he was certain that the name of the place he had written down was definitely in Iron Tank City.

He took out the map of Iron Tank City and began looking at the place names one by one. Immediately, his index finger paused on a specific location.

"Niester Region, this is a famous immigrant district. The people living there are all immigrants from other areas, all of which are either rich people or skilled elites."

He kept the map and wrote down the address of the place. After that, he looked at the sky outside.

"It’s still early, I can go take a look."

After saying goodbye to Lala, he willed his totems to prepare to leave.

He exited the villa, and jumped onto the top of the wall, looking at the totems in his possession quietly.

The three Giant Hawks on the roof circled around continuously and let out sharp deterrence-like howls, as if warning the other monsters in the sky that this was their territory.

On the ground, the Deep Swamp Croc commanded the eight Beetles to line up in the courtyard.

Garen left two of the Beetles behind, and arranged for the Petrified Giant Lizard to guard the house, while he took the remaining six Beetles out with him.

After that, he tried to recall the route from the map, and brought his totem herd around to the city, as they moved forward slowly.

Immediately, the Resonance Hawk found a hole in one of city’s wrecked walls. It looked as it had been damaged by a large monster.

Garen took the Giant Croc and Beetle into the city through the hole, which led to the craftsmen district in the inner city.

Grey-white bungalows were placed together in a row, and built tightly against the city wall. The insides of the building were completely empty and eerily quiet, except for the occasional sound of wooden doors and windows being blown closed by the wind.

The ground was covered with moist black soil, and there were white bones and blood stains everywhere. Meanwhile, numerous hammers and iron mats were scattered in the blacksmith shop by the road, and a few arrows were stuck in the pillars of a wooden building.

Garen was flanked by the Beetles and Giant Crocs, as they dashed into the area.

They spent some time turning circles around the clusters of buildings in the inner city, before hearing a voice echoing softly suddenly.

"Jegula, setingdiya,"

Garen furrowed his eyebrows, unable to understand what was being said. It sounded like a localized native dialect, unlike any of the languages of the Three Strong Empires.

He ignored it, and suddenly the sound of a woman sobbing emerged from the same direction as the previous noise.

The first voice grew louder and colder, as if it was scolding the woman.

Garen continued to ignore them, and passed through this region. In this chaotic world, only the strongest were the most powerful. Incidents like these were common occurrences everywhere, and could be seen anywhere.

Quickly, he passed through this vast region, and after continuing his journey forward for a period of time, he ducked down suddenly to avoid a large herd of Unihorn Lizards that flew past him in the sky. Although these monsters considered Silver Totems as one of their own and would not attack them without reason, in the event that they were provoked, they would still attack them, even if they happened to be of the same species.

Garen walked carefully until it was almost evening, before the crossroads of Niester Region finally appeared in front of him.

Along the way, he found six underground cellars in the outskirts of the city where survivors had been hiding. Many of these underground cellars had become private little kingdoms ruled by the strong. They hid in these underground cellars and became the kings they had always dreamed of becoming, wantonly enjoying themselves while trampling over the dignity and interests of other people.

Garen did not pay any mind to these people. Instead, he followed the address that he had memorised earlier, and rushed towards the rich businessman’s residence in the region.

Immediately, in the middle of the white buildings, a white house with a round silver roof appeared in Garen’s line of sight.

A large White Bat was perched on top of the silver roof of the house.

The bat was huge, as tall as five meters and as wide as four. Both of its white wings leaned against the roof, as if they were two pieces of white rags, as long as ten over meters when stretched open. Looking from afar, it looked like a white glider.

Garen willed his totems to spread out and surround the silver-roofed building. This house was the place where the rich businessman lived. It was obvious that this place had now become the White Bat’s residence, and if the rich businessman was not hiding, it would mean that he had been killed already.

Garen hid behind broken wall, poking his head out carefully to size up the Giant Bat.

A black iron chain hung around its furry neck, and the end of the chain was a red ball of flesh made up of a man’s corpse, dripping blood continuously.

Garen looked closely, and noticed that the black iron chain seemed to be growing out of the bat’s chest. Apparently, it was not something that was man-made.

He released his Aura carefully, as white-gold coloured ripples emerged slowly, covering the bat’s body at once.

Hiss!

The bat opened its eyes immediately, as if it had suddenly felt something. It shook its head from side to side, and began looking around at all directions.

A large splash of blood splashed through the air, sending Garen’s Aura back to him temporarily.

Whoosh!

Garen let out a low groan, and held his chest.

"To think that a monster’s blood could be this powerful!! My Aura comes from the polymerization of my Three Energies, and are not of this world. I’m surprised that it could use the circulation of its vital energy and blood to force my Aura back to me. Amazing!! The high levels possessed by the vital energy and blood, if compared to the previous world, would not be able to be destroyed even by bombs or missiles. Only nuclear bombs would be able to destroy them!"

This was the first time he had encountered a situation like this. After achieving his Godlike Accomplishment, the vital energy in his whole body expanded to reach the limit of a human, and from then on, even wild creatures could not be much stronger than him. However, upon encountering this bat, who’s vital energies were powerful to an alarming degree, he knew that it meant that it also possessed extremely powerful vitality. Therefore, as long as it was not killed, it would be able to recover to its initial state, and bounce back immediately. Creatures like this with extremely powerful vitalities were the hardest to defeat.

"In order to go in, it looks like I have no choice but to kill this monster," said Garen as he narrowed his eyes and hid deeper inside.

Once he had willed them, a Black Beetle crawled slowly into the courtyard of the house, as its large ferocious mouth pointed towards the Bat and screamed loudly to provoke it.

Hiss!!

The Bat ignored the Beetle completely, and acted as if the others were not there. It lay down again and prepared to rest. But the moment the Beetle tried to enter the building, the White Bat hissed and let out a warning noise.

Garen thought about it for a while, and decided to release the Neon Butterfly quietly, before using its poisonous powder to stain the claws of all the Resonance Hawks, as well dusting some on the Deep Swamp Crocs and Beetles as well.

Even though the Bat was an Aberration creature released by the Obscuro Society, the nature of its attacks still bore similarities to that of the Totem Light, and its specific strength was still unknown.

Garen took out the monster information pamphlet that he had gotten from the War Guild and began flipping through it.

Chapter 308: Adventure 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

He found information on the White Bat immediately.

‘Giant White Bat: Possesses strength almost equivalent to a Form 3 Totem. Extremely dangerous, likes collecting corpses and rolling them into ball-like shapes, and applying pressure onto the creature’s blood by squeezing their dead bodies lightly, to create an artificial blood circulating environment. Their size determines their strength, and the largest Bat has a wingspan of twenty meters, while the smallest ones have wingspans of ten meters.

Abilities: Ultrasound Wave Impact, Iron Chain Cage.’

"Almost a Form 3 Totem, huh… How impressive," said Garen as he narrowed his eyes.

Currently, his three Resonance Hawks and one Deep Swamp Croc were all at the level of Form 2 Totems. One of the Resonance Hawks were extremely powerful, and would probably be able to fight the White Bat, while the Deep Swamp Croc could launch a surprise attack in the dark. As for the Beetle, it would only be able stay alert around their surroundings. Meanwhile, the Neon Butterfly and Black-Striped White Tiger were left out of the equation, because as Form 1 Totems, regardless of their strength, speed, physique, and even abilities, they would still be surpassed by their opponents, and would only result in more casualties if released during battle.

However to face off something with this amount of strength, even if they attacked him together, Garen was still slightly wary of the probability of them actually defeating the bastard.

"That’s it, we’ll just have to try. A monster that has almost achieved Form 3 will definitely grant me an abundance of Potential Points once I’ve killed it. Furthermore, there may be unexpected rewards inside this house as well. This is also an opportunity for me to see the true power of my current strength," said Garen as he made up his mind, and prepared to make his first move.

A few Beetles spread out and kept watch, making sure to stay away from the house in the process.

Three Resonance Hawks circled around the perimeter of the house slowly. Meanwhile, the Deep Swamp Croc shook its giant tail and crawled into the shadows carefully.

A heavy atmosphere began to seep into the air slowly, as the White Bat seemed to sense that something was amiss as well. It folded its wings suddenly, and pointed its opened mouth vigilantly in all directions, releasing soundless Ultrasound Waves, as if it were judging the current situation.

"Resonance Hawks, go!"

Garen willed and commanded them.

The three Resonance Hawks flew in from three different directions and charged towards the Bat at the same time. The sarcomas on their heads began to bob up and down violently, as they grew redder and more blood-coloured with every moment.

Three shapeless vibrations flew towards the White Bat and crashed into its body.

Thump! Thump! Thump!!

A loud heartbeat echoed from the White Bat’s body instantly.

Hiss!!

It opened its large mouth and let out an angry roar. The roar was not loud, but a huge gust of white gas came spraying out with it. The White Bat tried to stretch its wings open to fly, but it was obvious that it was tired and having some difficulty getting up.

It shook its wings a few times and realised that it lacked strength, before beating them once again more violently, while its white eyes suddenly turned bloodshot.

Hiss!!

Once again, it let out a loud roar, as the sound of its flapping wings rang loudly throughout the air.

Opening its large mouth, the Bat suddenly released a series of silent sound vibrations, instantly hitting the Resonance Hawk on the left.

Hum!

The Ultrasound Wave Impact suddenly crashed into the Resonance Hawk’s body. The Hawk let out a sorrowful whine, as the feathers on its body seemed as if it had been blown by a strong gust of wind. It began falling to the floor in a heap. No longer could it continue to stay in the sky, as it began to fall and crash onto the roof, its whole body dripping with blood moments after.

Garen was left in shock, and quickly decided to command his other two Resonance Hawks to move forward and attack.

The two Resonance Hawks charged forward ferociously, one at each side, and cornered the White Bat from both the left side and the right.

Bang bang!

The loud noise sounded through the air twice, as the claws of the Resonance Hawks clashed with the wings of the Bat. The two Resonance Hawks had managed to suppress the White Bat, and had collided with it until the Bat nearly lost its balance. The flesh on the sides of the Bat’s wings were scratched up slightly, making it look like shredded pieces of white paper.

The two Resonance Hawks looked like two black dots as they flew around the White Bat, constantly looking for openings to attack.

The three of them fought in the air, as black feathers and white flesh endlessly floated downwards, showing that both sides had suffered losses and injuries.

The White Bat’s angry hissing noises grew more frequent, and it continued to beat its wings violently, making the chain on its chest shake harder in all directions.

A loud banging noise could be heard, before the corpse ball on the chain fell and crashed onto the body of the fi first Resonance Hawk that had not manage dodge in time.

The impact from the collision almost caused it to fall. Resonance Hawk No. 1 let out a sorrowful howl. Its chest looked like it had been dented inwards slightly, but the bird continued to flap its wings as it charged towards the Bat without any sign of death or dying.

Garen looked up and watched the fight from below. He knew that close-range combat like this was the best way to defeat the White Bat. Once the distance increased, the Ultrasound Waves and Chain Attack could take down any opponent easily. This was especially true for the Ultrasound Wave Impact that worked well in far distances, because it provided range-type damage.

Garen had already read the information about the White Bat. When this monster appeared on the battlefield, it always took at least three air-combat Totem users to get rid of it, and these fights always resulted in damaged Totems. Its terrifying Ultrasound Wave Impact was extremely powerful, and had already killed at least fifteen Form 2 Totem users. It was a formidable opponent, a bomber-plane type killer. It was similar to the White Dragonhawk in the human sense.

Garen controlled both of the Resonance Hawks quietly, commanding them to lead the White Bat slowly towards ground-level to continue their fight there.

A few moments later, the three creatures arrived near the shadowy areas near the wall where the Deep Swamp Croc was hiding.

Suddenly, a large black figure reflected outwards from the shadows, violently landing onto the White Bat’s body.

Tch!

The Giant Croc used its large mouth to bite down on the Bat’s neck brutally. Just like a wild animal trap, the Croc’s sharp fangs snapped down on the Bat’s neck quickly, not releasing it at all.

The Deep Swamp Croc’s large body was now wrapped around the Bat. Suddenly, large quantities of sticky white blood began to flow out of the Croc’s mouth. It was the White Bat’s fresh blood.

Hiss!!

The White bat hissed in pain and began struggling frantically, as if it was about to drag the Deep Swamp Croc up into the sky.

Out of the blue, the two Resonance Hawks flew towards them. They flapped their wings a few times, as their four claws attached themselves to the white wings.

The three beasts pressed their opponent against the ground, as white blood continued to pour out continuously like an endless stream of water.

The White Bat struggled for a few good minutes, and then stretched its big mouth open suddenly. The sound of empty air leaking out sounded out from its throat. Finally, all movement ceased.

At this moment, Resonance Hawk No. 1 relaxed itself as well. As it lay face up on the ground with its sharp beak open, its eyes turned white and it continued inhaling, but did not exhale. Its breastbone sunk in deeply, an obvious sign that something was not right anymore.

Garen walked out of his hiding spot and looked at No. 1 who was currently in a bad state, as a series of emotions began to bubble up inside his chest.

"You’re very brave," he said as he crouched down and stroked No. 1’s feathers and watched him gulp air slowly, noticing that he had almost stopped breathing. There was an indescribable feeling in his heart.

Just then, the Potential Value at the bottom of his field of vision began to change.

From the initial three-plus points, it began to skyrocket suddenly.

Four points, five points, six points, seven points, eight points, ten points. Finally, it stopped.

"Seven point Potential Value, it’s not worth it…" said Garen as he looked at his gravely injured Totem herd with a heavy heart.

The body of the Resonance Hawk began to melt slowly, and instantly became a pool of red blood. Even the feathers were not left behind, as all of its remains flowed into the white puddle of the Bat’s blood, and dyed it bright red as well.

Garen looked at the first Resonance Hawk that had been hit by the Ultrasound Waves. Every trace of it had long disappeared, and now the only thing left was a pool of blood on the roof.

His heart continued to grow heavier.

"Two Resonance Hawks for a seven point Potential Value. This Potential Value of this White Bat is not as high as that of the blonde woman that Goth defeated. It’s obvious that it wasn’t as powerful as that blonde woman, but it was still so difficult to kill," said Garen as he inhaled deeply. "Looks like I’ll need to continue working harder…"

He ordered the Deep Swamp Croc to drag the White Bat’s corpse into a dark place to hide it.

Garen allowed the two Beetles to follow him, as they walked towards the main door of the silver-roofed building together.

At the entrance at the main door, the wooden door had been smashed open, and lay at the floor by the doorway. Inside the hall, countless dead bodies lay on the ground, and all of them were bleeding from all crevices.

Garen walked closer to one of the corpses and examined it closely.

"He’s been dead for over a day, and they aren’t any obvious external injuries, so he must have been killed by the White Bat’s Ultrasound Waves."

There were both male and female corpses, old and young. It seemed like they were having a meeting, before the White Bat’s surprise ambush got rid of them.

Garen stood up. "Such terrifying Ultrasound Waves, good thing I managed to order the Resonance Hawks to attack in time. And good thing the Resonance Hawks possessed frighteningly powerful strength, if not this would have ended badly."

He surveyed the corpses for a while, but could not find anything of importance.

Following the wooden spiral staircase on the left to the second floor, he saw a white-haired old man lying on the second floor corridor with his head separated from his body, and his neck nowhere to be seen.

The old man wore a white robe that had been embedded with an agate gemstone, and the light green agate had been soaked by his blood, causing it to be dyed in a shade of dark red.

Garen walked over and and searched the old man’s body with his hands, before quickly finding a white jewelry box.

This jewelry box had been pressed against the old man’s chest, making it obvious that it was an important item.

Garen took the box and got up, before opening it.

In the middle of the velvet layer inside the box, a little dark-spotted Stone Ball with a white base had been placed there.

Garen took the Stone Ball out and looked at it closely, before realising that the dark spots were not actually dark spots, but tiny words and symbols that had been written closely together, forming little black spots.

He looked at the inner part of the box’s lid where something had been engraved, and recognized it as Endor writing.

‘The Eye of Isaiah -- Behold the gaze of the one who stares.’

"Endor writing?!" Garen felt an illusion as if he had returned to the Secret Technique world. "This place apparently has a connection to the previous world!"

He held the Stone Ball, suddenly feeling as if the symbols of the War Shackles on his left arm were beginning to heat up.

"Looks like these are Solidifying Tactics. I didn’t expect it to be connected to the Endorian writing." There was no doubt in his mind that this item was used to train Obscuro Society Totem users before they embarked to seize items. Now that it had fallen in his hands, he wanted to use it immediately, to see the effects.

He rolled up his left sleeve, and pressed the Stone Ball against the silver arrow symbol.

Hiss…

The Stone Ball started to melt quickly, and fused into Garen’s left arm.

On the silver arrow shape near the front of his War Shackle, a new white-grey Stone Ball symbol had appeared.

Garen felt like his whole body had gained an additional, mystical strength. This strength felt like a warm hot spring that flowed through his body from his head to toes, like a snake that continuously slithered down his body. Every inch of his body began to feel warm.

He looked towards the War Shackle Pane at the bottom of his field of vision. On the first empty spot out of two, a Stone Ball symbol had appeared, ad below it was an explanation written in symbols and words.

‘War Shackles:

Effect 1 --

Eye of Isaiah: Originates from the mystical Endor civilization Tactics. This Tactic allows an individual to possess all-seeing eyes, as well as the ability to see more than the average human.

Ability: Totem users will be gain Exhaustion Ray ability once a day. Area of attack: Eyes.’

"Exhaustion Ray?" said Garen as he rubbed his eyes, vaguely feeling like both his eyes had undergone a slight transformation.

He looked at the Attribution Points in his Attribution Pane.

His Attribution Points that had reached their limits much earlier had now increased apparently!

His Vitality had increased from 2.76 to 2.82.

He remembered clearly that he had checked them before leaving, and his Attributes still remained at the initial amounts. Now, however, his Vitality had apparently undergone a new increase.

"Don’t tell me that the Solidifying Tactic can actually increase a Totem user’s physical fitness?!"

Chapter 309: Evolution 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

After he had received the Eye of Isaiah, Garen continued to investigate the house. Apart from some silver rumbs and some jewelry, there was nothing else left.

Only then did he leave the house, before looking at his remaining Resonance Hawk waiting outside, with its exhausted, injured body. His heart dropped for a moment.

"Go home!"

His will sounded more like an order.

Suddenly, the Deep Swamp Croc and Beetles began to move respectively, as they gathered around Garen and crawled outside.

The Resonance Hawk had calmed down now. Currently, it was facing some difficulties flying, and could only perch on the Deep Swamp Croc’ back as they travelled together.

On the road back, Garen took the opportunity to stop by to search the medicine shop by the street. This area was quite a distance from the inner city, thus many shops had yet to be looted by the inner city dwellers. Garen hid himself in his Silver Totem herd, and managed to find a lot of medicine easily.

The road back seemed to be experiencing a peak of monster movement. Every ten minutes, a large herd of a hundred over monsters flew closely over his head.

On the ground, a large group of Dead Babies could be seen. They crawled crookedly, looking in every direction for a member of their species to kill. The crawling movements of these purplish-red coloured baby herds made them look like purplish-red worms that continuously let out wailing cries.

Garen had no other choice but to let the Deep Swamp Croc and Beetles hide him from view. He used the Bone Shrinking Secret Technique to hide himself in a closed alley while the Deep Swamp Croc and Parasites blocked off the entry points to prevent the monsters from entering. This was how he evaded countless monster armies. However, this also led to a few Parasites being devoured by starving Dead Babies, while the three remaining Parasites huddled close beside the Deep Swamp Croc.

Once the Dead Baby army had passed them, Garen quickened his pace, and went in the direction of his villa to return. As the armies grew more frequent, Garen became such that he did not dare to linger anywhere for a long time, because he knew that it would be a serious matter if he exposed himself.

There was no guarantee that he would not attract a swarm of monsters as strong as the White Bat in the next minutes.

He hurried back to the villa, where it was completely silent, with only two Beetles crawling around, patrolling the perimeter.

The suburbs also had some additional nomadic Dead Babies, and another black-skinned monster.

The black-skinned monster had sharp spikes all over its body. It was as tall as a human and resembled an upright hedgehog, with bloodshot eyes and sharp, long black claws, as if it possessed a pair of iron claws. It walked through the streets with an arched body, looking like a camouflaged hunter.

Garen returned to his villa carefully and decided not to go out anymore. He let the Deep Swamp Croc and Beetles go out hunting by themselves, to bring back a corpse for them to feed on.

He entered his study and began to practice his Tactics tirelessly.

Many days passed, and within this period of time, Garen carefully allowed the Deep Swamp Croc to accumulate Beetles, and before he knew it, the number of Beetles had increased to ten. The Resonance Hawk’s injuries also began to heal in about ten days, and it was finally able to go out and hunt.

Garen allowed the Resonance Hawk to provide assistance to the Deep Swamp Croc in the beginning. It would endlessly capture stray monsters and give them to the Giant Croc to be used for its Parasites.

A few more days passed, and the number of Parasites finally reached twenty. This was the limit, as twenty Parasites would only need to eat once every week to be full. However, Garen was worried about their frightening consumption rate, and decided to just capture all of the stray monsters in the vicinity.

After two of his Resonance Hawks died, he attempted to turn the captured monsters into new Silver Totems for himself. Unfortunately, these monsters could not be empowered or controlled, apparently because they were highly resistant to this.

Garen finally understood why the Obscuro Society were unable to control these monsters.

Garen used the twenty Parasites as consumables and began to release all of them while constantly assessing the movements in his surroundings.

Immediately, a monster herd with less than fifty monsters nearby the villa, were marked by Garen. Most of these were new monsters. Recently, the density of these monsters had increased, and it was obvious that most of them had come over because they were attracted by the people in the inner city.

Although Garen’s hiding abilities had increased, he was still too afraid to come out alone, as the density of the monsters outside was too high, and there were no dead ends he could use to hide.

Under the cover of his Beetle herd, he returned to the ruins of the War Guild once again, following the tunnels to enter the passageway to the inner city.

The two guards from earlier had disappeared without a trace. Bloodstains could occasionally be seen on the floor, making it impossible to tell if they were still alive. Garen was shocked but not afraid as he walked along the road, before finally arriving at the inner city.

There was a tense atmosphere in the inner city, but Garen did not have any time for this, as his goal was Goth.

After waiting for another five days, Goth finally left again.

***************

Inside a white house in an unknown area of the outskirts of the city

Boom!!!

A shapeless figure caught a man in a black robe violently, as if a large shapeless hand had suddenly thrown him in mid air.

"Where is Ansella??!!" Goth’s eyes were bloodshot, as he growled at the man.

The corner of the black-robed man’s mouth was bleeding, and a frightened expression was plastered on face as he looked at Goth. "We underestimated you… Goth, stop looking for Ansella, when you finally find him you’ll…" Suddenly, he stopped himself from continuing.

"Then, tell me! What about the medicine? The medicine to cure Jessica!" In one movement, Goth pulled the man towards himself.

"Medicine…? It’s always been with Lord Ansella. That’s the one and and only antidote," replied the man quietly.

"Where is the real Ansella?! I’m not looking for a substitute like you," said Goth as he used all his might to suppress the anger inside him.

"I don’t know. I only know the whereabouts of another Ansella, but I don’t know if he is really the Lord himself. I’ve only been following his commands and carrying out his orders this whole time. It would be useless for you to kill me." The man’s face was indifferent.

"Tell me!"

The man told him an address softly, and watched as Goth walked out of the hall without turning back, disappearing into the dark night in the blink of an eye.

Finally, he could not handle it any longer, and flopped onto the floor to sit.

"Hehe… All my effort, even if they were destroyed, it would only last a moment..." His gaze fell unto a mercury puddle not far from where he sat. That was where he had spent many years painstakingly nurturing Core Totems and Secondary Totems. Suddenly, something flashed in front of his eyes, as he looked towards the shadows in the hall.

"Who?!"

The shadows quietened down for a moment, before a figure in a grey robe walked out slowly. It was golden-haired Garen, whose eyebrows were also lightly gold now, walking out of the shadows as he raised his chin slightly.

"Which level are you positioned in the Obscuro Society?" Garen asked the man quietly.

"Who are you?" said the man as he furrowed his eyebrows. "Why should I tell you?"

"Because of this," Garen sneered as eight Black Beetles crawled out behind him, before surrounding the other man. "Just because Goth didn’t kill you, doesn’t mean that I won’t."

"These are?" The man blinked, before recognizing what they really were. "Silver Totems?! Don’t tell me you’re…" He shut his mouth immediately, as a wry smile appeared on his face.

"You’ve managed to find me. I don’t have anything left to say, so just kill me then. I’ll just accept this as an atonement for all my previous misdoings."

Garen knitted his eyebrows together and glared at this man. He could tell that this man knew a lot of things. However…

He raised his head and looked at the outsides of the house. After hesitating for a while, he finally raised his hands.

Tch!

A black line flew past and nailed itself at the man’s forehead. It was a black piece of wood.

A shocked expression appeared on the man’s face, before he fell face up on the floor.

Garen turned and walked into the darkness, his grey robe billowing behind him, as he disappeared quickly through the window.

A few seconds later, a dark figure entered the main door slowly, and crouched beside the corpse.

"Dead already?"　

******************

Every time Goth went outside to look for the supposed Lord Ansella, it was unfortunate that he could only find substitutes or counterfeits. He killed some of them but could not bear to kill others and ended up letting them go, only for them to be killed by Garen who was always following from behind.

Out of these people, some of them were strong while others were weak. The strong ones were almost as strong as the blonde woman, while the weak ones were merely Totem users who only possessed single Totems.

Garen had followed Goth for over forty days straight, before Goth finally ran out of clues. The injuries on his body had also accumulated, and worsened in an instant. He became bedridden, and had no choice but to rest to heal himself.

Garen did not linger on the road, and decided to return to his villa in the suburbs. During this period of time, he had managed to perfect the Sight Sharing Tactic after much practice.

He opened the door and walked into the hall, before taking off his grey robe and passing it to Lala.

Within the days of constantly following Goth everywhere, during his periods of hiding, he once encountered a terrifying Giant Spider, and nearly got caught and turned into food.

However the rewards that he gained were also extremely satisfying.

He had managed to kill six lost Obscuro Totem users right and left, and had finally manage to obtain thirty-over points of Potential Value. Including the acquisitions that his Silver Totems had gained from their hunts, Garen now had almost forty Potential Value points.

He never once had so many Potential Points in hand before. Garen controlled himself and did not use them immediately, so that he could accumulate them in preparation for the moment he would finally use them to attack a Form 3 Totem.

"You’re back?" Out of habit, Lala took the grey robe from him and prepared to wash it immediately.

"Hold on." Garen stopped her. "Be careful during this period of time. The density of the monsters outside had been increasing rapidly. Don’t open the curtains carelessly, and don’t go to places where you can be seen easily. The clothes should just be dried inside."

"Got it," Lala answered immediately. Seeing that Garen had instructed her so strictly, she was now aware of the severity of the problem, and nodded her head in agreement determinedly.

"I’m going upstairs now. Don’t disturb me unless it’s an important matter," Garen instructed.

"Yes, sir."

Garen walked towards the study on the second floor. His footsteps beat against the stairs rhythmically, releasing a clap-like noise.

"This time, I need to obtain a Form 3 Totem first. If I don’t, I won’t be able to keep up with their strength for much longer. The monsters in my surroundings are increasing, and if I don’t have enough strength, I won’t be able to protect this house either."

Inhaling deeply, he walked into the study and shut the door tightly.

On the floor of the study, the Deep Swamp Croc began crawling across the floor quietly. Its little green eyes stared at its owner intently.

Garen walked over and crouched in front of it.

"This time it’s all up to you, No. 2," said Garen as he stroked the Deep Swamp Croc’s head and said to himself. This was a habit that he had recently adopted. Ever since Resonance Hawk No. 1 died in battle for him, he began to form this habit.

The Deep Swamp Croc crawled a few steps forward before turning its head to look up at Garen, unable to understand what he was saying.

Garen stood up and took two steps backwards.

"The forty point Potential Value that I’ve accumulated this time, must definitely be used to reach Form 3 in one go!" he said as he took a deep breath, before his gaze fell onto his Totem Pane.

Chapter 310: Evolution 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

‘Deep Swamp Croc: The Form 2 evolution of the Short-tailed Croc, Second Form Creature Totem. Upgradable, Probability of successful evolution: 25%. Potential Point cost: 500%.

Ability: Explosive Surprise Attack, Iron Hide, Parasitism.’

"Forty Potential Points, that would mean eight chances. I don’t believe that it can’t go any higher!" Garen’s gaze remained on the Deep Swamp Croc’s body. These were all the Potential Points that he had gotten from Goth. Goth was currently heavily injured, and would not be able to go out and hunt Ansella. Likewise, he would not be able to receive more Potential Points as well, and thus, these Potential Points were all that were left for him to use to gain more.

If he failed again this time, the only thing he could do would be to slowly depend on his luck.

"Begin!"

Garen stared at the Deep Swamp Croc’s icon for more than three seconds.

Suddenly, the icon shook vigorously and became blurry. Under Garen’s hopeful gaze, the icon began to become clear quickly again.

It was still in its initial form!

Garen’s expression remained, and he resumed the process.

Three seconds later, the icon became blurry again, and then instantly became focused, without any other changes.

"Again! I don’t believe this!" Garen’s gaze grew serious. Continue!

The third time!

Failure again!

The fourth time! Fail!

The fifth time! Fail!

The sixth time! Fail!

The seventh time!

The icon became blurry for a moment, and then became clear once again.

"Failure again…" A reluctant expression flashed in Garen’s eyes. Suddenly, he looked at the icon properly once it had become focused again, and his voice caught itself in his throat. "This is…??"

The Deep Swamp Croc’s icon disappeared, and was replaced by a new unknown icon.

Roar!!!

The Deep Swamp Croc could not help itself and roared softly, as its body began to turn into a dark brown colour. Its body started to expand as well, and it grew from its original five meters, immediately lengthening to six meters, seven meters, eight meters…

The Deep Swamp Croc’s body expanded and soon reached the maximum capacity of the room. Garen stared at it with his mouth opened and his eyes dazed, as it broke the window frame and jumped out of the window, falling into the garden below.

Its body expanded endlessly, as it had finally underwent many years of growth in this short space of ten seconds.

Garen stood at the window that had just been broken open, and bent his head downwards to look outside.

The entire ten meter length of the garden was now almost fully occupied by the Deep Swamp Croc’s body. It had grown to almost fifteen or sixteen meters in length, and possessed a seven to eight meter wide body, resembling a large dinosaur from the Jurassic period.

The strangest part was that its initial head had grown in a slightly crooked manner, while an extra clump of flesh had grown on its right shoulder. The clump of flesh kept growing rapidly, transforming into something new. Finally, it grew into a large head that was the exact same size of the Giant Croc’s original head.

Bang bang!!

It was unknown when an extra pair of large feet had grown from the Giant Croc’s abdomen, and were now violently stepping on the ground. The six legs supported its large body altogether.

Finally, it completed its evolution, and had transformed from its original crocodile-like image into a salamander. Its two heads began to snap their big mouths in opposite directions, as its large mouth roared silently.

Shh…

Both of its mouths exhaled a large gust of smelly wind.

Garen finally snapped out of his state of shock. He looked at the brown Dual Headed Salamander below and realised that his Potential Points had been well-spent.

This sixteen meter long terrifying beast crawled around in his garden, looking as if it were a giant dinosaur from the past. Its size appeared to be slightly bigger than the White Bat that he had encountered earlier.

"Too bad it’s not a Form 3 Totem, but a mere Silver Totem instead!" Garen lamented as he looked at the Totem Pane in his field of vision, looking at the icon section carefully.

The icon of the Deep Swamp Croc had really been changed into the Dual Headed Salamander’s image.

‘Dual Headed Salamander: The Form 3 evolution of the Deep Swamp Croc, Third form creature, Final form cannot be upgraded.

Ancient informative message: This terrifying beast existed in the ancient Behemoth era, which was at least twenty million years ago. They were the overlords of the amphibians, and possessed great strength as well as unmatched defenses. They generally live in dark, damp maze-like caves underground, and have a strong territorial sense, and are extremely possessive.

Abilities: Digging maze-like caves, Life Biting (Creatures that are bitten by its left mouth will unconsciously allow their life force to flow into the body of the beast, creating a healing effect)

Dragon skin (Strong dragon scales that are able to prevent damage inflicted by most weapons and sharp teeth)

Dragon roar (Loud roar that will cause deafness and dizziness in all surrounding creatures, in order for the slow-moving Salamander will be able to catch up to its prey and swallow them)

Parasitism: The Dual Headed Salamander can lay its parasitic eggs inside the bodies of its enemies, causing painful injuries, and finally creating a single-headed ferocious Form 2 Deep Swamp Croc. The rate of egg production is one per week.

"Shh!!" When he looked at the Deep Swamp Croc, Garen could not help but sigh in relief.

The Deep Swamp Croc could create Parasites on its own, while this Dual Headed Salamander could create more Deep Swamp Crocs.

"I’ve gained so much this time!" Garen looked at the strong Dual Headed Salamander below him, and felt his heart fill up with satisfaction.

Howl!!

In a faraway part of the sky, an ear piercing howl echoed towards him, sounding like a leopard’s roar.

Immediately, a terrifying Giant Bird with a wingspan of more than ten meters flew towards the Dual Headed Salamander quickly. The body of the Giant Bird was jet-black, and there were eight yellow claws growing out of its abdomen.

The Giant Bird was illuminated by a yellow glow that looked like a halo around its whole body, as it flew towards the Dual Headed Salamander.

The Dual Headed Salamander raised both its heads and roared at the Giant Bird fiercely. The head on its right side had on a fierce and cunning expression. It stepped backwards slightly, as if it was gathering up its energy, and preparing to snap at its opponent.

Garen hid himself behind the curtains, and subsided the overwhelmingly conspicuous smell of his blood, as he quietly watched the battle between the two large beasts. The Giant Bird in the sky was obviously a Form 3 Totem, and had come here because it was attracted by the Dual Headed Salamander.

The battle between both of the Form 3 beasts was something that he could not intervene anymore. He could only wait for the conclusion quietly.

The Giant Bird continued to circle the sky, as if it was looking for an opportunity to dive down and capture the Dual Headed Salamander, but was wary because it felt somewhat threatened. After circling for a while, it gave up on this initial thought of starting a battle. It outstretched its wings and let out an angry roar, before flapping its wings and flying far away.

The shadow of the Giant Bird’s wings flew over the villa instantly, as it disappeared into the faraway hills.

Shh!!

The Dual Headed Salamander arched its head upwards and let out an arrogant roar.

Garen stood behind the curtains, and looked at the Dual Salamander down below through the crack.

"Go out and hunt," he instructed through his will.

The Dual Headed Salamander bowed its head suddenly, and began surveying its surroundings from left to right, as if it was sniffing something.

Immediately, he confirmed the location, and his large body began to head towards the produce market near the suburbs.

Crash crash crash…

Its six brown large legs seemed like six stone columns as they stepped on the ground, causing some of the small stones and white bones on the ground to be stomped into smithereens.

Garen jumped out of the window, and stalked it stealthily from behind.

As the Dual Headed Salamander walked on the road, all of the other monsters ran to hide. It mattered not whether they were Dead Babies or Unihorn Lizards, once they saw the Dual Headed Salamander approaching from a distance, they acted like mice who had just seen a cat, and would run away frantically.

The Salamander did not linger for long, and ran straight towards the produce market, as the loud sound emitted by its footsteps caused some of the buildings to shake slightly.

Garen followed it and continued forwards. Instantly, a rectangular shaped market made up of large grey and white caravans appeared in front of him.

There were large holes in many of these caravans in the markets, and a few Unihorn Lizards were resting on the roofs. Meanwhile underneath the shade of the caravans, a few Unihorn Lizards that had glowing red bodies were busy chasing and fighting each other.

There were nearly a hundred Unihorn Lizards in this place!

"Don’t tell me this guy actually wants to provoke this herd of monsters?" A thought flashed in Garen’s mind. Out of all these Giant Lizards, even if one of them was Form 3 it would be scary to think that…

Before he could even finish his thoughts, he saw the Dual Headed Salamander speed up suddenly, as it ran towards the grey and white caravans and began to knock them down. It seemed like a large freight carriage had just crashed into them.

Crash crash crash!!

The Unihorn Lizards flew up frantically, as if they were a startled pack of birds, as they flapped their wings quickly and let out weird cries.

The red Unihorn Lizards also flew up, and dashed towards the Dual Headed Salamander. They were greatly angered by this monster that had disrupted their sleep. The red Unihorn Lizards began making housefly-like buzzing noises.

These noises caused the listeners to feel drowsy, and made their whole bodies exhausted as well.

They made this noise while they circled the Dual Headed Salamander, endlessly looking for an opportunity to fly down to attack it.

But the large difference in size, made them seem like a group of children forming a circle around an adult.

The Dual Headed Salamander stomped towards the front of the caravans, and both its heads turned upwards suddenly. It stretched its blood-red mouth open, and roared in both directions.

Woo!!

A loud sound wave caused the air pressure to increase, creating a shock wave that could be seen with the naked eye, that spread outwards towards its surroundings like a water wave. Most of the Giant Lizards were affected and were forced to the ground, causing a loud banging noise as throughout the ground where they landed.

Bang!

The Dual Headed Salamander used one of its heads like a warhammer to hit one of the red Giant Lizards, causing it to fall out of the sky mid air. It landed on the ground violently and the Salamander took a large bite out of it and crunched hard, causing fresh blood to spray all over its own face. The entire red Giant Lizard was snapped into two separate parts.

Garen’s mouth gaped opened, unsure of what to say.

He looked at the Potential Points at the bottom of his field of vision and noticed that there had been an increase of two points, but when he looked at his fearsome Dual Headed Lizard, he realised that it had won the battle effortlessly because of its opponent’s lack of strength.

The red Giant Lizard possessed strength that was equivalent to a Form 2 Totem. A Silver Totem was unlike a Primitive Totem because their essence was accumulated in their own bodies. On the other hand, the essence of a Primitive Totem was always stored with their Totem users instead.

This was another reason why he could gain Potential Points from killing Silver Totems, but would not receive any benefits when merely killing the Totem user.

The death of the red Giant Lizard allowed Garen to gain two Potential Points at once. This meant that it was equivalent to the lowest ranking Form 2 Totem user.

The Dual Headed Salamander let out a loud roar, causing the hundred over Unihorn Lizards to fall on the floor like dumplings. They became dizzy and were unable to get up for half a day, a sign that they had all been stunned.

Meanwhile, the red Giant Lizards struggled on the floor weakly as they tried to get up. Their resistance was slightly stronger, but they were still unable to get up, much less flee from here.

The battle ended right as it was getting started.

Chapter 311: Fantasy 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

The Dual Headed Salamander ate the Unihorn Lizards slowly, as if it were enjoying a snack. It went around looking for the ones it liked best, picking the fatter ones and discarding the skinny ones. Even the Unihorn Lizards, who were only slightly skinnier, were rejected.

In this short period of time, this ferocious two-headed beast had eaten six red Giant Lizards. Now a large herd of Unihorn Lizards were crawling on the ground before flapping their wings and flying away. Terrified, they ran in all four directions, not wanting to come near at all. The same also applied to the red Unihorn Lizard.

Seeing that it was impossible to catch up anymore, the Dual Headed Salamander then turned away and looked around at its surroundings, waiting for Garen’s next order. Both of its heads had long, snake-like necks that stood up straight in mid air, waiting to lunge forward and bite its enemies like a snake.

"Too fierce..." said Garen softly, unable to deny this fact any longer. Six red Unihorn Lizards would be equivalent to twelve Potential points.

This evolution would help him regain almost one third of the Potential points he had used.

Garen noticed that out of the red Unihorn Lizards that the Dual Headed Salamander had killed, one of the larger sized ones had not been fully eaten. There was a blood-red coloured egg sticking out of its abdomen and beating continuously like a heart.

This egg was slightly over a meter tall, and was giving off a light silver glow.

Garen leaped up and landed on the Dual Headed Salamander’s back. He found a hollow area to hid there, before using his grey robe to shield himself further.

"Go back. Now."

Now that he had a Form 3 Totem, Garen had the right to steadily replenish his Potential points, to ensure that his Impact Core Totems could be upgraded to higher levels. If he were to single-handedly nurture Core Totems to be evolved, he would only obtain a low percentage of the points he required, and even if he accumulated the few points he had over the span of a year, he would still only be able to reach Form 2 Totem levels. By then, he would have easily been taken out by the Obscuro Society and Terraflor Society already. After all, his old man Vanderman had offended the Obscuro Society, and those bloodthirsty bastards would never be satisfied with just leaving a true-born son like himself alone.

Meanwhile, the higher ups of the Terraflor Society also held a life-or-death grudge with Vanderman.

"Fortunately, I finally have some self-preservation skills now. Even if the Great War broke out and Iron Tank City fell into chaos, I would still be able to protect myself somewhat," Garen sighed in relief.

Form 3 Totems, even if they were merely Silver Totems, were still equivalent to those of Elite-level in various cities. In Iron Tank City, there were almost five thousand Totem users, and less than fifty of them were Form 3 Totem users, the undefeatables, said to be the ultimate pillars of strength.

In Garen’s case, he was considered to have only touched the threshold of elite strength.

As for the Grand Duke and Grand General levels, one would definitely need a Form 4 final stage Totem. It would also require various secret and powerful means, which could include specially researched non-animal type Totems. In some of the monster information books that Garen had purchased from the war Guild, they mentioned certain unusual organizations that possessed Aberration Totem types.

These powerful Aberration Totems were far superior to most Totems, as they were aberration types that were specially forged and nurtured for strong individuals. An example of this would be the Grand Duke’s Platinum Dragonhawk, the most suitable Core Totem for a Grand Duke.

The Form 4 Aberration Totem, which was also designated as Form 5, was also officially acknowledged as the strongest level that had ever existed in the whole world.

Some of the information that Garen had collected clearly proved that point.

Form 5 had always been the unspeakable secret of the aristocrats and the royal family. It was also the true reason for the foundation of their existence that had been passed down from one generation to the next.

Putting his thoughts aside, Garen tapped the Dual Headed Salamander’s back lightly.

Shh…

The Salamander exhaled impatiently while one of its heads looked up at the Unihorn Lizard with the parasite. Its footsteps echoed loudly as it stomped on the ground, as it ran in the direction it had came from earlier.

Perched on its back, Garen resembled a tiny grey moth, as he lay on top of it gently, keeping his eyes downcast the whole time.

On the road back, Garen heard the loud cries coming from the inner city once again.

Strange cries of monsters could be heard throughout the sky as the ground shook slightly, causing some decrepit houses to toppled down instantly. Explosion-like noises echoed endlessly, one after another, continuously without stopping.

All of the monsters in the surroundings had gathered here because of the noise, and Garen took the opportunity to jump up and stand on one of the Dual Headed Salamander’s heads so that he could look into the inner city from afar.

In the grey-white sky nearby the city, a large cluster of small black dots along with another cluster of small dots, mostly silver-coloured, were fighting with each other. Within the silver dots, a large Platinum Dragonhawk continuously punched through the air as it flew, as if it were a sharp knife continuously cutting the small black dots into smaller pieces.

Perched on the back of the Platinum Dragonhawk was a tall man in gold armor, holding a sharp spear. Every time he pierced his weapon through the air, another red Giant Lizard would be killed.

"Is that the Grand Duke?" Garen squinted while he travelled further away on the Dual Headed Salamander, as the war zone in the inner city became blurrier the further he went.

Garen jumped off of the Salamander’s head and landed on his back, before checking the current amount of Potential points. After the Deep Swamp Croc’s evolution, there were only five Potential points left, but after that he had accumulated another twelve points, increasing the final amount to the current total of seventeen points.

When he returned to the villa, the Dual Headed Salamander’s large body frightened the other Totems and caused them to prostrate before it, before Garen instructed it to dig an underground maze for itself in the backyard, to be used as its nest.

Garen himself jumped off the Salamander’s back, and leaped a few times before going into the broken window on the second floor, into his previous study.

In the period of time after that, Garen allowed the Dual Headed Salamander to go out and hunt every day, while he hid inside the villa and practiced his Tactics.

He had not expected that Lala would have been so well-behaved. Every time she heard a loud, terrifying noise coming from outside, she was too afraid to walk out of the door to take a look, and was now completely unaware of what was happening outside.

This made Garen change his initial thoughts of explaining everything to her. Instead, he had now decided that he was not going to explain anything that was unnecessary.

Garen spent about four or five more days in his villa, and evolved his remaining two Blue Back Lizards into Petrifying Lizards. After that, he began accumulating Potential points, in preparation to impact the Black-Striped White Tiger.

‘Core - Black-Striped White Tiger: First Form Totem, upgradable. Probability of successful evolution: 11%. Potential point cost: 700%.

Abilities: Tail Whip, Puncturing Crunch.’

With only an 11% success rate while requiring seven points each time, this cost was not something that most Totem users could bear. This was also the reason why the Black-Striped White Tiger had not achieved a successful case in so many years.

The cost was greater than most of the Totems, while the success rate was smaller than most of them. Moreover, information regarding post-evolution nurturing was inadequate, and almost impossible to find.

Only those who used the method of high Potential points to evolve their Totems like Garen could afford to pile on the evolutions.

The Dual Headed Salamander’s terrifying rank suppression made him invincible in the midst of the surrounding red Giant Lizard herds. Every time it left, it would roar loudly, and would always successfully capture at least five red Giant Lizards. Furthermore, when it cooperated with the Resonance Hawks and the Beetles, they would always return with at least ten of their prey.

**********

Five days later.

Garen stood in the garden of his villa and looked around. The sky above him was clean, and there were no monsters flying there. This area had finally become the Dual Headed Salamander’s territory. Ever since it scared that Giant Bird away, other large beasts no longer flew past here anymore.

He stood beside the red Giant Lizard that was currently the Parasite host, and crouched down to stroke the red egg gently. He felt a warm and hard sensation creeping up his hand, as if he was touching a burning piece of rubber.

The red egg would jump occasionally, following the regular and rhythmic beat of a heart.

Moments later, the jumping movement became more frequent, and became faster as well.

Pop! Pop! Pop!

Tiny cracks began to form on the surface of the red eggs.

Ka-chak!

A soft noise could be heard. It sounded like a watermelon getting sliced open.

The red egg split open from the middle, and out crawled a half-meter long, black-coloured baby crocodile. The crocodile opened its mouth and exposed its red tongue, which had a ferocious-looking tip, the most impressive of all its mouthparts.

"It finally hatched, the small-scale Deep Swamp Croc," Garen stood up and watched as the little crocodile began to chomp on the corpse of the red Giant Lizard that incubated it.

Only when the little crocodile had almost finished eating did he turn his gaze away, before looking at the Pane of the Black-Striped White Tiger in his Totem Pane, his eyebrows furrowing suddenly.

"In these five days, I’ve obtained over sixty points of Potential Value, but failed and lost most of them apparently. This Black-Striped White Tiger is impossibly hard to evolve…"

His mood began to darken. Sixty-three points of Potential Value, and a grand total of nine evolutions, who would have expected that he would not even succeed once. All of these had caused Garen’s bad mood. He had used all of his accumulated Potential points on this because he was hoping to reach the next level in one go. Unfortunately, the situation was not as simple as he had imagined.

"The monster herds in the surroundings have almost been all hunted to death. The Salamander’s influence is becoming too strong, and it’s only a matter of time before it catches the attention of the Form 3 monsters. I cannot let this continue any longer."

Garen looked at the all the Totems he currently possessed.

Silver Totems: Dual Headed Salamander, Resonance Hawk, Petrifying Lizard, Howling Wererabbit.

Primitive Totems: Neon Butterfly, Black-Striped White Tiger.

The Howling Wererabbit’s icon was greyed out, showing that it was probably suffering heavy injuries, or was already dead. In this terrifying and chaotic environment, in order to survive properly, one would need to rely on their individual strength.

Moreover, the evolution percentages of the Primitive Totems were frighteningly low. It would be more cost-effective to evolve the Silver Totems first. After all, once a Primitive Totem was broken or had suffered injuries, in the event that there were no Totem repairing skills, the strength of the Totem would just gradually decrease.

Although the Silver Totems possessed weaker powers, they could still rest and restore themselves like living creatures. The most important factor was that the probability of successful Totem evolution for Silver Totems was much higher.

Garen looked at all of his Silver Totems. The Petrifying Lizard was the only one that could be evolved, and its evolution percentage was still very high.

‘Petrifying Lizard (Unnamed): Form 1 of the Blue Back Lizard’s evolution, Second Form Creature Totem. Upgradable, Probability of successful evolution: 34%. Potential Point cost: 500%.

Abilities: Petrifying Gaze (Any enemy creature that makes eye contact with it will be affected by the Light of Petrification), Rapid Drilling.’

"A thirty-four percent probability, I could take a chance and try. I’ll go and take a look at the situation in the inner city first, before I begin to evolve the Petrifying Lizard. I definitely need more Form 3 Totems. Including the Dual Headed Salamander’s parasite, I could surely forge a Totem army!"

A plan began to form in Garen’s mind.

"I should go and check on Goth and the others, I’m not sure if the wounds that Goth had sustained from earlier have healed by now. Jessica’s illness should be cured too, right? The time taken for me to go there and come back should be sufficient for the Salamanders to regain their Potential points."

He had attacked the Black-Striped White Tiger so many times, but they always ended in failure. Garen wanted to take this opportunity to cool down, and subside his emotions as well. At the same time, he wanted to see how Jessica was doing. Although history showed that she was alive and well, he was still worried in case there were any changes.

Chapter 312: Fantasy 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

In the inner circle of the city.

The four block district in the inner city looked very depressing.

What was once a lively place filled with crowds was no more. Now, most of them were in bandages.

In the hospital, Andy and Goth were walking along the white corridor.

Both of them tried to hide their expressions as best as they could to prevent Jessica noticing that something had went wrong.

"Don’t worry. It’s fine. Everything will be fine." Goth patted Andy’s shoulder.

"Perhaps." Andy put on an unnatural smile.

As they arrived the familiar ward of Jessica, Goth opened the door and saw a man in grey robes peeling apples as he sat in front of Jessica.

He saw Jessica smiling at them, and he couldn’t think of an apt explanation.

As the man in grey robes heard the door being opened, he turned around and revealed a handsome, gentle smile.

"Goth, Andy, long time no see."

"Garen!!?? Goth’s voice was unusually high as he pointed at Garen in shock and disbelief.

Andy, who was at one side, was very surprised as well.

"Garen, didn’t you…?"

"Did you guys assume I was dead?" Garen started to laugh. "I was hiding in a corner of the ruins below and survived on the food I found inside. I took the opportunity to escape as the creatures were attracted by the battles in the inner city." As he told the story, he was very emotional and seemed to be traumatized as well.

Goth opened his mouth, as if he wanted to speak up, but he couldn’t utter a single word. He went towards Garen and gave him a big hug.

Andy was so happy he started to smile as well.

"It’s good to see you return unharmed."

Both of them were in a major slump due to Jessica’s unfortunate incident. Their moods lifted slightly as they found out that Garen was still alive.

Goth patted Garen’s back with a considerable amount of force.

"Don’t make me lose another friend again." He said in a deep tone.

"Why?" Garen was confused. "What happened."

Garen didn’t pursue further, and instead gave a smile to Goth, as he realized that Goth did not want to talk about it.

The three of them were talking about their recent life inside the ward. Jessica was lying in the bed listening as she smiled.

The group of four was finally gathered together again. It was worth celebrating, as none of them were absent.

Unlike the emotionless Goth, Andy could feel that Garen didn’t come back as what he had told. This person, who was once his partner had become more and more mysterious.

After the three of them chatted with Jessica, the three of them went to a restaurant together to have a proper meal.

Garen crossed his fingers as he placed them onto the table and calmly looked at Goth and Andy, who were sitting opposite him.

"Alright, can you guys tell me what actually happened?" He calmly stared at them as he asked in a deep tone.

The atmosphere had suddenly become heavy.

Goth and Andy’s expression was completely unnatural.

Garen noticed something was wrong and he stared at Goth.

"That’s not right! What happened to your left eye Goth!?" His voice was anxious. Deep in his heart, he had already recognized Goth as his friend. However, they were things that were out of his expectation, as if the history had started to change.

"Left eye?" Andy was shocked as he looked at Goth’s left eye. "What about your left eye?"

Goth awkwardly turned away.

"It’s nothing. I didn’t get any proper sleep lately and am feeling a little bit uncomfortable." He muttered as he tried to come up with an explanation.

"Don’t move!" He stood up and pushed away Goth’s left hand that was covering his left eye.

The took of them had a clear look at Goth’s left eye. That pupil’s color was not Goth’s original color, but a lifeless color of red. It was an ocular prosthesis.

Goth silently allowed his two friends to look at his left eye.

"It’s nothing big really. Actually… I was just trying to complete the quest. At least I survived. He muttered.

The atmosphere among the three had gotten worse.

Garen looked at Goth without saying another word.

"Goth, is it… because of Jessica?"

Andy gripped his fist as he lowered down his head.

Goth revealed a relaxing smile.

"My left eye was injured by a creature a few days ago and I lost my sight afterwards. Madam Madeleine had created an artificial eye for me. It’s nothing to be honest, since I can still see with one eye, right? Loosen up a bit you two. Relax. It’s a rare occasion that we are able to gather together and isn’t it good that everyone’s alright?"

Garen didn’t expect this to happen to Goth while he’s away for such a short while.

Although he wanted to rely on Goth to keep obtaining the potential points, he didn’t want to obtain it in such a fashion.

"Let’s talk about Jessica." He sighed as he sat down.

"Jessica is fine, trust me." Goth gestured his hand. "I found a doctor from the Duke Household to treat her. Have the people from the Duke Household ever failed in treating a sickness before? Don’t worry, I believe that Jessica will recover very soon, and the four of us, the Panther Group, will be together once again. We will then win the war, and obtain awards from the Duke, get knighted by the Royal family and reached the climax of our life as we become important figures. Hehe… It’s so exciting whenever I think of this!" Goth started to daydream as he spoke.

"You’re just daydreaming…" Andy couldn’t help but to give him a punch.

The food came just in time, and the atmosphere was no longer tense. The three of them started to talk about their current situation in life and future plans. Among the three, Garen was the one who was bombarded by the most questions. However, he was able to not raise any suspicions about his experience, as he had already prepared a scripted answer beforehand. He then added a few details along the way, and it was completely flawless.

Even Andy, who was calm and analytic, was fooled by him.

As they were eating their food, a young man in purple shirt came into the restaurant. This man was handsome and had an elegant smile. He scanned around the scarce restaurant and immediately walked towards Goth and the gang.

"Doctor Elielan!" Goth stood up immediately as he was the first one to notice him. "Why are you here? Come! Let’s eat together."

Andy stood up as well as he smiled wholeheartedly. After greeting him, he waved at the waiter to come and serve him.

Garen smiled politely as he had a good look at this purple shirted man. He could faintly feel a sense of familiarity from him.

"I am Garen, one of the members of Panther Group." He reached his hand out.

This man, Elilan smiled back as he reached out his hand and greeted Garen.

"I am Elielan, the specialist who will be responsible for Jessica’s sickness. It’s a pleasure to meet you."

"Same here."

With such a minor interaction, both of them knew that they were hiding something from each other.

Or rather, both of them could feel each other’s true personality with their own unique methods.

Both gently shook hands for a very brief moment.

Goth and Andy immediately asked about Jessica’s condition the moment Elielan sat down. On the other hand, Garen was sitting at one side as he listened to the three of them quietly.

They had their meal for at least an hour.

Goth and Andy invited Garen to sleep over at their place, but Garen denied.

After multiple large scale wars, the population of the inner city was reduced drastically, and most of the houses were vacant. Totem users didn’t even need a money to stay over at a place. They only needed to register from the clerk and they would be granted access to a space to live.

Garen casually found a decent house to live in.

The next morning, He went towards Jessica’s ward and found the ward doctor who was responsible for Jessica.

"The condition of No. 128 Jessica? Whom are you to her?" The doctor questioned Garen skeptically.

This middle aged female doctor, who was preparing to leave the office with a report was interrupted by this man in grey robe.

"Yes. I am her friend. It’s just that the rest of her friends are hiding her conditions from me and didn’t tell me the truth. I only wanted to know the truth." Garen nodded seriously.

"Her actual condition?" The female doctor frowned. "Patient Jessica has a rather strange sickness. It looks like a rare condition; we’re basically keeping her alive by using painkillers and anti-inflammatory drugs. However, she only has less than half a year left…" Perhaps the doctor had seen too many people passed away and her expression was rather regretful.

"I am very sorry. Jessica is a very wonderful lady."

"It’s okay. Thank you doctor." Garen’s heart sank, and he stood by the entrance, watching the doctor leave as she was welcomed by the nurses.

He walked towards Jessica’s ward with heavy footsteps.

It was early in the morning, and the sun wasn’t even up yet.

Garen stood at the ward’s window and looked quietly at Jessica, who was fast asleep.

"Reality and history had completely gone into different directions… What will happen next?" His emotions were fraught with complexity.

He opened the door and sat beside Jessica. Suddenly, she opened her eyes and looked at him calmly.

"Didn’t you go out with my brother yesterday? Why are you here this early?" Jessica smiled as she tried to get up from the bed.

"I came alone. I didn’t expect your condition to be so complicated. I have been wanting to check up your condition, since I have some medical knowledge that I have learned in the past." Garen answered softly.

"You have a medical background?" Jessica tried to laugh but couldn’t help herself and coughed.

"Alright. You should get some rest and have some faith in me." Garen used his finger and pressed onto Jessica’s pressure point at her neck.

It was a pressure point that supplied blood to the brain. He had learnt this when he was practicing secret martial arts. He can cure some sickness by pressing onto it gently and kill the person if he used an incredible amount of force onto the pressure point.

Everyone who practiced the secret martial arts had some basic understanding of a human’s anatomy. Garen, who stood at the peak of the martial art world, had immense knowledge in the human’s qi and blood circulation could be considered a medical expert.

Jessica yawned as she started to feel sleepy.

"Alright then. I’ll sleep a little bit more. I’m not sure why but I feel very sleepy all of the sudden." She laid down once again and was soon fast asleep as she covered herself with the blanket.

Garen stood up and looked around. Once he was firmed that no one was around, he took off Jessica’s blanket.

He placed his hand on Jessica’s head and a white golden aura slowly seeped into her neck as he tried to feel the blood circulation in her head.

He then checked her heart, internal organs and her physical condition.

After a thorough analysis. Garen sat down as he frowned.

"Her qi and blood circulation are normal, just weaker than usual. Her organs are completely fine as well. In fact, she’s much more healthy than average people. What is going on?"

Suddenly, rhythmic footsteps could be heard outside of the ward.

Garen immediately stood up. Although Jessica and Garen were good friends, Jessica was still Goth’s partnet, and he must maintain a certain distance towards her.

As he was about to turned around and leave, A mysterious silver light suddenly flashed on Jessica’s face.

"This is!!??" Garen stood still as he had seen this silver light somewhere!!

Click.

The ward’s door was opened.

Doctor Elielan who was in a purple shirt came in with a smile on his face.

"Eh? Sir Garen, you’re here too?" He was surprised to see Garen’s back.

Chapter 313: Reaching Out 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

Garen slowly stood up, to turn around and stare at Elielan, who was in a purple shirt.

The two of them stood against each other and didn’t say a word.

Garen quietly stared at Elielan, who was in front of him.

He was a young and elegant person. It was not just his shirt that was purple in color, even his pupils were dyed in dark purple, and he seemed to be carrying a slight smile on his face all the time. He stood at the entrance and gently closed the door as he stared calmly at Garen.

"Why the expression? Why do you look so serious?"

He gently and calmly asked.

Garen squinted his eyes and didn’t say a word.

Elielan walked towards Garen and sat beside Jessica.

"Perhaps you have some misunderstanding about me? Although I don’t know how I have wronged you, I apologize for my wrong doing."

He took out a pair of purple spectacles from his shirt’s front pocket and as usual, he had a calm smile on his face.

Garen was emotionless.

"I want to know…"

"Your visions were blurred, right?" Elilan cut off his speech. "It’s very common to have a blur vision early in the morning. Perhaps you should take some rest."

"Looks like you know…"

"You can leave now as I am about to examine Jessica’s sickness." Elielan cut off Garen’s speech once again.

Garen’s cheeks twitched as he stared at him.

"To understand her condition? Do you know her…"

"Can you please leave this room immediately? I need a quiet environment." Elielan did not change his expression as he raised his voice.

Raged, Garen pulled his collar.

Bam!

The chair was knocked down to the ground and he pulled Elielan up and placed him infront of him.

"It’s common courtesy to let a person finish his sentence. If you do not wish to abide by this rule, I will cut your tongue out and you’ll remember this forever.

"It’s best for you to let go of my collar." Elielan said calmly as he pushed his spectacles up.

"Are you threatening me?" Garen smirked. This feeling felt very fresh to him as he hadn’t been threatened by anyone for a long time. He was the one who had been threatening everyone all these while.

Boom!!

The ward’s door opened as Goth and Andy rushed inside the ward.

"Garen! Elielan! What are you two doing?!" Goth rushed in and took Garen’s hand away from Elielan’s collar as he stood in between two of them. "Let’s talk things out. Has there been any misunderstanding between the both of you?!"

He and Andy each grabbed hold of Garen and Elielan as they fear these two would start a fight.

"I came here early in the morning and saw Garen was already inside Jessica’s ward. He was sitting beside Jessica and was trying to cover her with the blanket. I wasn’t prepared to entered the ward yet but I had accidentally knocked onto the door and made a sound. He rushed towards me with rage and pulled my collar as he saw me. I don’t even know what his deal is." Elielan started to explain softly.

His words were extremely misleading.

Although he didn’t blurt out the obvious, his statements suggested that there was a scandal between Garen and Jessica. It was as if Garen came early in the morning to visit Jessica so that he could do something dirty to Jessica when they’re all alone.

Imagine a sick and gentle lady and a strong muscular single man in the ward together, and the man would lose his temper when was afraid to be found out, and decides to threaten the opponent by holding him by the collar.

Andy and Goth looked at Garen skeptically as he heard it. They couldn’t believe that Garen was such a person hence they needed an explanation from Garen.

"I came alone so that I can understand her condition. I know a little bit of the art of medicine. I wanted to see if I could be of some help. Jessica herself had even agreed to it." Garen replied calmly.

He didn’t mention that there was a possibility that Jessica was being empowered.

Empowerment was currently the Obscuro Society’s most confidential asset, and very little people knew about it. Furthermore, he wasn’t sure whether Jessica was really being empowered, hence he needed more evidence before making any movement.

He had thought of the possibility of empowering a human when he obtained the Derivator. The Obscuro Society must had done some research on empowering the human body since they had already tried it on so many animals.

However this required concrete evidence.

Elielan obviously was the key to understanding the whole situation.

""It’s just a misunderstanding." Goth obviously believed Garen’s explanation. He believed that his friend would not be seduced by physical appearances.

Although Andy was rather suspicious of his explanation, he believed that Garen would never harm his sister in any way.

Afterall, Garen had save his sister’s life. If he wanted to further his relationship with Jessica, he would have the best chance back then.

This incident was brushed off as Jessica woke up, and her explanation was the same as Garen’s. Everyone stopped commenting anything afterwards.

However, the relationship between Garen and Elielan had obviously worsened.

Because of Garen, Andy and Goth had obviously distanced themselves away from Elielan, since they were in a life and death situation together.

After leaving the hospital, Garen’s mood didn’t change for the better, so he left a message by his mailbox outside his house. After that, he went to his villa outside of the city through the War Guild’s underground passage alone.

He could feel that the history was currently deviating from what he knew, and was heading to a future that nobody could imagine.

*************

Garen, who was in his grey robe, was staring quietly at the big circular hole at the back of his yard.

The edge of the hole was stabilized by the black stone which looked like an artificial fence. It was a unique adhesive secreted by the dual headed salamander. It could be used to solidify soil, and he could use it to build his own underground palace.

Garen stood in front of the 7 to 8 meter hole, silently looking.

Cool breeze blew out of the hole and flapped his grey robes in the wind. The breeze was very cold and brought a faint stench along with it.

The hole was completely dark, and the end of the hole could not be seen at all.

Garen picked up a stone and threw it in. A faint echo of an impact was heard after 10 seconds or so.

"It managed to dig to such depths in such a few days?" Garen praised. "No wonder the dual headed salamander was able to create its own labyrinth."

Garen clapped his hand and yellow petrifying lizard appeared behind him.

"Go in and check it out." Garen pointed at the hole.

Szzz…

The petrifying lizard responded and slowly crawled into the hole, and soon disappeared into the darkness.

The other two petrifying lizards crawled to the spacious field behind Garen.

Garen looked at these two petrifying lizards with concern.

He wanted to check out the condition of the petrifying lizard as he came back from the inner city. To his surprise, the three petrifying lizards were bored to death, and decided to petrify most of the villa. The surrounding walls, floors, trees, windows, and even the bread that had just been freshly baked…

Most of the place of the villa had been completely petrified while he was gone for a few days.

Petrifying things seemed to be their hobby.

"Let’s see what will you guys evolve into." Garen muttered as he looked at the two petrifying lizard in front of him.

He set his sight onto the petrifying lizard’s icon on the totem’s pane.

‘Petrifying lizard (unnamed) : first evolution of blue backed giant lizard, a second form of totem being. Can be evolved. Success rate 34%, Potential points consumed: 500%.

Abilities: Petrifying Gaze ( Whichever beings who stared at their eyes would be damaged by its Light of Petrification, Rapid Drilling.’

"I have collected about 30 potential points within these few days in the inner city. Let’s try my luck."

He looked at the petrifying lizard, which was on his left, and had a rather rough and sharp back.

"Number one is dead. From now on, you’re called Copious Thorn."

The one on his right obviously had a very eye catching teeth.

"You’ll be called Big Teeth."

Garen casually named both of his petrifying lizards.

"Let’s evolve Copious Thorn first."

He set his sight upon the icon of Copious Thorn, and could see its name behind the icon had indeed changed to Copious Thorn.

He focused for three seconds, and 5 potential points immediately disappeared.

The icon shook violently and became clear again in the following three seconds.

"It failed… Again." Garen didn’t change his expression. He started to notice the laws of evolving using potential points. He might still be observing at the moment, but perhaps he could prove his it soon.

He set his sight onto the icon for the second time.

The icon went blurred for a moment and became clear afterwards. He had failed again.

"I knew it!" Garen started to had some idea. "Again!"

The third time!

The icon was blurred for a moment and he failed once more!

This was the fourth and last time.

Garen stared at the icon. Copious Thorn’s icon started to vibrate violently and didn’t become clear as fast as before. This effect lasted for at least ten seconds.

Sizz!!!

He suddenly heard the roar of the giant lizard. Garen immediately looked at Copious Thorn.

This petrifying lizard was struggling in agony.

It was rolling on the ground as dust flew into the air. It was as if its body had become boiling water and its body started to bubble up with blood. The bubble soon exploded and became a white substance that covered its skin.

At the same time, its body size expanded from four to five meters to five to six meters. It then continued to expand to seven to eight meters until it reached twelve meters! Its strong body had changed its color from brownish yellow to pure white, as it was completely covered by the white substance. The sticky substance solidified in a very short time, and become hard and reflective scales which covered the giant lizard’s body.

Garen had to take at least ten steps back to allow enough space for the lizard to evolve.

What was originally a yellow lizard had become a gigantic monster, pure white in color. It was as if time was accelerated, and one could see its growth with the naked eye.

Similar to the legendary elegant white dragon of the west, its back had a pair of bat-like humongous white wings. Its long tail swifted across the yard and produced a whirring sound from the friction.

Garen stared at the white giant beast which was eight meters high and spanned twelve meters long. He was filled with surprise and happiness.

Woah!!

This giant beast that resembled the white dragon had four thick legs, and its body was filled with streamline and muscular textures. Its neck was as long as a snake, and its head, which was in the middle of the sky, had a triangular white membrane that stood vertically like a shark fin’s when it surfaced out of the water.

The two humongous white wings gently opened up and the wild winds blew away the weeds in the garden.

It lowered down its neck and gently placed its head in front of Garen to show its loyalty towards Garen.

Chapter 314: Reaching Out 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

"This is really surprising…" Garen couldn’t believe it. It was as if he was witnessing a legend or a folklore. This gigantic beast in front of him looked exactly like the humongous dragon mentioned in the legend of the west.

"Oh right! Let’s look at its abilities!" He recalled the most important part and placed his vision onto the totem pane.

‘Petrifying White Dragon: third evolution of the petrifying lizard. Third form totem beings. An ultimate being that cannot be evolved further.

Ancient Genetic Information: This terrifying creature likes to petrify their prey before consuming them. They liked to consume different kinds of quality gemstones or jades to increase their physical attributes. During the ancient era, they stood at the top of the food chain in the mountain ranges. The time when they were active was unknown, and they had a strong interest in collecting items such as gems, diamonds, crystals and even strong creatures they have petrified. They had an unusually invested hobby.

Abilities: Agility Light of Petrification (Able to reduce the enemy’s flexibility in a huge area and reduces the joints’ sensitivity.This terrifying ability is why they’re not afraid of group battles)

Dragon Skin (The strong dragon scale that is able to negate the attacks from normal weapons and sharp bites)

Heart of Petrification (The white dragon has a total of three hearts. It can petrify the enemy with its breath. It could also use either of its two hearts as a petrification grenade that covers a wide area of effect. Naturally, this would hurt its body)

"The Petrifying White Dragon… It’s incredible!" Garen walked towards the white dragon’s head, which was as tall as him. The huge dragon eye was black with a silver vertical pupil in the middle.

He reached out his hands and gently caressed the white dragon’s head.

The sensation was cold and hard, similar to touching a snake’s scales or a sturdy rock.

Garen suddenly had an idea that he had not thought of before as he looked at the beast in front of him.

"If it is the legendary giant dragon… Then… Will its blood give a human endless and mysterious effects just like the legend said?"

With this thought in mind, Garen had a sudden urge to find out whether the legends were true or not himself.

"Stand still and don’t move!" He commanded.

Roar!

The white dragon roared softly, raised his head up and didn’t move afterwards.

Garen walked to the side of its body and took out a black dagger that he always brought along with him.

"I believe I won’t be able to break its scale." He suddenly recalled that he would not be able to harm a totem without the totem light’s properties in his attack. He could probably damage a form one totem with his strength but what was infront of him was a form three totem.

Immediately, he willed.

The dragon and him were waiting at the back yard.

Time was passing every second.

Lala, who was in the villa, tried to see the situation outside multiple times. However, she understood Garen’s order and didn’t come out of the villa by herself. This girl was either very timid or very smart.

She knew what she needed to know and need not know.

She sat on the sofa in the living room as she read the historical novel in silence. She ignored the roar of the white dragon outside, and continued flipping her book as she read.

She already knew that she knew too much of Garen’s secrets, and to leave the mansion would be impossible. She was glad that she was able to rely on a strong person during the chaos. What made her feel even more glad was that this strong person did not demand her at all.

She was very satisfied that she was able to pass her days like so.

Soon, dense and strong footsteps could be heard outside of the villa.

That beast with the big head had returned.

Lala placed down the book and thought that she couldn’t avoid seeing a glimpse of that beast through the window.

Its skin was dark grey, and part of its body had completely blocked the whole window. The scale on its body kept moving, and soon sunlight would come through the window once again, after the the beast moved away.

"What kind of a figure have I encountered?" She started to feel curious. She was constantly surrounded by weirdly shaped beasts and insects, and the whole villa seemed to have become a base and a nest for monsters.

Only that man could casually enter and exit this place.

************

At the backyard

Garen silently watched the dual headed salamander run back from afar. The backyard could not accommodate two huge monsters, hence the dual headed salamander had no choice but to knock over the surrounding walls so that it barely stood beside Garen.

Two huge beasts, A pure white colored one and a dark grey one. Garen couldn’t be seen as he was completely squeezed in the middle.

The body of the dual headed salamander was slightly larger than of the petrifying white dragon. Two of its head reached towards the petrifying white dragon’s body and started sniffing at it. It was as if it was curious as to how this huge beast appeared and could it be eaten?

Roar!

The petrifying white dragon roared fiercely at it as white mists started leaking out of its mouth, ready to fire its petrifying breath.

Garen stood in the middle and willed both of them into a relationship. After that, he quietly ordered the things that he had thought of beforehand.

The Petrifying White Dragon reluctantly took a few steps back and opened its right wing to reveal his muscular side body. He then moved to the mouth of the dual headed salamander.

Munch!

The dual headed salamander took a huge bite at the petrifying white dragon’s body without holding back.

In a blink of an eye, a big amount of white colored blood gushed out and landed into the small hole underneath it and it took no time to fill up the small hole.

The dual headed salamander retracted its heads and made some noises to show dissatisfaction. It seemed like something went wrong to its mouth and was slightly uncomfortable.

The petrifying white dragon blew the white mists onto its wound and the blood immediately clotted.

Garen then squatted just beside the pool of white blood.

He quietly looked at the White Dragon’s blood as he could smell a very strong stench coming off of it.

The White Dragon’s blood looked just like an expired rotten milk, with bubbles kept coming up to the surface. As these bubbles popped, the released a huge stench.

He extended his index finger and gently dipped it into the white colored blood.

An intense pain travelled through his index finger.

Sizzle…

His index finger’s skin swiftly tightened up.

Garen pulled back his finger and had a look at it. What was an originally white skin had become slightly grey, as if it was petrified.

"What a powerful corrosion!" Garen moved his finger. He had deactivated the Totem Light’s defense on his own and tried to test the true effect of this dragon’s blood.

"Looks like it still can’t be used." Garen gave up on the idea of bathing himself in the dragon’s blood. It was obvious that part of his finger had been petrified. Perhaps dragon blood was beneficial to a human body, but it was definitely not the case for the blood of the petrifying white dragon.

"What a pity…" He looked at the two beasts beside him. "Go hunt, both of you. Kill anything that may threaten our territory’s beasts."

The Petrifying White Dragon roared softly and opened its wing to soar elegantly up in the sky as four of its limb moved forward. A white halo could be seen surrounding its body, and as it flew higher and further, it soon became a small white dot.

The dual headed salamander roared softly.

All of the sudden, two crocodile heads emerged from the shade in the vicinity of the garden and kept making noise. The sound of insects crawling about could be heard as well.

These parasites were at least thirty to forty in number and it was a nest of an army as they marched.

As Garen raised his head and looked at the white dragon up high in the sky, he felt vibrations coming from the derivator which he always brought along side him.

He immediately took out the Crystal Derivator.

This red colored ball was throbbing in silverlight, and a crystal clear message appeared in the center of the ball.

‘Incoming message from the outer realm, do you want to connect?’

Garen was shocked.

"A communication request?! Does that mean there are people with Derivators nearby?!" He recalled that this crystal ball was a terminal used by the Obscuro Society to control the Silver Totems, so it was impossible to not have a communication functionality.

Garen could feel that there was a possibility that he would lose the Derivator.

He hesitated for a moment as he looked at the communication request.

‘The communication level had increased to emergency. Do you want to accept?’ The crystal ball changed its sentences and a yes and no choice appeared at the bottom of the crystal ball.

Garen placed his grey robe on his head and covered his face. He then squatted down and made a rough mask by cutting the solidified white dragon’s blood with his heads. He placed it onto his face, even his eyes were covered.

After these preparation, Garen then reached out his hands and gently pressed ‘yes’.

In a blink of an eye, the crystal ball produced red ripples and a woman with a deep tone could be heard.

"I didn’t expect there is still an Elemental General in the Iron Tank City. Didn’t those damn monsters had kill all of you? This is very rare." He paused for a moment. "Do you not speak? Looks like you’re the legendary Jess."

"It’s obviously him since I have already found Ania and Jeffs’ corpses, and they looked terrible! Hehe." The teasing voice of a man could be heard, "Where are you now Demetrius? I am at the Ender Kingdom managing the situation. These monsters had destroyed part of the nests. If not for me, there would be no survivors at all here."

"I am currently at Canbria. The situation is complicated but manageable. How about your side Jess? Your side is very crucial; the Grand Duke’s White Dragonhawks are not easy to deal with." Demetrius asked Garen.

"My side?" Garen replied calmly. "It’s alright. Everything is fine and smooth. It’s just that most of my underlings are dead." He purposely said with a strange and hoarse sound.

"What happened to your voice?" Demetrius asked suspiciously.

"I have hurt my throat. Took me a long time to recover." Garen replied emotionlessly.

"The current situation is like so. I could only manage to get in contact with eleven generals at the East Continent. Based on the current positions we are in, three of us will be formed as a team." Demetrius explained simply. "I didn’t want to contact you guys as well. However, I have to request for assistance from you guys, since it is an emergency."

Chapter 315: Jess 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

"Urgent situation? Is this not urgent enough? Ever since the meeting, we’ve been running into nothing but trouble. What can be more urgent than this?" the man’s voice dropped an octave.

Demetrius didn’t bother with him, and continued talking,"Now there are two things from HQ. First, is the mass amount of mutations in the experiments destroying the research bases. They want us to be extra careful, they even sent a report about a specific beast that we should watch out for. Secondly, a traitor has escaped from Obscuro, they want us to find and arrest this person. He was last seen within the three of our jurisdictions. From what we know, he sustained severe burn injuries and has mostly blacked skin."

"They only seek us out when they’re in trouble," the man scoffed.

"Don’t get all grumpy Andora, your mission is the most important. The King of Ender is a rare master of Aberrations. You can’t just understand him with biology or chemistry anymore. Make sure you don’t mess up when the time comes," Demetrius sounded unhappy.

"Alright, that’s it. I hope you two will keep these two issues on your mind. Also, Jess, if you can, HQ wishes that you acquire the treasure in the Grand Duke’s mansion," Demetrius added.

"Treasure?" Garen was piqued.

"It should be called the Heart of the Dragonshadow or something. Along with my Crown of Thorns, it is a special type of treasure," Demetrius said coldly,"Alright, I have other business to tend to. We’ll talk again when we have time."

With a loud clapping sound, the voice cut off.

"I should get going too. Let’s keep in touch Jess. Honestly, among the three generals, you’re the more likable one. If the Grand Duke is too much trouble, I can come help you out," Andora said coldly and cut off too.

"Thanks."

Garen watched as the Crystal Derivator slowly turned back into its original red, and a short text indicating the signal had been cut off, then only he sighed a breath of relief.

It was only a few short minutes, but they were enough to have Garen sweat all over.

"Elemental General… If there are only three in Iron Tank City, then these three must be considered amongst the top masters in the city. Combined, they might even be able to topple the city’s order. Also, who would’ve known that those mutants in the wild were actually runaway experiment subjects of Obscura."

Garen carried the Crystal Derivator, something that he used to rely on, now felt dangerous.

"I need to find a way to eliminate the threat quickly," He planned to understand the Derivator properly.

After a moment of thought and murmuring, Garen let the Dual Headed Salamander take most of the bugs out to collect some potential points while he sulkingly walked back to the villa.

In the next few hours, Garen stayed in the villa trying to figure out the Crystal Derivator’s functions and purpose. This was top priority for him as it was related to his greatest energy source, so he put everything aside; even on Goth’s side he only left a letter saying he had to go away for a while, and warned him about Elielan.

After ten plus days.

Finally, Garen found something new in the Crystal Derivator.

Something about the command chain.

***************

In the scarlet colored study, Garen sat beside the broken window that had been broken by the Petrifying White Dragon, which was also in turn partially fixed by the Petrifying White Dragon’s solidified spit.

Garen sat with his back against the book rack facing the study table. On his left was a mattress filled with all sorts of notes and rolls of paper. Under his feet were a ton of loose paper on the carpet.

There was a horrible stench in the room as well.

Garen just kept staring at the Crystal Derivator on the table, continuously fondling it with his fingers.

Finally, the derivator glowed a soft red. In the middle, a line of Kovitan text appeared.

"Would you like to connect to the derivator network?"

"Do I have control of all subordinate derivators?" Garen suddenly understood, the derivator could issue and accept commands using voice, so he spoke back in Kovitan.

"All derivators can be controlled by superior derivators. Lord Garen, your derivator is a "General Level" derivator, your immediate superior is the marshal level, and your immediate subordinate is the colonel level."

"Serial number: 0032gcr, your derivator is the east state’s 32nd. There is a total of 10 derivators in the Kovitan region. Your rank is General, under you there is Lieutenant General, Brigadier General, Colonel, Lieutenant Colonel, Major. Please select which rank you would like to command. You may modify the selected user’s derivator usage privilege at your own will."

Upon discovering this, many inexplicable things before made sense now.

Garen stared at the five different choices floating in the interface.

"Since I can modify their usage privileges anytime, that probably means that the people above me can do the same to me as well. I better be careful."

He squinted his eyes, feeling even more threatened than before.

"I need to find out how the derivator controls its users. Those experiment mutants should’ve been under control but yet they managed to shake loose the influence. How did they do that?" Garen suddenly thought of the traitor mentioned by Demetrius.

"Perhaps I can find an answer there," he suddenly had an epiphany,"Let me see what I can do with my subordinates for now."

He tapped the derivator softly.

"Lieutenant General rank selected, you have two subordinates that can be contacted,"

Two names appeared on the derivator.

"Lieutenant General Helis, Lieutenant General Kuiman."

Both of the names were grayed out, and there was a text saying "not contacted" behind their names.

Upon reading that, Garen remained expressionless and continued to scroll down to the next row of names. Suddenly five names popped up, two of which were grayed out, and three were red with a row of text saying "contacting…" behind their names.

Garen’s heart skipped a beat.

He reached out and tapped on the name of one of the brigadier generals.

"Brigadier General Harry," he said softly,"where are you now?"

The other side hesitated for a moment before replying,"General Jess? I am now based out of White Dew City. The Governor’s house here has been completely overrun. I don’t know what HQ wants out of this, how is any of this relative to our initial mission?" It was the voice of a young man,"I don’t know understand why we’re dragging innocent people into this mindless war."

"Do not question the actions of the ones above us," Garen replied in a coarse voice.

"You share my thoughts too? I am so honored!," Harry seemed surprised,"I always knew that among the Three Generals, you were the warmer one!"

"I would like to ask you a question, could you answer me honestly?" Garen asked softly.

"Please ask away," Harry’s mood seemed to have improved.

"About the White Dragonhawk plot in the Grand Duke’s place, how much do you know?" Garen quickly asked about the situation closer to him.

"White Dragonhawk plot? This is under the purview of General Jeffs, I am not privy to the details of it. However, I am particularly close to General Jeffs’ Brigadier General Ally, I can ask her."

"Thanks, that was my first question, now for my second question; could you tell me how many men do you have under you right now?" Garen’s eyes seem to reflect worry upon asking this.

"Subordinates? Under me? Immediately beneath me there are 32 Colonels, 109 Lieutenant Colonels, 188 Majors. We practically control all of White Dew City. Do you intend to move about a large amount of manpower? Sorry, I don’t mean to question your intentions sir." Harry quickly changed his words.

"You didn’t lose many men?"

"Thankfully the derivators came in time, else it would’ve been a mess." Harry replied with certainty.

"Lastly, there has been a traitor recently that escaped from HQ. He is charred from top to bottom, so his skin is black, keep an eye out for him," Garen passed on orders from above,"Alright, how about this: if I ask of you to get me ten third form totems, do you think you can do it?" He was now directly trying to test the abilities of this man.

Harry hesitated.

"Third form totems would be a bit tricky. From what I am able to do now, I can control two at most and they’re both animal forms. The rest you will have to check with the other Brigadier Generals. You usually don’t ask much, why the sudden interest? Oh, I’m sorry, I’m overthinking again."

"Mm, that’ll be all," Garen cut the line.

After this, Garen tried to contact the other generals and colonels, some were just silent, seemingly either dead or that they broke their derivators.

One Lieutenant General, three Brigadier Generals, twelve Colonels, thirty-eight Lieutenant Colonels, and over two hundred Majors, all directly under him.

By ‘directly under him’, it meant that these men would only take orders from him and nobody else.

They were practically his own private army now.

Garen contacted as many of his subordinates as he could, these would be his men now.

After he was done contacting all of them, the sky was started to turn dark.The sunset light shone into the room, illuminating it with its golden glow, emanating an aura of warmth.

He put down the derivator.

He finally understood two things.

"The first, is Jess’s old image," Garen took out a piece of paper and with expert mastery and control, he quickly sketched out the shape of a sillhouette.

Chapter 316: Jess 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

The strange floating man who was dressed in a black robe as on the paper suddenly became clearly visible, like an odd image.

He did not have legs, his robes covered him from head to toes. From the front, only his pale and delicate jaw could be seen.

"From the subordinate’s description, it seems like this Jess is a somber figure - suspicious, untraceable, huge and less bossy. No one knows his specific strength, nor has anyone seen his body type." Garen described Jess’s outlook in details with the information he retrieved.

"These characteristics of him are very useful for me to pretend to be him," Garen kept his pen. "Following up is the second point; to estimate this as a whole, even though General Jess has lost his strength, but if he can directly or indirectly control over fifty heads of third form series of animal totems, it would at least be over a hundred heads for the form two totem. This is a huge power. If Jess’s strength does not excel the Grand Duke’s, then it is equivalent to the entire Iron Tank City’s power. This kind of power is still secretly in the plan, don’t know how many totem users are part of the Obscuro Society in Iron Tank City but it’s even tougher if we don’t want the city to collapse…"

Garen got unusually scared at the thought of it.

However, Obscuro Society’s strength was really overwhelming even with the monster’s leftover powers after the mess. If it has fully recovered, the estimate would be much stronger.

But this doubt momentarily floated on top of his head - unless the hole he first went in with Goth was really a Form Two totem users’ residing tunnel?

Merely Form Two totem users but they can protect the General’s exceptional derivator?

Or let’s say even if Obscuro Society has the confidence, did they think no one would be able to unlock the derivator in three tries?

Garen reminisced the last time the shooting white spirit light exploded. That explosion startled the whole of Iron Tank City; the shooting spirit light was much more gleaming than the lighthouse but only the furnace inside exploded.

What kind of factory furnace had such a huge force?

One doubt after another appeared in his heart.

"By the looks of it, Goth’s underground experience wasn’t that simple," he seemed to have made a conclusion.

"That’s it. Now, we should focus our energy on solving the derivator’s control’s hidden problem," Garen diverted all his attention onto the headquarter’s traitor. If this person could be found, maybe then he would be able to provide some news and reports.

"Just in case, try your best to accumulate the Dual Headed Salamander’s and Petrifying White Dragon’s hunting potential points to its fullest for me. As well as before lifting the hidden problem, the potential points cannot be put on the Silver Totems."

Garen made his decision.

History has already deviated. He must then face the what’s to come next, on his own.

Garen’s potential point also altered as time changed, increasing more and more as days passed. Once he triggers the stronger third form monsters, he would then mobilize the department to capture the monsters. If it was really strong, then he’ll avoid it for a moment. By going back and forth with it, his potential point would slowly increase to an objective point.

Garen used it all up on the revolutionizing the White Core Tiger. Unfortunately, throwing in hundred over points did not even reveal a single bubble. This made his mood uncomfortable.

The surrounding bunch of monsters has slowly been wary towards Garen’s mansion. They started gathering, it was getting more and more difficult to brush up potential points. Often he would bump into two or three third form monster, surrounded by a huge herd of second form monsters and first form monsters.

One after another third form monster formed a huge army, segregating the whole outer part of Iron Tank City.

Garen occupied the east side of the city, six heads of the third form strange birds occupied the city’s west, the north and south side have been occupied by appalling numbers of more than hundred heads of third form monsters. Moreover, the number has been increasing. This force belonged to Iron Tank City’s main suppressor, the monster’s army. There were even an extremely tough Three-eyes Black Panda among them - this monster’s body was humungous, with thirteen meters tall and twenty meters wide. Its speed ability was exceptionally strong, around its body lingers a huge scale of odd mauve emmanuel. These type of emmanuel-covered-body monsters possessed a dramatic increase in speed ability. Not only are they not afraid of death, but each one who defeated it completely their senses.

The Three-eyed Panda and the Grand Duke’s Petrifying White Dragon have been confronting each other for a long period of time; they both fear each other. But the human strength of Iron Tank City got weaker each time they fought; with that, the lesser they fought. Instead, the monsters fought more and more.

Basically the Three-eyes Black Panda did not even need to raise a hand for the Grand Duke to show his moves. That was the only way to prevent the defense ring from receiving too much impact.

Garen has many times seen the fight between the Black Panda and the Grand Duke from the east side of the city.

The Black Panda jumped on the top moving building, looking far and wide. The surrounding buildings and he were like blocks of wooden houses - with a push, it would be destroyed; with a knock, it would fall.

On the side, Garen couldn’t help but continuously piled potential points on the Black-stripped White Tiger. Primitive totem and silver totem’s evolution had their differences, in which even he couldn’t see through clearly.

And in the city, the situation was getting worse.

Garen was not able to meet with Goth and company the few times he was in town. Jessica’s health condition has been miraculously improving, it seemed to have a very strong turning point.

On the other hand, Goth and Andy had both participated in defense ring against the outer city’s monster battle.

Especially Goth, he was nowhere to be seen.

*********************

Inside the hospital ward, Jessica wore a white patient-uniform while sitting on the bed, gently rubbing her stomach and her face showed a slight trace of happiness.

Garen sat at the side, peeling her apples.

A faint morning sunlight shone on the both of their right sides, the floor showed the shape of the window with white spots.

"When did you realize that?" Garen lightly asked, as he continuously peeled the apple skin.

"About a few days ago. That time, I felt like throwing up and after the doctor came over for a checkup, I gave him a huge scolding." The delicate face Jessica showed at first suddenly became gentle and sweet.

"Goth, that bastard is really not genuine." Garen shook his head, "Even with your health, he was still thinking about it… "

"Don’t blame him, it’s me." Jessica interrupted Garen, "I was the one who wanted to give him a child." Her face carried a carried a small hint of a smile.

Garen carefully hid his observation of Jessica’s complexion, he suspected that Jessica must have been empowered.

Goth pushed open the hospital ward as he saw Garen sitting by the side of the bed, quietly peeling an apple. Ever since he received the news about Jessica’s pregnancy, he immediately rushed back from the front line, to witness it for himself.

"Garen?!" He fiercely patted Garen’s shoulder as he was a little shocked.

"Andy, Elielan and I were just talking about you yesterday. Elielan said he blamed you wrongly the last time and wanted to apologize to you but he couldn’t find you. I didn’t think that I would see you here. What’s up? You’re here to see Jessica?"

"No, I’m here to see you." Garen stood up and split the apple into two; one for Goth, and one for Jessica.

"Let’s go. Let’s give Jessica some time to rest, we can go out for a chat," as he pulled Goth out of the room without explanation.

"What’s the issue? What’s the rush?" Goth unsatisfyingly said as he gnawed on the apple. After Garen pulled him out of the hospital ward, the two of them found a quiet corner and faced each other.

"Alright, can you say what’s the issue now?"

"What is wrong with Jessica’s health?" Garen paused, and then asked again, "She looks to me as if she’s much better than before"

Goth relaxed slightly and smiled.

"Even though there is no way she could fully recover, but now, it should not be the same as it was half a year before. You can relax."

"Last time." Garen appropriately said his next phrase, "The last time, there was actually a reason behind why I told you to be careful of Elielan."

His face, along with Goth’s became serious.

The air slowly got a bit heavier.

Garen paused. "I’ve once come across a type of Obscuro Society’s special tactic - the name was Empower. It is a type of special method that could control living thing’s behavior."

"What are you suspicious about? Empower? Jessica has been Empowered? That’s what you wanted to say right? That you can rest assure, Elielan has mentioned it before. We have also come across similar Silver Totems; the characteristics are quite clear, Jessica should be fine. After you reminded me the last time, I’ve checked. Don’t worry!" For a moment, Goth relaxed and uncaringly patted Garen’s shoulders, "you’ve been thinking too much, you should relax a little. Don’t always be suspecting of everything."

Garen frowned. As he observed Goth’s expression, he also doubted his own decision-making skills.

"After empowering, you have to destroy the controller thoroughly. Only that can you lift the empower off the living being."

"Destroy the controller?" Goth pondered.

As he achieved his goal, Garen did not say more. Instead, he pulled away from the topic and asked about the city’s current situation. Knowing that Goth and the Grand Duke have now met, he felt happy for him, from the bottom of his heart.

Once again, the two parted in their own ways - Garen was focused on capturing the Obscuro Society’s escaped fugitive. Being able to escape from the headquarters to here, he must not be an easy person. If it was the original Elemental General Jess, then maybe would not fear each other. However, he’s only a fake good now and his abilities are more or less the same as the General’s. If his identity was exposed, he believed even the General could not beat him.

Not to mention the Lieutenant above, General’s level.

Back at the mansion, Garen was able to concentrate on practicing his tactics. Finally, he was able to sight share this skilled tactic exercises, which can be used for practical purposes.

He sat by his mansion, the parasitic beetles under his hand spread out and crawled towards all directions; the Dual Headed Salamander controlled the Four Headed Deep Swamp Croc and commanded over hundreds of parasitics bugs, as they spread out everywhere.

After putting in over a hundred potential points, the Black-striped White Tiger seemed to show a bit of movement. Even though the evolution failed, but it’s body surface started to show circles of much thinner stripes; it looked as if it was a White-striped Black Tiger. Its body size was gradually getting bigger too, developing in the direction of a Behemoth.

This gave Garen more hope.

There was only a result when over a hundred potential points were given, but this made him let out a sigh. By witnessing the difficulty level, he finally understood the reason why after so many years, no one had been able to successfully nurture a second form Black-striped White Tiger.

Every minute, every second was washed away.

Garen took all his potential points and used it on the Black-striped White Tiger’s body. The parasitic beetles' army became increasingly more and it has triggered the attention of the surrounding third form monsters. When the number of beetles hit two hundred, Garen finally stopped the parasites from forming. He only allowed the Dual Headed Salamander’s parasitism on the Deep Swamp Croc. At the same time, he relied on his Sight Sharing tactic; continuously using the silver totems to control the surrounding situation,

As time passed, the monsters around increased in numbers. The high-level monsters became more and more. In a short period of two months, the third form monsters increased by ten heads.

Garen stayed in his remote mansion, even he felt the downpour in the city will cause a sense of terrifying repression.

Chapter 317: Defector 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

Screech!!!

A huge white dragon flapped its wings slowly, creating large, whistling gusts as it glided through the grey skies.

Garen, who was in his gray robes, gazed at the Petrifying White dragon gliding by as he stood by the window. His focus didn’t change at all as he seemed lost in his thoughts.

He was standing in a new study room.

The room was entirely white, including the walls and floors. The wall cloth and carpets smelt like newly washed, moist laundry.

After standing for a while, he turned and looked at Lala who was rearranging things.

"Have you moved everything that was in the previous study room?"

"Yes sir." Lala returned the cloth to the basin. "Do you have any other orders? The time now is 3 o’clock in the afternoon. If there is nothing else, I will fix the hole in the study room."

"You can just nail up a few layers of woods." Garen ordered.

"Okay." Lala hesitated. "Air will leak it though."

"Don’t worry about it."

"Then, I will go now."

"Alright."

Garen turned around and sat at the desk with his gaze out of focus, as though he was looking into the distance.

Lala gave him a strange look before walking out of the new study room, gently closing the door.

Her footsteps slowly faded.

Garen sat by the table without moving.

After some time, a clear clicking sound was heard from his arms.

Garen refocussed his vision as he blinked and rubbed at his temple points.

"Hmm… This Tactic, Sight Sharing still requires more time before I can get used to it… The situation and the sound it makes doesn’t tally up, much like those soundless movies in the theatre."

He started to feel suspicious after he’d rested for a while. He took out the exquisite golden pocket watch from his pocket and realized that the clockwork had stopped.

Garen wound up the pocket clock gently so that it could run again.

"It’s been so many days. How long has it been since I met Goth? Ten days? Twenty days? I can’t help but feel that something’s weird about Elielan." He put down the pocket watch as he frowned.

Suddenly, Garen’s face was filled with surprise. He stood up and looked at the white abandoned building through the window.

Among the abandoned city walls and buildings, a black beetle as tall as half a man was swiftly scurrying towards the villa.

A black pants leg could be seen in its mouth, and it was dragging a weak-looking dark human body.

This body which was in long black clothes had all of its hair burnt out. The hand and legs that could be seen were covered in blackish red ulcers. The body left an obvious, dirty trail as it was dragged along by the beetle.

The beetle scuttled on the flat terrain towards the villa hastily as it dodged a few large craters.

Garen opened the window, and lightly leapt out of it as he exerted some force with his legs. He landed in the villa’s garden daintily. As he regained his balance, he personally greeted this black beetle which had dragged a person along with it.

As he took a step forward, a foul odor wafted in his direction.

Garen frowned as he carefully inspected the body.

The body was completely burnt black and literally all visible skin was coated in blackish red blisters. These blisters of all sizes appeared in clusters, morbidly similar to grapes. Some of them had already burst due to the friction and a yellowish black viscous substance could be seen flowing out of them.

Furthermore, its hair was completely burnt off and half of the skin on its head appeared to have been ripped off with great force, as the underlying flesh could be seen.

Garen narrowed his eyes as he observed this body, and he was suddenly cautious.

"Interesting. Let’s assume you found me on your own accord instead of me finding you. I will not believe in such a coincidence. Out of this enormous range, you chose to faint in my territory."

He muttered to himself. He then walked closer, squatted down and pulled open the person’s shirt.

He pulled off the outer black shirt and without any underwear, a pair of half rotten breasts, covered in purple red blisters, was revealed.

"A woman?" He covered her body with her clothes and stood up as he tried to resist the horrendous smell. "Since you found me on your own, I really want to see what you’re going to do."

Garen turned around and walked into the villa. A Deep Swarm Croc gently flicked its tail and rolled the girl on its back, carrying her while following Garen.

The villa’s entrance was already opened by Lala, who stood beside it. Her expression was completely calm; she had seen too many strange scenarios and it was obvious that she was used to it already.

She followed the Deep Swarm Croc which was following Garen and she couldn’t help but feel shaken at the horrible state of the body. She was unable to resist covering her nose as she got closer to the eye-watering stench.

Nauseous couldn’t begin to describe the foulness of the odour.

"Go bring some clean towels and water and help clean her up." Garen ordered quietly.

"Okay. I will go get some warm water!" Lala rushed towards the kitchen.

With his left hand on the person’s shoulder, Garen turned around and easily picked up the giant croc with his other hand to provide support for the girl.

"Who are you?! Are you not Jess!?" Her eyes fluttered open in shock as she stared at Garen.

Even though she’d finally spoken, her voice was that of a broken wind-box as most of the words that came out of her mouth were just noise. Unexpectedly, her accent was a pure Daniela accent.

She suddenly got up and shrunk away from Garen.

"Jess? You sure do know a lot." Garen squinted at this girl who’d been balded by a fire. "What fearsome vitality. With such an injury, if you were a normal human you’d be a fried corpse . By the way, your Daniela accent is very accurate."

"Daniela accent?" The girl was puzzled. "What is that?’

"Tell me, why are you looking for Jess?" Garen asked softly in the Daniela language. He had picked up these commonly used languages during his time in the inner city. He didn’t have to worry about wasting potential points as he had a lot right now. The current him looked very intelligent.

"Jess?" The girl was suddenly baffled. "That’s right… Why am I looking for Jess? Who is Jess?" Her eyes were clearly filled with confusion.

She then suddenly covered her head with her hands and squatted down as her face twisted in agony.

"My head… It’s hurts…!!" She tumbled to the floor and squirmed about like a disgusting worm, leaving a pool of sticky viscous substance on the tiles.

The stench started to spread and Garen, who had a supersensitive nose started to feel nauseous.

As he scanned the woman’s blood and qi’s circulation, he could clearly see it.

Her blood and qi were mostly stagnant in her brain and the remaining parts of her body were incredibly weak, so weak that she was just barely surviving.

It looked like a very messy tangled red thread and the only place to unknot everything was her head.

"What is your name?" Garen asked softly as he used a secret martial art to send the message directly into her ears.

"My… My na.. Name?" The girl’s head was in complete chaos. "I can’t remember! My head hurts so much…"

She grabbed her head tightly as she curled up on the ground like a caterpillar about to burn to death.

At this moment, Lala came in with a silver basin and a black towel, but was stopped by Garen.

Garen was baffled. "Let me handle this. You can go and do the other tasks."

"Yes." Lala didn’t enquire further and turned around with her head down as she proceeded to do her remaining duties.

Garen gently picked the woman up and carried the towel and basin with one hand as he went up to the vice bedroom on the second floor.

Along the way, he tried to ask this person some basic questions and found out that she had forgotten everything. Furthermore, based on her qi, she didn’t seem to be lying.

This woman seemed to have suffered severe head damage. Through her qi, Garen found out that her brain was damaged; a quarter of her brain had already turned into a mush. Amazingly, she hadn’t died and had survived.

"This is a miracle!" Garen exclaimed as he lay the woman’s head down and gazed down at her unconscious body. Her face could’ve been from a horror movie. It was ugly, swollen, smelly and rotten. It was literally purple rotting meat. If not for her breasts that left persuasive evidence, nobody would’ve been able to make out her gender. As a matter of fact, no one might’ve even see her as a human.

With just a light touch, Garen’s palm was filled with the stick and smelly substance. "With this look, those dead babies by the roadside would have classified themselves together with you. Severe infection throughout the body and purulence. You’re as good as dead had I not discovered you."

He locked the door and soaked the towel in the warm water. He then wrung out the towel and gently wiped off the sticky substances on her face.

With fingers that were as sharp as blades, he cut off the woman’s long shirt and pants to reveal the swollen body underneath it.

Garen then cleaned the girl’s body with the utmost care as he removed the dirt and blood clots. He managed to clean up her body after changing a few basins of water through Lala.

He then closed the door firmly to ensure that Lala would not enter the room no matter what.

Alone, his palms started to glow red, resembling a sculpture made out of gem.

Garen took a deep breath as he stood in front of the woman.

"Buzz!!!"

A loud buzz emitted from Garen’s mouth as he moved his fingers swiftly across the woman’s chest, head and legs.

The sound waves constantly vibrated her body. Garen felt like he was treating a burnt corpse as he placed his fingers onto pressure points that felt like rotten wood.

It was a secret technique used to temporarily activate the life potential, which would enhance physical recovery. This skill was similar to the Polaris Fierce Arts. Although this activation method would affect the body’s lifespan, this woman would have died if she couldn’t endure this so there wasn’t much of a difference.

Chapter 318: Defector 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

After a series of finger tapping, white sweat started forming on Garen’s forehead. He took two steps backward as his red jaded palms faded away.

The woman was covered in a layer of transparent light upon completion of her treatment. The layer of light flashed as it completely covered every part of the woman.

A cool and sharp chill suddenly filled up the whole room.

"She’s indeed a totem user." Garen smirked as he activated his white totem light to resist against the strong energy fluctuation.

The woman’s eyelids twitched before she opened her eyes and her slightly slanted mouth.

"Who… am I…" Her bloodshot, grainy eyes were filled with confusion.

"You’re Reylan." Garen immediately walked to her side and gently said, "You’re Reylan Lombard, the biological sister of Garen Lombard, which is I."

"My name is Reylan?... Garen Lombard’s biological sister…" The woman unconsciously repeated Garen’s sentence.

"We were separated since young due to the fire." Garen’s voice was softer at this point.

"We were separated since young due to the fire…" The woman repeated Garen’s sentence word by word as her gaze started to clear up.

With Garen’s guidance, he spun a flawless lie within her mind. Although he knew that she had lost her memories due to the severe injury of her brain, her strength was obviously incredible judging from her totem light. She must not be an ordinary character, considering that she was able to escape from the Obscuro Society.

As to whether if this mislead would succeed or not, Garen had no idea. He was just testing it out and there would be no loss for him anyway.

After spending about half an hour on her, Garen finally let the woman to fall asleep.

He then left the room to get some fresh air as he had a hard time breathing inside the smelly room.

He’d only crafted the story of her oldest memories and had not tampered with the the rest of her memories. He told her that he’d found her outside of his house and he didn’t know what had happened to her during the years they were separated.

"Looks like I’ll need to spend some time to obtain something useful from her."

****************

Garen then accompanied this girl and treated her as Reylan Lombard, in which she believed that she was Reylan Lombard.

Since her brain was partly damaged, most of her memories were already jumbled. She’d already accepted what Garen told her and acted as if she was his younger sister.

Garen took care of her everyday life by himself. This assured her of her memories, as if not for a biological relative, who else would still be willing to take care of a smelly ‘burnt corpse’?

Reylan started to open up to Garen. Her figure had been completely disfigured so no one actually knew how she looked like in the past.

One side of her lips had been burnt, resulting in her mouth slanting to the right. Saliva would drip out of her mouth whenever she tried to speak, and food would come out as she tried to eat. As her skin recovered, it was marred with scars from the blisters and the wrinkled skin that was left behind by the burns made her look eighty to ninety years old.

Garen then started to probe for some information, after Reylan had opened up to him.

**************

More than ten days later.

Reylan sat on the huge bed inside the very clean room, silently gazing at Garen who was reading a book. The cool air entered the room through a small gap of the window and mixed with the faint odour of a corpse.

The golden sunlight shone on Garen’s right hand, reflecting a smooth and white luster.

Reylan was envious of him.

"What’s wrong?" Garen placed down the notebook in his hand. It was the book he had found from searching the golden hair totem user’s body and it contained information of the primitive totem’s nurturing method. It was an isolated tradition and even though there was little information about it, it was still worth the reference.

"Nothing. Brother, are you looking at the notes on how to nurture a primitive totem?" Reylan asked softly. Her voice had recovered a lot and was no longer leaking. Her voice was coarse but it sounded like a woman of not more than thirty years old.

"Yeah. I obtained it from the enemy and I’m just reading it casually." Garen replied with a smile. "Do you have anything you want to talk about?"

Reylan thought for a while as she frowned.

"My brain’s damage is too severe. Although I don’t remember everything, I still can recall some stuff. Compared to the primitive totem, the Creature Totem is much more stronger. So, why is brother not focusing on nurturing the Silver Totem?"

Surprised, Garen shook his head and replied: "There are no other choice. A Crystal Derivator is needed to control the Silver Totems. Based on this assumption, doesn’t that mean that I will forever be controlled by someone else?"

"A Crystal Derivator?" Reylan looked confused. "That sounds familiar…"

Garen was patient and sat there quietly as he waited for Reyland to recall her memory.

Time slowly passed.

Reylan finally opened her mouth.

"I remember this thing. Its control mechanism isn’t perfect so it can be avoided." She paused for a while. "Technically speaking, this item isn’t able to send images and can only send voice messages at best. Although the user interface is partially encrypted, it’s fairly easy to hack into it. The basis of deactivation is… Ah!!"

Suddenly, she grabbed her head as she let out a deep cry of pain and toppled onto the bed. Her body started to shudder, as though she was running in a blizzard without clothes on.

"Don’t force yourself too much. Get some rest! Get some rest and relax!!" Garen immediately stood up as his face filled with concern.

He swiftly reached out his hand and pressed onto a few pressure points to reduce her agony.

"Looks like you’re being assassinated because you have this knowledge. Those Obscuro Society bastards! I will kill all of them some day!" Garen’s eyes burned with killing intent.

"Don’t! It’s impossible to win against them brother!" Reylan resisted the pain as she pulled Garen. "I’m certain they’re trying to destroy this part of my memory. Believe me, I will find a way to recall!"

"There’s no need to rush." Garen sat down and covered Reylan with a blanket.

What was supposed to be a young woman looked like a seventy to eighty year old bald hag, with wrinkles and scars all over her body. Other than her voice, there was not a single external sign that she was young. Furthermore, she constantly smelt of a musty unpleasant odor.

She was touched when she heard Garen’s response.

"I managed to survive when they wanted me dead. Although I don’t remember who’d hurt me to this state, I will find out no matter what!" Reylan said fiercely before she paused and looked at Garen.

"You don’t have to be impatient too brother. Although I don’t recall how to deactivate the Crystal Derivator’s authorization mechanism, we can at least temporarily bypass it and control the authorization mechanism."

"Oh?" Garen’s eyes glimmered. "To bypass?"

"Yes. The authorization rights only allow the higher level Crystal Derivator to monitor the Crystal Derivator of the lower level. Since secret phrases are very reliable, it is very uncommon that a fake leader would appear. To control a lower level crystal with a higher level crystal, one must go through the Control Crystal. There are two prerequisites before one can go through the Control Crystal. The first condition is that the crystal that is being controlled must not be broken."

Garen nodded as he saw the broken crystals turned grey and couldn’t function any longer.

"The other one is that the crystal that is under control must be in a sluggish state."

"A sluggish state?" Garen repeated his question. "What is a sluggish state?"

"It is a special state of the crystal. When the crystal is in this state, its functionality, abilities and communication speed are all reduced. Errors occur more frequently as well. This way, if one were to keep using it without anyone from the Obscuro Society to fix it, the crystal will eventually break. This would still be fine for the typical crystals. However, if it’s a high grade crystal such as the Field-level crystal which is hard to create, they would not forcefully command the lower grade crystal under these circumstances to prevent any losses."

Reylan explained with full confidence.

"Furthermore, in the current world of chaos where strong experimental creatures have escaped, there were a lot of generals killed. Hence, crystals in a sluggish state are natural and inconspicuous. As long as you execute it naturally, no one would be suspicious of it. At the very least, you do not need to worry about the Creature Totem that you nurtured so hard going against you."

"This is a great plan." Garen nodded as he agreed with the feasibility of this method. "However, we can’t always be in the sluggish state, can we?"

"This can drag up to months and we will think of another idea when the time comes." Reylan explained. "At least we don’t have to worry about the crystal’s information being casually looked upon."

"You can casually look at the Crystal’s information?" Garen was startled.

"Only the Commander-level Crystal can do so." Reylan nodded. "Come over here and I will set up your crystal’s state."

Garen squinted his eyes as he hesitated but he took out his Crystal Derivator in the end.

"You don’t have to pass it to me. Just hold it like that will do." Reylan had no intention on obtaining the Crystal.

She reached out her right index finger and immediately produced a black fire.

The fire kept producing complicated black Tactic symbols in the air, which looked like endless of alphabet K superimposed together in a roulette shape.

"Go!" She gently pushed the Tactics forward.

Pew!

The black Tactic symbols turned into a black light instantly and went into Garen’s Crystal Derivator.

The pink Crystal Derivator glew brightly before it dimmed down for good. Garen could feel that the constantly faint ripple gradually disappeared.

"It’s a success. However, brother should learn some of the basic knowledge in case something complicated comes up when I am not around so you can solve the issue." Reylan explained.

Garen was startled and smiled afterwards. "That’s fine by me. I had the same intention as well."

Chapter 319: Cruel 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

Reylan was a very talented researcher. If she could rid herself of her terrifying appearance, the learning environment would have been perfect.

Under her guidance, Garen learnt the basics of evolution, advanced mathematics, advanced physics, biological anatomy and a series of specialised advanced science knowledge.

Days passed as Garen was immersed in his new knowledge and had almost forgotten about everything else.

Kaboom!!

Suddenly, the feather pen in Garen’s hand fluttered and left an ink splotch on the piece of paper.

"What happened?!" He leaped to his feet and looked outside as he rushed to the window.

A swarm of black dots in the grey sky, like dots of inks in clear water, was flying towards the inner city.

These small dots were composed of flying creatures of different sizes and shapes. There were Unihorn Lizards, giant flies, etc. These new models were of strange different shapes and all of them were flying towards the inner city.

"This is!?" Garen suddenly recalled an important task towards the people in the inner city.

"Brother, what’s going on?" The room’s door was pushed opened as Reylan entered with a grey robe concealing her body. "I think I sense a high density energy core resonating!"

She used the grey robe to cover every part of her maimed face.

"I have no idea but these creatures are commencing a large-scale attack towards the city," Garen replied seriously. "The scale of this attack isn’t typical. In fact, it is much larger than the previous ones. I’m afraid the strong creatures are going to come out soon."

"Legend has is that the Iron Tank City has a high-grade national treasure known as the Heart of the Dragonshadow. It can slowly erode the enemies within a certain area. These creatures are nothing to worry about if the people inside can buy some time." Reylan casually explained. She then looked at Garen’s expression. "Brother, do you have any friends in the inner city?"

Garen didn’t say a word and nodded.

"Okay. I may have to go and have a look. You should stay in the villa and don’t leave it for no reason."

"I understand." Reylan nodded as she replied. She then turned her head and shouted. "Lala! Lala! Come quickly!"

She wasn’t as gentle towards others; her tone usually had a tone of impatience.

Soon, Lala who was in a black and white servant dress came rushing in.

"Ms Reylan, Do you... Have any orders?" Lala didn’t like Sir Garen’s sister as she always glared at her face and skin with jealousy. A girl who had lost her physical appearances would view their own beautiful kind with jealousy and this made Lala uncomfortable.

Reylan looked at her with disgust.

"Who are you trying to seduce with such a short dress? My brother? You damn whore. You might as well not wear anything if you want to wear such a short skirt. Quickly prepare the shirt and gears for my brother’s departure!!" Reyland shouted loudly with impatience.

"It’s alright Reylan. There’s no need to be so strict with Lala since she’s still young." Garen frowned as he said softly.

Reylan changed back to her gentle tone. "You have no idea brother. You need be strict with these underlings so that they know that life isn’t easy! They wouldn’t know their place if this keeps up. Let me handle the small stuff so that you can do what you need to do."

Garen didn’t say anything else as he could see that Reylan didn’t have a good attitude to begin with. Now that she had lost her physical appearances, her attitude had worsened.

"Then I will take my leave."

"Okay. Do you need me to accompany you?" Reylan asked very softly.

"No need." Garen shook his head and brought Lala out of the room. As they walked alongside the corridor, Garen looked at Lala sympathetically.

"Don’t mind her. Sister was severely injured so her mood isn’t very good. Be a little bit more patient with her."

"... I understand." Lala replied softly.

"Good." Garen nodded.

After changing his shirt, Garen put on his grey robes and hat as he immediately left the villa’s vicinity.

A twelve meter long giant white dragon crouched in the empty field in front.

The petrifying white dragon was completely still and it looked like a very well crafted white gem sculpture.

As it sensed Garen’s arrival, it slowly raised its head and softly growled at Garen.

Shh…

Garen strolled towards it and stroked its head.

"Alright. I may need you to bring me out this time. Be careful and not let any stronger creature notice you." Garen smiled as he leapt onto the Petrifying White Dragon’s back.

The White Dragon’s body was rough and non-reflective. With its layer of scales covering its body, it had an aura of elegance around it.

Garen landed on the white dragon’s back and sat in an empty spot between the wings. In front of him was the White Dragon’s head which was completely defenseless and the triangular fins on the top of its head which Garen used as an indicator to determine direction.

Garen sat on his knees and placed his hands onto the warm, hard dragon scales. He found two scales that were tipped up and decided to hold onto them.

"Let’s fly." He ordered.

The Petrifying White Dragon expanded its ragged wings, flapped a few times as it sprinted forward.

Whoosh!

It beat its wings with all its might and a turbulent was created, blowing away the rocks and dusts underneath him aside.

The Petrifying White Dragon opened its mouth filled with sharp fangs and exhaled a mouthful of white gas. It then moved its wings rhythmically and flew towards the inner city.

Garen, who was sitting on the back of the dragon, looked down at the streets and houses that gradually became smaller. The swarms of black beetles, Deep Swarm Croc, and the eye catching Dual Headed Salamander gazed up at him as they growled in dissatisfaction due to them not able to hunt outside of the villa.

The white house underneath him became smaller and gradually looked like a wooden box. Most of the buildings in the urban area were damaged. The districts which were close to the city walls looked like a pile of white stones gathered by the city walls.

As the Petrifying White Dragon flew through the sky, Unihorn Lizards started to appear in the surrounding. They were in either black, red, or even grey color for the bigger ones. Although the white colored Unihorn Lizards were a little bit smaller in size, they still looked very fierce.

Garen concealed his aura to the best of his abilities as he hid behind the White Dragon’s back with his grey robe.

Whoosh!

A black giant bald eagle appeared to the right of Garen. This giant eagle was as big as the White Dragon. What made it different from the other creatures was that although it was a little bit afraid of the White Dragon, it didn’t maintain a respectable distance between them.

Dissatisfied, the Petrifying White Dragon growled. He was stopped by Garen as it was about to attack the weird eagle.

As they flew towards the inner city, the surrounding creatures in the sky increased in numbers, as they were now within the city There were so many the sky was literally covered by them. There were creatures of different shapes and sizes everywhere and there were countless above him as well.

Garen looked down at the Iron Tank City, which had originally been white and circular but was now in ruins. Only a small portion of the district in the center of the city was still in perfect condition, as there was a semi spherical glass barrier covering it.

A giant Three-eyed Black Bear and a Panther with black wings on its back were creeping closer towards the inner city from opposite sides. Behind these two were countless of creatures leaded by them.

From the bird’s eye view, it looked like two black curtains that were slowly covering the inner city.

The frigid breeze kept gusting through Garen’s grey robe, sending chills down his spine. He adjusted his aura to prevent himself from being frozen to death and noticed by the creatures.

As he laid on the dragon’s back, he quietly gave orders to the white dragon to descend.

Shh…

The white halo appearing on the Petrifying White Dragon’s body covered Garen as well. As it plunged down, the surrounding creatures avoided its path of trajectory as whatever was inside the white light would have their speed reduced and their joints stiffened.

The Petrifying White Dragon left Garen at the entrance of the War Guild.

Garen quietly jumped down from its back and swiftly ran into the entrance.

As though it was his backyard, Garen swiftly rushed towards the inner city through an abandoned route.

After a few turns, two guards in black armor appeared in front of him.

"Who’s there!?"

Without saying another word, Garen flashed out his membership card.

The two guards were stunned.

"You must have rushed back from afar. Enter quickly because the creatures are about to attack the city!"

Totem users who could stay outside were definitely not your typical totem users. Hence the respect the two guards showed was understandable.

Garen swiftly passed through both of them and soon saw a totem user and a black spider totem on the wall, staring fiercely at Garen with its red eyes.

"Identity yourself!" The totem user asked coldly.

Garen flashed out his membership card again. As he looked to the front, he was stunned to see multiple levels of totem users on guarding duty.

"What happened? Why is the guarding so strict?"

The man didn’t say a word as he looked at Garen and shook his head.

"Sir, please enter quickly because the inner city is in need of someone of your caliber. You’ll know once you enter."

Garen nodded as he swiftly entered.

Soon, he passed through all the guards and entered the main hall. There was barely anyone inside as everyone was out.

Chapter 320: Cruel 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

The streets were filled with people. Most of them were looking up in silence.

Garen followed the crowd and looked up as well.

There were thousands of White Dragonhawks and Giant Hawks forming into a circle in the sky, prepared to attack the countless creatures outside at any moment.

"Oh right, Goth and the others! Where are they?" Garen hurried through the crowd in the general direction of Goth’s house.

Everywhere was on high alert along the way; he could see guards and totem users sprinting about constantly.

Garen finally recalled that this was the key war of the Iron Tank City before the major change. He didn’t expect that he would forget such an important timeline after Reylan’s appearance.

*****************

Goth was staring sombrely at the scene before him.

The glass of the black and white photo frame on the table had some minor cracks in it.

He gently picked it up and carefully wiped off the layers of dust.

The ground was littered with an assortment of belongings.

"Goth!!" Suddenly a familiar voice called from outside.

Goth was startled. He then regained his composure, stood up and opened the door. Outside, he saw Garen standing alone in a grey robe who looked extremely dishevelled.

"Are you alright!?" Garen looked at him suspiciously.

"Of course I’m fine. A person like me who could torture two of you, how can I be in a pinch?" Goth flexed his biceps as he smirked.

"How about Jessica?" Garen asked softly.

Bam!

A huge hand slammed onto the door beside his face.

"Don’t mention anything about Jessica!!" Goth lowered his head as his tone darkened.

"What happened?" Garen was stunned as he let himself into the house and locked the door.

As Garen entered the house, he saw vulgarity scrawled all over the walls.

‘Goth you are such a selfish prick!’

‘Curse you! May your corpse will be eaten by stray dogs when you die!’ ‘I hope you’ll never have kids. Even if you do, they will never have a good life!’...

Strong words were written onto the walls and they weren’t written out of anger. They’d been written in a jerky manner.

These red words covered all the walls in the house.

"What exactly happened?" Garen sat down and asked.

Goth sat down as well but he didn’t immediately answer Garen’s question.

Both of them sat together quietly.

"Andy is dead…" Goth suddenly opened his mouth.

Garen’s eyes widened when he heard it.

Goth looked at him in an unexpectedly calm manner.

"He died because of me."

"!?" Garen didn’t know what to say. He didn’t know what had happened during his absence but Andy was dead!!??

Goth smiled. "A few days ago, we engaged in a close combat battle with the creatures. Andy rushed into the creatures alone and never returned."

"Why?" Garen asked softly. He couldn’t comprehend what was happening. "Is it because of Elielan?!"

"Elielan? He’s also dead.." Goth said emotionlessly, as though he was narrating a story that was unrelated to him. "I thought that he and I would become the best of friends."

"To be honest, I don’t really know what happened. Everything had changed when I regained consciousness." Goth’s face was very pale. "I was slow witted when I was young and would always lose in a fist fight, getting punched in the face every time… I’m simple minded and stupid."

"My dreams are so simple. I just want my mum to be recognized by the household, by my father."

Garen looked at him without saying a word. He had a bad feeling about this.

Goth smiled. "I’m old fashioned, don’t know how to dress up, inflexible and I like to daydream frequently. I never thought that a girl would fall for me in the future. I couldn’t even look at myself in the mirror. I didn’t expect a girl to like me."

His laugh was cold, as if there was a hint of sadness in it.

"I am really naive. I really thought that a girl liked me… I’m old fashioned, ugly, poor and have no power.. Haha…"

He stood up and looked outside of the window.

"Did you see the crowd outside? They probably don’t know… My father, the Grand Duke White Dragonhawk no longer possesses the Heart of the Dragonshadow. The strongest Tactic Precious Heirloom is no longer in his possession."

"How do you know?" Garen’s heart sunk.

"Because I took it away." Goth replied blandly. "Garen, I lost everything… really. I have lost everything…"

"You still have me as a friend!" Garen stood up and replied calmly.

"Friend?" Goth turned around and chuckled.

He suddenly stared at Garen.

"Then can you tell me how you obtained the Totem Light? Sir Totem User of the Obscuro Society?"

Garen was stunned as he didn’t expect Goth to mention such a phrase.

He stood still as he was unsure of how to answer him.

"I have lost everything…" Goth laugh miserably as he took a few steps back and accidentally knocked over the table’s photo frame.

Whoosh! A black figure flashed and he vanished, as though he was never there to begin with.

He then quietly walked out of the house to see a black carriage and a man in black with a few totem users in front of the house.

"Can you spare a few minutes of your time?" The man asked as he walked towards him.

Garen looked at him and took a deep breath.

"Good timing. I wanted to know what happened."

"You must be Goth, Andy and Jessica’s friend, Garen right?" The man confirmed. "Do you have any clues for this incident?"

"Incident? Clues?" Garen was startled. "What incident?"

"Do you not know?" The man asked suspiciously.

Ten minutes later, Garen pulled up his hood and was speechless as he watched the carriage leaving. He suddenly understood why Goth had been so cold and emotionless towards everyone.

The man didn’t know the overall situation as well. He only knew that his superior wanted him to monitor this place and enquired anybody who had visited this place.

Garen’s feelings were complex. Andy was dead, Jessica was lost and Goth seemed to be severely injured emotionally.

Perhaps only the three of them knew what truly happened. Now that Goth had left, he couldn’t find anyone who understood the situation and was at a loss.

"Based on Goth’s reaction, he could obviously see my empowered totem light. Since he was able to see through it, there must be others out there who could too." Garen pondered for a bit and decided to deactivate his black totem light, leaving behind his primitive totem’s totem light.

As Garen strolled along the main street, he kept analysing Goth’s whereabouts as he couldn’t understand Goth’s last words before he left.

It contained a lot of information.

Without realizing, Garen had arrived the War Guild’s headquarters.

Among the crowds by the headquarter’s entrance, a familiar figure was sitting by the stairs. It was Angel, Therese Angel.

She immediately stood up as she saw Garen approaching.

"I have been waiting for you for a long time. I’m impressed that the shackles had an additional effect."

"Let’s talk about it once we enter." Garen wasn’t in a good mood.

The two of them squeezed into the guild and found a seat at the corner of the hall.

"What plans do you have?" The moment they sat down, Angel asked quietly, just loud enough for Garen to be able to hear her. "The current situation is dire and I have already arranged an underground passage to leave this place through the guild. This place will soon become a playground for those creatures."

"Plans?" Garen thought for a moment. "I wasn’t in the city recently. Has anything major happened in the inner city?" He whispered.

Angel’s attitude towards Garen had obviously changed for the better due to the secondary effects of the War Shackles, which had given her a few advantages during her multiple battles. She now felt completely at ease with Garen’s shackles.

"Major event? Do you mean… the incident of the Duke Household’s Chief Commander?"Angel asked skeptically.

"Let’s hear about it." Garen whispered.

"The Duke Household’s Chief Commander, Goth’s wife had killed his mother and I heard that she even stole an important item from the Duke’s household. She is currently wanted throughout the city. I heard from a few acquaintances that the situation is extremely complicated." Angel pondered before she whispered her reply.

Garen was still dissatisfied. Although he was able to pull the history back onto its original course, Goth was still being forced into a dead end. Andy was not supposed to die, and Jessica has murdered Goth’s mother and went missing.

The situation was very difficult for Garen to imagine. Jessica had killed Goth’s mother. Was it because of the Silver Control?

Garen wasn’t sure if Goth had found out that Jessica was being Empowered, though he knew that whether Goth liked it or not, he had to walk this path.

Or else the entire Iron Tank City would be dead.

He wanted to avoid it but the Iron Tank City would be wiped out if he were to do it. Garen was truly stuck in a dilemma.

"This is the road the strongest person must take... " Garen lowered his head and sighed. He had been neglecting the fact that he had yet to try and make a conscious decision.

Had I really forgotten about time? Garen asked himself.

"Are you alright?" Angel asked in confusion. "Do you know that Goth?"

"He’s my friend." Garen nodded. "Alright let’s not talk about this. Where’s your small team? How’s it going?"

"It’s alright. We’re currently defending the southern region." Angel answered. "How about it? Do you want to tag along?"

"No thanks, I have other things to do." Garen shook his head he passed a paper with a written address to Angel. "You can come to this place if you encounter any trouble. Perhaps things will take a turn there. Remember not to bring too many people, not more than five people."

Angela took the paper skeptically and studied it. It was an address outside the city. "What have you been up to in the dark?"

"Don’t worry about it. Alright, that settles it then." Garen stood up as he’d heard shouts from the outside.

The city reverberated with countless creatures’ growls.

The final battle had begun.

Chapter 321: Dazzle 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

Garen kept observing the changes in the sky as he left the War Guild.

Huge numbers of White Dragonhawks and Giant Hawks were battling with the creatures and corpses would plummet from the sky from time to time.

The streets were completely empty as most of the citizens had gone to defend the borders. Only a few people remained in the center of the inner city.

A melody of harp music drifted from Garen’s right. It was a middle age man with a freckled face. He was giving his all to a performance that no one was listening to.

"Life is like a water splash without the foam, clear and paradoxical. What is the purpose of the war when I hear the sadness of the Iron Tank City during its night. I could clearly hear the creatures scream in the wee hours. Ahh~~~ The blood is red and it is so thick… Yet tears are colorless and so thin… Life, where it could bloom a cursed flower, could also bloom a pure lily. Ahh~~ Will you please tell me if the beauty eventually dies…"

The poet’s musical voice echoed in the empty streets.

Garen saw the tears on his face and a black golden adonis flower adorning his chest, which was only worn when a family member died.

Garen gently pulled down his hood as he walked past this person.

*************

Inside the white Palace in the inner city.

At the center of the empty Palace laid a pyramidal hero monument.

The monument was pure white in color and black names were densely carved onto it. They were the names of the totem users who died during the war.

Multiple men in black stood in front of the monument.

One of them was a youngster. He was looking at the pyramid in silence, thinking of something.

"The Memorial Tower, where all the dead totem users were buried here and had their names carved." An old man walked towards the monument as he said softly. "Aisaiya, I hope you live a better life in heaven and not suffer like how you did here…" He gently spread soul sand onto the pyramid. The black sands landed onto the pyramid and gave off a sizzling noise.

Garen, too, grabbed a handful of sand and gently spread them out.

He spread the sand at the familiar name in the pyramid.

‘Andy Cruise’

"May you rest in peace in heaven." He muttered.

"Perhaps I have been keeping a low profile for too long… I have almost forgotten the glory back in those days." Garen opened his hands and quietly stared at his hands which had taken countless lives. "Time will eventually erode a human’s will, and I am not excluded. Perhaps it’s not too late…"

He looked passed the pyramid through the small gaps and saw a little girl standing at the opposite end of the pyramid. She had a long golden hair with fair and tender cheeks. The girl was quietly staring at him in sadness as well.

An adult and a child, staring at each other in silence.

Garen smiled, turned around and left as he put on his black robe.

*****************

Kaboom!

The right halo instantly exploded the abandoned area and shattered many fragments of stones into dust.

Goth stared coldly at the creatures that had exploded. This creature that resembled an ostrich had instantly died to him.

Behind him stood a man and a woman in white shirts with golden sleeves.

"Be careful! The Thousand Moon Flower is just up ahead" Goth ordered softly.

"Don’t worry about it." The white-clad woman huffed. "I alone could have completed the mission if not for my superior, who wanted me to work with you!"

"Quit it Aisijia. It wasn’t Goth’s fault!" The white robed man placated her.

Goth continued walking forward without any change in expression.

Two of them followed closely.

The situation in the inner city had been stagnant for a while and they required an elite to eliminate the energy source of the creatures’ Enhanced Spirit Light, the Thousand Moon Flower. It’s a magical item that was created by the Creature army’s Sammy, which could provide endless stamina and strength towards the army.

Goth’s team was one of the few that were ordered to take care of the Thousand Moon Flower.

Goth was still replaying the scene of him meeting his father.

The father that had never tired in his memory, had been covering his wrinkled face with his hands.

"It’s alright. Have confident in your father. I am the Iron Tank City’s Grand Duke White Dragonhawk and I have a formidable presence even going against the royal alliance. The Heart of the Dragonshadow is nothing."

"Go and battle with ease and do not let other things distract you. You are my son and my pure blood flows within you. The Blackfield Birds are the proof of the bloodline." The Grand Duke looked at Goth and his injured eye with sympathy, as though he saw himself in the past.

"You have to learn to forget. If you’re truly unable to forget them, keep them as the beliefs within your heart."

Goth felt warmth inside him.

"I still have my father. He would not lie to me…"

The Grand Duke’s words were like a sharp sword that instantly destroyed the confusion in his mind.

Goth unconsciously sped up as they arrived at the outskirts through the dark passage. They were attempting to alleviate the stress upon the inner city.

Huuu~~~~

Suddenly, the Dragonhawk Horn’s blast echoed from the inner city.

"It’s the Dragonhawk Horn! The final battle in the inner city is about to begin! The Three-eyed Black Bear and the remaining third form creatures have appeared!" Goth turned his head and looked at the inner city. His red totem light expanded and turned the surrounding creatures into mince meat.

Countless creatures had gathered to form the black cloud above the inner city.

"It’s starting…" The girl in white robe whispered.

"Quick! We have to speed up!" Goth muttered. "We will retreat immediately once we destroy the Thousand Moon Flower!"

"Okay!" Both of them responded in unison. Both of them were the strongest form two totem users. Excluding the form three totem users who were currently busy, they were the best candidates for this mission. Since the city was lacking many form three totem users, they simply couldn’t send out their men for an away mission as they had more important things to take care of.

Furthermore, a form three totem user would’ve attracted a lot of attraction so they had specifically sent out the elites from the form two totem users for this mission.

The three of them jumped through the abandoned grey city at incredible speed, passing through countless creatures. These creatures were under the form three ultimate creature’s command to rush into the inner city so they would ignore the trio unless they were being attacked by them. The three of them had high speed so they instantly killed the ones they could kill and avoid the stronger ones. Just like this, they had arrived at an abandoned wall in the outskirts.

"This is it!" Goth confirmed the mission’s location from his memories. "Start searching! There should be Transparent Creatures around! Stay alert Aisijia!"

The girl in white robe didn’t say another word and took out a white short staff and slammed it onto the ground.

Pew!

An invisible ripple expanded through the region with her at the center of its source.

Multiple invisible wolf type creatures were discovered by the ripple as they were trying to ambush the trio from their back.

Aisijia sighed and a silver light burst out from her back and shifted into a white hawk that spanned at least three meters. It immediately killed off the transparent wolf type creatures in her surroundings.

The beak of the giant hawk was burned with a brown flame. As it opened its mouth, it spewed a brown torrent of flames and scorched all the wolves. The wolves started to roll on the ground in silent agony and died after a few moments of struggle. What was left behind were burnt corpses that were no longer invisible.

Goth and the other man were looking for the Thousand Moon Flower’s potential hiding spot.

"I found it!!" The man in white robe yelled in excitement.

They gathered and found a square transparent black box underneath the rock. Inside it lay a delicate and beautiful black crystal flower.

The flower stood straight and there appeared to be a black pearl in the middle of the petals.

"Thousand Moon Flower! Let’s quickly destroy it!" Goth ordered. "The time limit is 1 minute. Once we attack the Thousand Moon Flower’s defense, we will definitely alert the form three totem users. We will work together and attack at the same time!"

"Okay!" "Okay!"

Three of them placed their hand onto the black transparent box at the same time.

Suddenly, a deafening avian cry rang forth from the inner city.

Chirp!!!

It sounded like a cross between an eagle and a nightingale and the outcry reverberated throughout the inner city.

"That was… The cry of the Grand Duke’s Dragonhawk King!!" Aisijia recoiled as her face was filled with despair. "Only an injured Dragonhawk would produce such a noise!!! We must go back and support them!"

"Quickly!!"

Goth started to panic.

Three of them took out a yellow scroll, which was covered in Tactic symbols.

"Tactic Curse!" Aisijia glanced at Goth

"Dragon Spirit Summon!!" Goth shouted.

A high pitched sound rang out and red lightning burst forth from all three of their scrolls at the same time. The red lightning soared and struck the surface of the black box as wind gusted in all directions.

The red lightning slowly shifted into tiny dragonhawks hovering around the box.

Crack!

A fissure gradually widened on the box.

The black flower started to wither at a rate where the process could be seen with the naked eye. It swiftly arched down from a straight posture and soon turned into a pool of black ash.

"Let’s go!!" Goth shouted as they packed up the scrolls and retreated.

Two white Giant Hawks grabbed the duo in white robes to increase their speed. The Blackfield Bird chirupped and melded into Goth’s body, increasing his speed tremendously.

The three of them accelerated into streaks of black and white, and sprinted towards the inner city.

***************

As the three of them were moving swiftly, something apperated in a dark corner on their right.

"How could I let you guys leave and destroy the work of my lord?" A shrewd voice whispered from the shadows. "The Blackfield Birds. Hehe. If it could merge into the Grand Duke’s White Dragonhawk Totem, its strength would be unexpectedly strong. I didn’t expect to have such a little surprise. Three form two totem user elites? It will be a good appetizer for my babies, hehe."

A man clad in a black robe sauntered out from the shadows as he stared at Goth with his Emerald eyes. Although the movements of his legs appeared slow, it was surprisingly agile as he surged towards Goth’s team to intercept them.

He then stomped the ground with his leg.

"Who is it!" He looked to the right as his emotions started to falter.

"A battle is the collision of life. A stage for us to perform our best dances." A second man walked out from the darkness. He was also in a black robe and had short golden hair. His eyes couldn’t be seen, but he projected a fierce and powerful aura.

"Do you want to spice up your life? Trash from the Obscuro Society?"

Garen took off his hood and squinted his eyes.

In an instant, pairs of emerald eyes surrounded him from the darkness.

From the top view with Garen as the center of point, green eyes were densely packed staring at him from up to a hundred meters away. These Giant Wolves were emitting a faint signal. They were all from two totems!

The man in his black robe smiled as he stared at Garen with his green eyes.

************

Goth’s team was sprinting across the abandoned buildings. Suddenly Goth picked up a strange signal.

"What was that?" He couldn’t see anything as he was moving so swiftly.

"What’s wrong?" The man in white robe asked loudly. Two white streams were generated by the Giant Hawk above his head, which tore apart whatever was in their way.

"It felt like someone was there… whatever, let’s move quickly!" Goth dismissed the thought.

"Okay."

Chapter 322: Dazzle 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

Garen looked at the man in black nearby. He wasn’t one of Jess’ men from this area.

He had used the Derivator before to check information about all of Jess’ subordinates, but he wasn’t one of them.

Brr…

In the air above the inner city, far away, a sphere of black light was continuously expanding, like a growing fireball.

The sky and the ground began to tremble. The surface of the light ball kept shooting out pillars of black light, each light pillar accurately hitting the totem users in the inner city.

Vaguely, everyone could see the bird-like creatures sprawling their wings and chirping within the light ball. They had long and sleek black tail feathers, graceful wings, and a peacock crown shining with silver light.

Brrr!!!!

The black birds once more made a loud, jolting cry.

The black ball of light instantly scattered into a halo of black ripples, throwing all the nearby totem users away into the air.

Garen didn’t turn back to look at the black light ball’s terrifying attack, his gaze quietly fixed on the green-eyed man before him.

"You’re not one of Jess’ men," he said suddenly.

The other party’s green eyes gave an abrupt jolt.

"Who the heck are you!?"

"Devour him, White Dragon!"

Garen spoke those words calmly.

Whoom!!

A large white shadow fell from the sky, and rushed towards the man in black.

The Petrifying White Dragon immediately sprayed a large cloud of grey-white mist, covering this entire area.

It was as though the grey-white mist had a life of its own, gathering towards the man in black en masse. As soon as this mist touched the ground, be it the grass or the rocks, the dead bodies and carcasses, the blood stains… everything would be quickly petrified, turning into grey-white stone.

The swarm of Green-eyed Giant Wolves rushed towards Garen madly, with total disregard for their lives, but were completely surrounded by the petrifying mist in mid-air. They howled, their bodies quickly turning into grey stone, and they fell to the ground one by one. But these then morphed into puddles of green liquids, which meant none of them was the real thing.

The man in black wanted to raise his hand, but realized in shock that his actions were more than a little stiff. He tried to draw tactics in the air.

Boom!!

A huge amount of grey-white petrifying mist swept past where he stood.

The man in black was immediately petrified into a human-shaped statue.

Garen turned his head to look into the distance.

The Dual Headed Salamander slowly pointed its head out of the ground, holding a Green-eyed Wolf as big as a calf in its mouth. The Giant Wolf’s body was shriveling up, fast enough for the naked eye to see.

Ker… Ker-chak!

The Dual Headed Salamander broke the Green-eyed Wolf’s body in half with one bite.

At the same time, the petrified man in black also broke apart. With a whoosh, he became a pile of meaningless rubble.

Garen looked at the corpse of stones that had been killed instantly.

"A totem user outside of Jess’, interesting."

He turned around to look at the sky of the inner city. That giant mass of black light was madly sweeping shots at the totem users inside the city. Several small platinum dots were circling the light balls and attacked non-stop, but in the end they could only wander outside, held away by the light.

"Goth, this is as far as I can help you…" Garen murmured as he looked at the inner city. "Don’t die…"

He stood alone amidst the swarm of monsters. Countless monsters walked past him, but none at all attacked him. He was like a coral in the current, they split and went around him as though it was natural.

*******************

The giant black light ball floated mid-air.

The Grand Duke was wearing platinum armor and riding the Platinum Dragonhawk King, avoiding the black laser light pillars with the speed of the lightning.

He gripped his giant gold-colored Dragon Spear, pointing the spike on the sharp end towards the black light ball.

Hiss!

A pillar of black light brushed past his face, making his Totem Light tremble and shake.

"You alright, Reid." A woman’s voice came from the platinum-colored Dragonhawk. There was already a large silver abrasion wound on its stomach, dripping slowly with silver blood.

"I’m fine." The golden hairband behind the Grand Duke’s head had been blown away, and his long golden hair blew about in the air behind him. "After so many years, it’s been so very long since I fought together with you. Thinking about how we used to conquer together back in the day, my heart still palpitates even now."

"The opponent this time is far more challenging than any battle before, you and I might die in battle here," the Platinum Dragonhawk King said calmly, her silver eyes shimmering with a human-like light.

"That’s fine, I’ve long wanted to join her down there. I’m just sorry to trouble you, to make you come with me." The Grand Duke’s expression showed a hint of gentleness. The black light of the light ball shone on his face, as though plating him with a layer of holy light.

"Why are we still talking about this? Your son has already awakened the Blackfield Bird, why don’t you ask him to let you temporarily merge with his totem, so you have a higher chance of finishing off the enemy?" the Platinum Dragonhawk King asked softly, confusion in her voice.

"I’ve already made him leave the core area here. That way, I can protect the lineage for my family." The Grand Duke suddenly paused. From above in the air looking down, he could already feel that familiar aura rapidly approaching.

"Didn’t I ask him to leave here!?" He frowned for the first time.

Suddenly he heard the waves of cheers from below.

"Blackfield Bird!! It’s the Blackfield Bird!"

"As long as it merges with the Platinum Dragonhawk King, it can create the legendary strongest King of the Skies!!"

"We won’t lose!!"

Many of the totem users below them were well-read, and instantly recognized the black bird with its wings outstretched.

Once the Blackfield Bird merged into the Dragonhawk King, the strongest King of the Skies would appear once more. When that happened, they would definitely be able to finish off that strange bird in the air!

That was the understanding everyone reached at the time. The dozen or so remaining Form Three totem users were all staring intently at the Blackfield Bird carrying Goth. The giant black bird flapped its wings and rushed towards the Dragonhawk King, its eyes also filled with leaping black flames.

This was the last hope for all those people who could barely catch their breath under the light ball’s oppression!

The Blackfield Bird and Dragonhawk King constantly avoided the countless black light pillars and approached each other.

The Grand Duke looked at his son, who was riding on the Blackfield Bird’s back, helplessly.

"You shouldn’t have come back…" He had purposely let Goth go to the outskirts, to leave the core, just so he couldn’t come back for now, but to think… He had always felt guilty towards this pair of mother and son, towards that female totem user, who was so gentle, and who had always supported him quietly behind his back. Sadly, it was already too late to understand that now. She was already dead as well…

And now, now, all he had left was his son.

Looking at Goth flying towards him with determination in his eyes, he was suddenly and indescribably moved.

The Blackfield Bird flapped its wings, and suddenly accelerated, avoiding a blast of black light that shot towards it, and rushed towards the the Dragonhawk King.

Pff!

In an instant, the Blackfield Bird abruptly spat a gold thread from its mouth.

The gold thread pierced through the Dragonhawk King’s wounded stomach in the blink of an eye, and with a hiss, emerged from its back.

It was as though the sky fell instantly quiet. Everyone was shocked.

Silver blood poured down from the Dragonhawk King’s stomach.

No one guessed this would happen.

The smile on Goth’s face froze, his eyes widened, filled with disbelief and despair. He shook his head, his lip bleeding from where he bit it, and his expression panicked.

"No… No… It wasn’t me… It shouldn’t be like this! ...Not like this…!!" He kept shaking his head, sitting on the Blackfield Bird, the despair in his eyes so deep it was nearly madness.

The gold thread bent, and with another whoosh, it went straight through the Grand Duke’s armor, as well as his heart in his left breast.

"No!!!" He heard Goth’s angry roar of despair.

The Grand Duke looked down in shock, staring at the gold thread on his left chest. His expression went from surprise and pain, to dazed, release, and peace.

His mouth coughed out some blood despite himself.

"I’d only truly remove the Totem Light’s core defense when merging, you sure counted accurately…" He seemed to understand something.

"Reid… To think… that we really are going to die together this time…" The Dragonhawk King laughed somewhat sadly, but it was difficult.

The Grand Duke smiled sadly as well.

He wiped the blood from the corner of his mouth, and slowly turned his head to look at Goth underneath him, his face already covered with tears. Even this simple movement seemed to be unnaturally hard for him.

"Don’t cry, this life of mine has already been interesting enough. This isn’t your fault." He raised his head, his face nothing but peaceful. "Life is like a show, there are ups and downs, highs and lows. I have just walked to the ending I was meant to reach."

"Father…" Goth sat on the Blackfield Bird, but was completely unable to control his own body. He could not help but grab the gold thread, and toss it hard. The sharp tip of the gold thread poked out again, and penetrated the Grand Duke’s heart once more.

Psst!

Goth’s face was covered with tears, he had no idea what he was doing. An unimaginably huge power was controlling him, making him do these completely incomprehensible things.

The Grand Duke smiled, his face already rapidly growing pale. He glanced at the strange bird’s light ball in front of him, now gathering an unprecedented black light. The overwhelming sense of danger already felt as though it could explode at any time."

"Goth… don’t blame your mother… If possible, please… protect the Dragonhawk family’s Iron Tank City for me…"

Before he could finish his sentence, he abruptly waved his hand.

A powerful invisible force field suddenly spread out, pushing Goth away. It sent him flying, towards the most important core of the inner city, the Grand Duke’s residence.

The Grand Duke faced the black light, on the verge of explosion, and an intensely burning desire to battle rose in his eyes.

"Come, Anna! Let my people witness the true glory of our Dragonhawk family!!!"

"As you wish!" The Dragonhawk King’s gentle voice reverberated throughout the sky.

"Howl of the Heavenly Arc!!!"

In an instant, a blinding ball of golden light appeared in the sky, and hung high in the air just like the black light ball. A web of black and golden electric arches wove between the two light balls, and the sound of crackling electricity was everywhere.

By now, the totem users had been forced down into the lower skies or onto the ground by this extreme force. No one could have predicted this result.

The two light balls were like magnets, rapidly attracting each other.

And then there was the soundless collision.

Goth had been blasted into the pond in the Duke’s residence. Both he and the Blackfield Bird were numb all over, completely unable to get up or move. They could only stare blankly at the dazzling golden light ball in the sky.

His face was drowned in tears, and he tried to open his mouth, but couldn’t say anything.

A flash of blinding white light instantly dazzled the sky.

Boom!

A suit of platinum armor crashed down in front of Goth, steadily sticking into the grey-white stone floorboards.

That was the Grand Duke’s legendary armor, and also the White Dragonhawk family’s heirloom. The left chest that had been pierced by the golden thread just now was presently good as new.

After a long time, the light faded, and the stiffness enveloping Goth’s body also slowly diminished.

He walked out of the pond, covering his face with his hands, and silently knelt down in front of the armor.

Chapter 323: Leave 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

Garen stood in front of the memorial tower in the inner city, wearing a golden adonis flower. Standing alone in the line of people dressed in black, Garen didn’t stand out in the slightest.

Everyone in front and behind him stood in a straight line, making offerings to the Grand Duke’s body one by one. Those who had offered their flowers walked away quietly, and stood to a side. The people behind him followed suit quietly.

In the wide memorial hall, everyone somehow came to an unseen agreement to not make any sound.

In the large grey-white hall, next to a pyramid-shaped memorial tower, there were the Grand Duke’s remains. His body had been frozen by a platinum-colored, amber-like translucent metal.

Garen didn’t recognize the people in front of and behind him, but the shimmering ripples around everyone prove that nobody here was weak. With all these people lined up here, only he had a Form One totem user’s Totem Light.

Everyone else was either a Form Three or Form Two totem user, their bodies covered with the thick scent of blood.

Anyone who could survive safely in these times, would definitely be an executioner whose hands were stained with the blood of countless monsters.

Soon, it was his turn.

Garen took one step forward, and put the adonis flower in his hand in front of the crystal coffin lightly. He bowed, and turned to the left.

He glanced over. It was compact with people, but he didn’t recognize a single one.

The people were gathered in twos or threes, speaking softly. Some stood alone at a side, their expressions cold. Not far away, a heavy air hung over the nobles.

Garen didn’t see Goth anywhere.

After the Grand Duke expended his life to clash with that strange bird yesterday, the army of monsters suffered a heavy loss, and finally retreated. That strange bird was also grievously hurt, and flew away pathetically to save its life.

The situation had been temporarily stabilized.

But Goth had vanished without a trace.

Garen sighed. At first he had only come here to meet Goth for his own personal gain, but he didn’t think that after seeing the scenes from history with his own eyes, he would feel rather upset inside.

Soon enough, a middle-aged man and woman entered the memorial hall, both wearing platinum armor, covered by a white robe with silver edges.

"Lady Vesta, Lord Kanan." The receptionist went up to them and greeted them respectively.

"The situation is urgent, we can only stay for a short while." The man, Kanan, nodded solemnly. He and Vesta were now the strongest Form Three totem users in the inner city. Although they were still far from as strong as the Grand Duke, the monsters were obviously too afraid to really bear down on the inner city after the fright from the previous battle. The situation had also calmed down significantly.

A group of people surrounded the two of them respectfully as they walked to the coffin. Some asked about the situation, some were worried, some wanted a guarantee.

Most of the people went up to them, surrounding them in hopes of getting the answer they wanted.

Garen gave the center a wide berth, feeling suddenly frustrated at the rather noisy situation inside.

Turning around and leaving the hall, he raised his gaze to look. The surroundings were echoing empty, and he could barely see anyone anymore. There were only a few lonely people with numb expressions walking on the road. Most of them had already ducked into the defense fortifications that had been built in advance.

Garen had already searched everywhere, but hadn’t caught even a glimpse of Goth’s shadow.

It was empty inside the city now, there were too many places for him to hide. Walking on the main street, he wandered for a bit but eventually decided to leave the inner city through the underground tunnels.

"Garen?"

A confused voice came from a passing carriage.

Garen turned around, and looked towards the black carriage that had stopped beside him.

"You are?"

The carriage door curtain was pulled aside, revealing a solemn man’s face. "I saw you that at Goth’s house. Won’t you come up for a chat?"

Garen hesitated. "Alright."

He pulled aside the curtain, entered the carriage, and sat on the man’s right.

The carriage gave a slight jolt, and started moving again.

The man looked at the street outside calmly. "That day I went to investigate Goth’s house, and just happened to see you walking out from inside. How is it? Do you know the situation?"

Garen shook his head. "I’m completely in the fog right now. Goth was controlled by someone and killed his own father, but who on earth controlled him? And what’s up with Jessica?"

The man’s face flashed with a hint of heaviness.

"We’ve already started our initial investigations on this matter, but only a few higher-ups know about it. All of this started with Goth’s mother, Jeanria Jess."

"Jess?" Garen’s gaze grew serious.

"You know about it too?" The man glanced at Garen in surprise. "As a Form One totem user, you sure are well-informed. Since I happened to meet you on the street, I might as well explain the situation to you, so you can help to advise Goth if you ever meet him."

Garen nodded.

The man fell silent, although organizing how he should explain what happened next.

The carriage also slowed down very considerately.

"Actually, be it Jessica being Empowered and taking away the Heart of the Dragonshadow, or Goth’s assassinating his own father, all of this was already planned from the start." He finally spoke slowly.

His deep voice echoed slowly around the carriage, making it seem even more solemn.

"Jeanria Jess used to be one of the higher-ups in the Obscuro Society. She infiltrated Iron Tank City, but accidentally developed feelings with the Grand Duke… sigh… and their feelings grew stronger by the day. We don’t know a lot of what happened in between, but in the end, we think Jess threw away all her standings for love, gave up everything she had before, and chose love. And she became pregnant with Goth. After she threw away everything, she realized that the one the Grand Duke truly loved wasn’t her."

The man paused.

"Jess was a very proud and single-minded person, she gave up everything she could have for the Grand Duke. After abandoning everything, and getting pregnant, she went alone to the Grand Duke for solace, and realized that the Grand Duke didn’t really love her, but was only playing with her. Back then, the Grand Duke was young and handsome, talented and capable. There were too many people in love with him, so he hadn’t taken this tolerably pretty girl seriously. And then… the tragedy began."

"So this was the source of it all." Garen breathed out softly. "The deeper the love, the deeper the hatred. She set a trap on Goth for twenty years, and now it has finally taken effect."

"Oh, life…" The man sighed, "We make a lot of mistakes in life, choose the wrong things, but never let your mistake be unsalvageable…" He seemed to have remembered his life as well.

"Then where is Jess now?" Garen asked the most critical question, the one most important to him.

"Dead." The man laughed rather helplessly, "Why else do you think Goth’s Blackfield Bird could be activated that easily? That’s a peak-level totem that only appeared once in history!"

...…

By the time he alighted from the carriage, it was already afternoon.

The orange sunlight dyed the entire inner city a sea of golden-red.

Garen glanced at the carriage as it drove into the distance, standing at the door to the War Guild headquarters. For a while, his emotions were inexplicably complicated.

He still remembered Goth’s mother, that gentle and beautiful middle-aged woman. She gave off a feeling like a spring breeze, and he just couldn’t see through her, but to think that she was hiding such a deep vengeance within her heart.

"If she’s Jess, maybe everything can make sense now…" He touched the Derivator in his pocket. "The Derivator has to ability to connect at all times, so if Jess wanted to hide and carry out her own plans, she naturally couldn’t carry a Derivator with her. Maybe she would destroy her own Derivator directly, and ask headquarters to get her a new one. That way, that means this Derivator’s appearance near Iron Tank City was also planned ahead."

His thoughts turned quickly, and he was just about to understand everything.

"Because Jess didn’t want a Derivator at all, perhaps even Goth’s igniting the furnace explosion to destroy the base was also a part of her plan." Although this explanation was still flawed, it was nevertheless very complete as is.

Walking up to the War Guild, Garen glanced at the Grand Duke’s residence for the last time.

He didn’t know how Goth was doing now, but it was evident that right now, he was already on the brink of breakdown.

"Oh, life…" Garen sighed deeply, and turned to walk into the Guild. He knew, that this was the critical time for Goth to truly metamorphosize.

The Grand Duke had been destroyed by his own heartlessness in the end. Although his actions were very common in the world of aristocrats, it was extremely unfortunate that he chose the wrong target.

***************

Half a month later…

Garen sat by the desk, quietly studying the second tactic.

In the scarlet study, Angel and Reylan took up one corner each.

Angel was playing with a small silver knife, tossing it up and down, a mischievous smile on her lips. Her gaze would sweep over Garen occasionally. She was wearing skin-tight brown leather armor, her long slender legs wrapped in brown leather leggings, making her look like a forest hunter on the hunt.

Reylan was wearing a grey robe, her terrifying face hidden with the hood. She sat in a wheelchair with an air of hostility, staring at Angel at the side with some jealousy.

"I wanna join in Brother’s War Chain," Reylan said in a deep voice.

Garen’s pen paused, as he raised his head to glance at Reylan.

Angel also looked at Reylan in surprise, the knife in her hand pausing slightly.

"I won’t let a woman prettier than me get too close to Brother," Reylan said darkly without holding back.

Garen’s expression looked instantly speechless. Based on how Reylan looked now, didn’t that mean even sixty-year-old grandmas couldn’t approach him now?

Reylan was totally unfazed, her icy cold gaze sweeping over Angel like a poisonous snake. "There are far too many ways to make someone wish they were dead…" she hinted, and turned the wheelchair to leave the room, closing the door quickly.

Garen smiled wryly at Angel, whose expression had obviously changed.

"Why do you have such a crazy little sister!?" Angel sat down promptly and angrily. "To be honest, if she weren’t your little sister, I’d really want to squish her dead with a slap!"

Garen didn’t really know what to say either, should he be grateful that his brainwashing was too successful, or should he be worried around Reylan’s overly extreme thought processes?

"Be a little more forgiving, Reylan is actually a good person." He could only comfort her like that.

"Good? You haven’t seen how your little maid is always pale as a sheet from fear." Angel was speechless. "The forger from my team is also so scared that he only dares to live on the first floor. Will your sister get jealous as long as it’s a woman?"

Chapter 324: Leave 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

She stood up again, walking to the window and looking down.

"Come to think of it, it’s weird but even though you obviously have nothing standing guard here, not a single monster dares to enter the vicinity. Looks like you must have used some secret methods."

The streets of the suburbs underneath them were empty, without a thing in sight, and that was what piqued her interest.

Garen smiled. There were ten Deep Swamp Crocs hidden in the shadows, the Dual Headed Salamander was waiting in the labyrinths underground, the Petrifying White Dragon was hibernating in the ground underneath the suburbs. After eating too many monsters, these instinctive monsters would also know that this wasn’t a place to mess around with.

Even Form Three monsters would not purposely start trouble here without a definite benefit to gain. The scent of two Form Three Silver Totems was enough to completely mask the smell of humans in the villa.

"How’s your situation now?" Garen asked casually. "It’s been a while since you reached Form Two, right? Any new developments?"

Angel continued to toss the knife in her hand.

"Developments are average, the regular Form Two totem is no problem. I can take two on at once, and I have to thank your Exhaustion Ray for that, this solidifying tactic works pretty well."

"You have to speed up your own growth, the times wait for no one." Garen closed the notebook in front of him. "I also plan to move elsewhere, this place won’t be inhabitable soon."

"Why? With surroundings like these, where else would you want to move to?" Angel was taken aback.

"This place isn’t that safe anymore, I plan to return to Kovistan," Garen replied calmly.

"Kovistan?! You’re crazy!" Angel stared at Garen with an expression of shock. "It takes at least three days to reach Kovistan from here, and that’s including the steam train! If you want to walk, it’ll be at least five or six days. Do you know how many monsters there are between that? Even the Form Two monsters might come in droves!"

Garen didn’t explain, only smiling.

"What does your whatchamacallit group plan to do?"

"It’s the Hunting Group!" Angel frowned and corrected him. "Our plans, hmm, we plan to scrounge a living around Iron Tank City. Now that all the knowledge in Iron Tank City is open to all, it’s practically heaven. As long as you have the ability to, you can crawl your way up!" She whistled. "I heard that the White Dragonhawk Grand Duke died and was resurrected. To think that the Dragonhawk King has the ability to fake death and resurrection, did you know that?"

Garen paused.

"Fake his death and then get resurrected?" Comprehension quickly dawned on his expression. "I never did know about that."

"The situation in Iron Tank City is not bad right now. The fact that the Grand Duke wasn’t dead after all really raised the spirits of many commoner totem users. That damned Goth assassinated his own father, and he’s apparently been executed by burning, incinerated directly in the furnace." Angel casually told him the important matters that had been happening recently. "I heard that on the night of the memorial tower, the Grand Duke suddenly sat up in his coffin, and nearly shocked the guards into wetting their pants."

"Is that so?"

Garen just kept smiling.

The news he was hearing now was slightly different from that of history, but the change happened anyway.

Right now, on the Kovistan side, his hometown of Lush Forest district was probably experiencing a change as well.

His father on this world, Vanderman Trojan, his cousin Sofea Hathaway, and those normal, harmful friends of his. And there was his previous crush, Aquarius too.

He had left for so long. It was almost a year, so it was time for him to go back and check. And it was time to return to being that Acacia from before as well.

The Royal Alliance was currently at a disadvantage, but it was still huge. As long as the three strongest countries at the core didn’t fall, the Alliance would never encounter any sort of problem. The three strongest country powers wove together, creating the terrifyingly large three departments.

"I heard that the revived Grand Duke plans to take the initiative and attack, trying to clear the straggler monsters in the surroundings as much as he can. If you have to leave, go check out the outgoing team just before you set off, it’d be a lot safer if you follow behind them too," Angel advised him.

Garen was planning to rely on his Silver Totems to protect him the entire way, so he could solve the Derivator’s hidden problem and upgrade his own core totem in the meanwhile. Right now, his potential points were snowballing by the day.

The Derivator’s hidden problem, upgrading his core totem and finding Solidifying Tactics to increase his physical qualities. These were the three goals he had set for himself.

"Why don’t you just come with me? And bring your group, I have a way to solve the camouflaging problems," Garen said directly.

"I can tell, what with how confident you look." Angel laughed. "After dealing with you for so long, I’ve gotten to know you, and you don’t do anything you’re not sure of. Last time I thought you couldn’t hold up on your own, but you’re doing quite well despite living in the outskirts. Looks like you’re no weaker than I am…"

"As long as you’re clear about that." Garen didn’t explain further. "How about it? Won’t you consider?"

"I still need to rely on the War Guild for my Legacy…" Angel was conflicted. "And I’ll need a lot of resources too."

"It’s alright, there’s always hope," Garen said determinedly.

Angel looked at his expression of confidence and was slightly hesitant. But then she thought about the series of events happening recently, and how far away she was from Form Three. She clenched her teeth.

"Fine! I’ll go with you! I’m telling you in advance, I already have two elite Form Two totems, it’d be extremely hard for me to reach Form Three."

"No rush…" Garen wasn’t worried in the slightest. Once he got back to the Royal Alliance’s territory, there would definitely be as many resources as they could want, now that most of the totem users were incapacitated. It would definitely be a lot better than Iron Tank City, which was relatively poor.

The two of them continued to discuss some other areas of cooperation in detail. With the War Chain connecting them, Angel felt a sense of belonging with Garen. After their chat, they finally heard cheers coming from the direction of the inner city.

"They must have killed off a few more groups of monsters in the surrounding outskirts," Angel said with a laugh. "It’s always been like that these past few days."

Garen nodded. "We prepare to leave in a few days. We’ll do as you said, and set it at the same time as the Grand Duke’s rounds."

"Sounds good."

*********************

Five days later…

Large tides of monsters flowed towards the inner city from three directions around Iron Tank City.

After the flood of monsters, it was the three spots of Form Three monsters.

Iron Tank City, which looked like a white disc, seemed like it was being flooded from all directions by countless black ants, and there were occasionally larger insects among the ants.

Outside the city, on a tall yellow cliff.

Garen wore grey robes, several carriages stopped behind him. These horses were all purely black, with horns and fangs. They looked like horses on the surface, but they were polluted animals.

Angel and four members of the Hunting Group gathered to discuss something in whispers. The few of them looked at the large group of monsters walking around them curiously, and also had a mysterious respect for Garen, who brought them out.

The black monsters flew across their heads, black shadows gliding past, as they flew towards the inner city.

Reylan sat in a white armchair, counting something with her pen and paper. She kept writing and switching many complicated equations and numbers. No one except her could understand them.

Meanwhile, Lala was constantly on hand and ready to take care of Reylan.

Garen looked far and long at the inner city that was slowly being surrounded by the monster tide.

In the inner city’s defensive area, a circular hole was opening slowly.

A group of people in black hoods riding black horses slowly walked out of the hole, each of the riders wearing extremely heavy black armor under their hoods.

The man leading them all was tall and stout, sitting with a straight back on a large horse. His black helmet completely wrapped up his head, so that all anyone could see was his slightly red eyes.

His whole body was wrapped inside the magnificent and imposing armor, making him look like a moving iron tower, as he slowly rode out of the defensive circle.

Bang bang…

The huge horse’s hooves stepped on the ground, leaving fist-sized holes, and throwing up sprays of dust and tremors.

Ker-chak…

The rider suddenly raised his head, his whole body of armor making slight noises.

A breeze blew by with a whoosh, picking up the long white hair from underneath the rider’s helmet, and making the waist-long hair fly in the air.

With a clang, the rider suddenly unsheathed the huge sword at his waist.

"We fight to protect the weak and elderly! We fight for justice and honor! I am the Grand Duke Cadersman, King of Glory."

"This is a fight for the people, to retreat is to give up!!" He abruptly raised his long sword. "Charge!!!"

Countless monsters rushed at him fiercely. The Three-eyed Black Bear and the Black-winged Bird returned, bringing even more huge Form Three monsters with them as they charged forth.

The heavy footsteps grew heavier with each step.

All the sounds were instantly overwhelmed by the strange cries and roars.

A pair of enormous black wings appeared suddenly behind the black-armored rider. With him in the center, a huge vicinity of black spirit light appeared out of nowhere, and any monster that entered this territory was instantly disintegrated, as though torn into pieces by some tremendous power.

Several Form Three monsters rushed at the Black Territory madly.

Screech!!!

There was suddenly a loud cry, and in the sky above the entire Iron Tank City, the illusion of a huge black bird began to materialize slowly, covering the entire sky.

The black rider sat on his huge horse and didn’t move. The huge horse advanced slowly, the black spirit light as though a mouth swallowing everything in its path, devouring all the monsters it touched and turning them into mincemeat.

Nothing could stop his advancing. The black spirit light was like a plague that kept spreading.

The Three-eyed Black Bear roared, and finally turned around to run away.

Many black riding soldiers gushed out from behind him, charging at the group of monsters on the outside. They were like a black current, mercilessly piercing into the monster tide.

From far away, the black rider suddenly looked at Garen’s direction.

Garen met his eyes as well.

"Is this your decision? Goth, I wish you luck..." He murmured softly, sighed, and finally turned around to leave the cliff.

The carriage slowly turned around, arranged in one line, and drove into the distance.

"Charge!!"

Amidst the endless cries for blood.

Goth was like a pitch black coral, his body surrounded by thick black smoke. It was the terrifying air that came from between the black feathers.

Sitting in the middle of the battlefield, all the sky above covered his shadow.

Chapter 325: Conjecture 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

The golden sunlight scattered.

Amidst the emerald grass, a yellow dirt road curved and winded ahead into the distance.

On the road, three black carriages drove slowly ahead.

Garen sat in the carriage, quietly looking out the carriage window.

On a high mountain far to their left, there was a line of grey fortresses, their serrated surrounding walls wrapping them up in the center. Some parts of the wall had already been knocked down. Everything was silent.

A few huge black bats were circling above the forts, and there was even a black bat flying out from inside the fort.

There was the smell of something burning in a huge fire in the air.

Garen took out his pocket watch to check the time: 3:24.

"Let’s rest for a bit, we’ve already been on the road all morning," he said calmly.

He didn’t speak loudly, but it was just enough for the other two carriages to hear him.

He sat in the middle carriage, and Reylan sat right opposite him.

The carriage in front of them carried Angel and her Hunting Group. Behind them was Lala and some supplies like food and drink that they had to bring with them.

The three carriages instantly stopped at the same time. The three aberrated black horses naturally stopped without requiring anyone to order them.

Garen opened the carriage door and got off the carriage. He raised his gaze to look at the surroundings.

Everything around him was emerald green grass plains, with flower bushes on each side to welcome travelers. The bushes had little red and yellow flowers, unusually vibrant. The breeze made these tiny flowers sway in the wind continuously.

He followed the plains and gazed into the distance. The green grassy plains continued to the fortress at the faraway mountain, with dying yellow weeping willows dotting the large swathe of green in between.

Garen raised his head to look at the fort, frowning slightly.

"These are the private fortresses near Iron Tank City, we haven’t left the governance territory of Iron Tank City yet." Reylan alighted from the carriage behind Garen, her voice deep. "We need at least one more day to leave the territory, judging by our current speed."

"Looks like that fortress has already been conquered," Garen guessed.

"Definitely, the ones flying in the sky are Carrion Bats. These bats come out in the day and rest at night. Unlike normal bats, they only eat rotting corpses," Reylan replied calmly. "Carrion Bats will only appear where there’s no danger, they’re very cowardly. Be it monsters or humans, they’re all things these bats think they should avoid."

She took out a small notebook, and started to carefully note down something. He didn’t know what, and could only hear the scratching of the pen she brings with her everywhere on the paper.

Garen nodded, indicating that he understood.

"How much longer can our supply of food and water last?"

"I’ll call Lala out. She knows the answer to this best," Reylan frowned, and walked directly to the third carriage.

She quickly got onto the third carriage, but he didn’t hear her scolding Lala.

"Brother, come and look. Lala seems to be pretty badly sick," Reylan’s voice came from the carriage.

Garen glanced at the Hunting Group members, who had just gotten down from their carriage, waving as a way of telling them to rest. Striding towards the third carriage, he stepped in from the wide open carriage door.

It was slightly cold and dank in the carriage, all sorts of miscellaneous items in barrels littering the dark interior. The yellow wooden barrels were wrapped into a cross with metal belts. Lala leaned on the wooden barrel, her face flushed and her breath panting.

"Cough… cough…" Lala coughed painfully, the sound of phlegm in her throat. She held her chest with her hand, as though unable to catch her breath. Even when she sat on the ground, it was weakly.

She only wore a grey summer dress, without long socks.

Garen surveyed Lala’s entire body, crouched down, and lightly picked up the cloth on the right shoulder of the dress, carefully taking a black speck off from it.

"I… feel like… can’t breathe…" Lala said with difficulty. Her gaze on Garen was as though she saw her savior, her eyes lighting up.

Garen sighed, pressing her chest lightly with his right hand.

"Brother!" Reylan’s voice came from beside him, sounding unhappy as she grabbed Garen’s hand, "It’s just a servant, it’s fine if she dies, but don’t let her pass it on to you."

Garen glanced at her. Reylan’s pale yellow eyes shone with jealousy and dissatisfaction. She averted her gaze slightly, turning her hateful glare at Lala instead.

"She’s having an asthma attack, it was my fault for not thinking ahead. I let her live for a long time in a place with bad air circulation, and a breeding place for bacteria and other microorganisms as well. She’s just a normal person, it’s already not bad that she managed to stay this long without falling sick."

"Let her die, we don’t have any medicine for asthma." Reylan’s gaze flickered. "I’ll take care of these supplies for you."

"Leave for now," Garen said calmly. "Be a good girl."

Reylan glared at Lala unhappily, before she finally got off the carriage.

Garen turned around, suspending his right palm over Lala’s chest. His fingers expanded rapidly, turning into five thick black steel rods.

Smack-smack-smack…

His fingers instantly began dotting Lala’s lungs quickly.

"I don’t know the actual healing method, so I can only reduce your symptoms for now. And besides, I’m not really sure that it is asthma," he said softly, looking at Lala relax as he continued his treatment.

Her soft chest kept shifting into different shapes underneath Garen’s hand.

Lala had just recovered when she felt the strange sensation on her chest, and her face flushed again. She turned her head to aside, unsure of how to reply.

On the other hand, Garen was unperturbed. After quickly solving the problem of the blocked blood qi in her lungs, he finally added a bit more force into his palm.

Wah!

Lala pitched forward, and coughed out a mouthful of black phlegm.

The black phlegm was about to land on Garen’s body, but he flicked his fingers to shoot out a blast of air that shot it out of the carriage and onto the grass far away.

Garen stood, his heart sinking slightly.

"Once you fall sick at this time, under these circumstances, it’s very hard to find medicines to treat you. Right now, all I can give you are medicines to reduce the inflammation and coughing. The rest is up to you."

Lala nodded. "It’s fine, I’ll get better soon." She smiled at Garen, telling him not to worry.

However, Garen frowned. "I found cockroach droppings on your clothes, it’s best if you don’t stay here anymore. Switch carriages."

Lala nodded, she noticed this reason as well.

Garen shook his head and got off the carriage, coming face to face with a thunderous Reylan.

"What’s the matter?"

"You shouldn’t have agreed to let her come along," Reylan said in a low voice. "That person is a burden. She doesn’t have to worry about anything, and now that she’s fallen sick, she can’t do any little thing at all! Why should we keep her?"

"You’re being a little extreme, Reylan," Garen frowned. "Her family died in the previous war, and now she has no other relatives, so she has no choice but to come with us."

"So what?" Reylan glanced at that carriage jealously, "Brother, don’t tell me you want to fuck that whore? Isn’t she just a little prettier, with slightly better skin!? Do you still expect to enjoy yourself under these circumstances? If it was any normal time, I’ll catch as many as you want for you! But now’s different!"

Garen looked at her expression and knew that she was getting more and more jealous of Lala. After her own face was destroyed, she got unusually jealous of other women with whole faces.

"I promised her that if she worked for me, she would get sufficient safety in return. Right now, I haven’t achieved that promise yet," he said softly. "Alright, Reylan, I know you’re in a bad mood, but don’t take it out on others!"

Reylan didn’t say anything else, but her expression grew darker, and finally she turned and left without a word.

Garen massaged his temple, feeling a headache coming on.

Looking at the sun above him, the golden sunlight was bright but not very warm.

Compared to Lala, Reylan was indeed a lot more important. She was still teaching him a lot of basic knowledge on how to study the Derivator. Right now, he had no choice but to rely on her. That was why Garen couldn’t afford to piss her off either.

But her twisted view of the world and values could indeed cause the team a great deal of trouble.

From the Hunting Group’s side, Angel walked over, her expression confused.

"What’s the matter?"

"Lala fell sick, it’s probably acute asthma," Garen replied helplessly. "She’s the only normal person among us, and her body isn’t that strong either, plus she got hurt before. It’s already not bad that she only fell sick now."

"Now what do we do?" Angel also frowned. She also had a pretty good impression of Lala, the dutiful maid. "I still have some Tavinipin here, take it to her and it might help."

"Should be okay."

Garen took the medicine to Lala, and after she ate it, she did recover a little shortly. This sort of medicine was mostly to suppress coughing.

Garen didn’t think too much more about it. He let the Petrifying White Dragon lead the way, and had the Dual Headed Salamander ride two Petrifying Lizards to watch the rear. On the two sides, the Deep Swamp Croc and Resonance Hawk stood guard from a distance. They carried many parasites with them, chasing away any strong monsters that might appear nearby, and only allowing some weaker fellows to enter so Angel and the rest can train.

His potential points kept increasing, but at an extremely slow pace. It was far from his time in Iron Tank City.

They basically didn’t meet any strong characters at all in the wild.

After that, they proceeded for more than another day, all the way until they reached the border of Iron Tank City’s territory. All they met on the way were Form One monsters, with extremely few Form Two monsters. There was no need to chase them away at all, so Garen decided to let his subordinates ignore them all, letting them come in directly.

By now, his potential points had reached an unprecedented 125 points. He had been hoarding them since Iron Tank City.

He planned to hoard more at once, and then focus them into evolving the Black-Striped White Tiger.

******************

The pale morning sunlight shone in from the cracks in the curtains.

Garen slowly awoke from his dreams, massaging the back of his neck, feeling slightly sore. When he opened his eyes, he saw that Reylan, who was lying down opposite him, was sleeping soundly on her side.

Everything was quiet outside, except the occasional snorting of the aberrated horses.

He sat up from the cushion seats, and pulled away the blankets on his body, putting on his leather breeches. He peeled a wooden blank away from the wall of the carriage to their right and let it down, supporting it with two wooden sticks to form a simple table.

Taking up the dried vegetables and beef jerky that he hadn’t finished eating from last night, Garen took two large glasses of water from the water bottle, and tossed the dried vegetables and meat inside.

And then he held one glass in each hand, his palms glowing slightly like red jade.

After more than a minute, the smell of beef jerky and dried vegetables wafted throughout the carriage.

"Brother?" Reylan woke up from her sleep, looking at Garen with blurry eyes. With the table between them, she instantly saw the two large glasses on the table.

White steam floated out from the mouths of the cups, carrying a faint aroma.

Chapter 326: Conjecture 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

"You’re awake? Come eat something," Garen said with a smile. He loosened his left hand and pushed the cup towards her. The water inside was boiling, with some radish, cabbage and scallions floating on the surface, and expanded jerky at the bottom. The water in the cup had also turned into a pale milky white.

Reylan looked touched. She got up neatly, her hands cupping around the glass and feeling the heat it emanated.

"Your body’s a lot better, huh," Garen said softly.

"Mn," Reylan nodded. "My injuries have more or less healed, and there’s no problem with my stamina either. It’s just that the scars got left behind, so many scars…" Her emotions sank in an instant.

"If I want them to heal, I’m afraid…"

"Don’t say such negative things so early in the morning, you’ll have a chance." Garen rapped the table. "Alright, the others haven’t woken up yet, so let’s start today’s lessons."

"Sure, we’ll talk as we eat." Reylan quickly took a petite little red leather notebook out from beside her, putting it on the table next to Garen.

"I had collected these from my own memories, they’re information about biological engineering. Silver Totems and the research regarding the Derivator, all of it is very complicated, and dabbles in content from many fields. Biological engineering is just one of them, after that you still need to learn about material and energy science, as well as advanced mathematics. Of course, you just need to understand it, it’s enough for you just to be able to tell what’s good and what’s not."

"Biological engineering, material and energy science, advanced mathematics? Are these three subjects enough?" Garen asked.

"Of course, these three subjects are actually umbrella terms, if you want to be more specific, there are even more branches of study." Reylan nodded. "The Obscuro’s way is to evolve creatures, it’s different from the Royal Alliance’s way of tools. Obscuro seeks to use totem techniques to finally increase the level of their own lives, that’s why they developed creature totems."

The Royal Alliance, on the other hand, uses White Silver Totems. In other words, they develop the primitive totems to a certain peak, and their final path is to use the peak-level primitive totem to boost the original totem user in return."

"Both paths seem clearer now. They just use the same power differently." Garen nodded.

He picked up the Reylan’s notebook, and read through it carefully.

Because he had basic knowledge in advanced maths and physics from Earth, as well as some research knowledge here on this world, he went through the notebook in no time. Other than some extra formulas to do with totems, he understood the rest easily.

He had also studied biological engineering with his teacher Emin, just not as deeply as this.

"I’ve already taught you some of the earlier basics," Reylan said calmly. "Now I’ll tell you about the main points in this book. Once you got a hold of that, you’ll be considered a Beginner in biological engineering."

With that, she started to explain some of the important formulas in detail to Garen.

As she spoke, Garen quickly understood these formulas completely.

Finally, he saw some change in the skill pane at the bottom of his vision. A new skill icon slowly materialized, and lined up together in a pane together with the other knowledge types.

"Biological engineering: Beginner. (By understanding this, you have understood the principles of a creature’s internal and external structures; one of the compulsory studies in totem research.)’

It finally became a skill.

Garen also heaved a sigh of relief. Now that it was a skill, that meant he could use potential points to level up. As long as he had the follow-up knowledge, he could improve rapidly.

As for the other two subjects, as long as he understood it all, he just needed to find an opportunity to grab some research materials from the Royal Alliance and his old man. With that, he should be able to reach extreme heights in no time at all. He would then have a certain level of confidence to solve the Derivator’s secret problem.

He might be no good at everything else, but his ability to learn was nothing to scoff at. With enough potential points, it would be a cinch for him to steal research, systems, knowledge, and experience from others.

His potential points allowed him to drastically reduce his studying and comprehension time.

So far, the Derivator seemed to be lagging, so the other two Generals hadn’t contacted Garen for now, giving him a short buffer time. He needed to use this time to quickly solve the secret problem.

Based on his conjecture, the reason he didn’t develop a skill when he was studying biological engineering with his teacher Emin was because he hadn’t learned all the basic knowledge in this field. Now, with Reylan’s teachings, he had finally completed it, and obtained the skill icon.

Biological engineering, materials and energy science, advanced mathematics. Garen had learned some basics in all three subjects before, but in order to act normal, Garen purposely controlled his learning speed, so that Reylan wouldn’t notice that he was too fast.

Today, however, Reylan was tossing out all the last bits of knowledge, so Garen threw caution to the winds, memorizing and comprehending everything about these subjects immediately.

His body had now reached the peak of human understanding, achieving the uppermost limit where he didn’t need to worry about the subject requirements.

He completed the Beginner level in no time. Each of the three subjects became skill icons, one after the other, in less than four hours.

From the knowledge of these subjects, Garen also obtained a deeper understanding of Silver Totems. He especially understood a lot more about the key to how the Derivator controlled Silver Totems.

All the way until noon, the carriages finally continued moving on automatically under Garen’s control. He used the Derivator to control the horses pulling all three carriages, so he could carry them forward without a driver.

Cough cough…

The sound of coughing came from the first carriage again. Lala had been transferred to the first carriage. Her condition seemed to have become even more serious.

Garen woke up from his calculations, frowning slightly.

But there was nothing he could do. He looked up to glance at Reylan in front of him, but she didn’t seem to hear a thing.

"Totem users have their core totems, that’s why they can avoid infections from most of the outside bacteria, and be unafraid of diseases." Garen sighed inwardly. No wonder all totem users seemed to be looking down on others, the reasons came from all areas.

"Forget it, it’s more important to upgrade my core totem now. Without real power, I can’t do anything even if I found the medicine." He didn’t really know how to deal with this sort of bacterial infection either, and looking at Lala, it seemed to be more than just asthma.

He calmed his heart, his gaze falling on that part of his totem pane.

‘Core - Black-Striped White Tiger: Form One totem, upgradable. Probability of successful evolution: 11%. Potential point cost: 700%.

Ability: Tail Whip, Puncturing Crunch.’

After Garen’s gaze rested on the totem for three seconds, the entire icon become blurry, and then quickly cleared up. It was as though nothing happened, if he hadn’t lost seven potential points, Garen might even have thought that his eyes were the ones that went blurry.

"Once more." He was already numb to it. After throwing more than a hundred potential points last time without a successful evolution, this time it was mere child’s play to him.

Second attempt, failure.

Third attempt, failure.

Fourth attempt, also failure.

He didn’t know if it was a trick of the mind, but Garen vaguely felt as though his core totem changed a little.

Fifth attempt. Failure.

Brr…

Suddenly, a description in tiny red figures slowly appeared behind the icon.

‘Missing core: striped crystal. Unable to evolve. Begin returning of consumed potential points, a portion of the potential points caused a catalytic effect.’

The Black-Striped White Tiger’s icon instantly dimmed.

Garen paused. In that instant, he felt an enormous gush of clean, cool air gush out from the icon. After taking a round inside his body, it returned directly to his brain.

His potential point value shot up madly.

From a little over 130, it rapidly increased to 150, 170, 190, 210.

And only stopped at 213.

Garen’s heart settled.

"As I thought, when I evolve a core totem with potential points, there’s an accumulative mechanism to it. Looks like if I try to evolve it without the critical core, the potential points I pile on won’t disappear totally. Instead, they would be stored in the totem, becoming an accumulative power. This is just like before, potential points that didn’t successfully upgrade something would return to me naturally. Looks like the potential points I put on those failed evolutions didn’t disappear, nor were they wasted, they merely gathered inside the totem, and were used to accumulate power."

"Then why are there these probabilities?" He frowned again. "Or are these gene fragments different? Is it a problem with the activation probabilities? Is it a random chance of activation every time, or will it only activate and evolve after accumulating to a certain level?"

He suddenly remembered the biological engineering he just studied. Putting it together with the basic genetic knowledge he had from Earth, he suddenly made a bold conjecture.

"Could it be that each activation attempt is activating a gene fragment, and failure to activate means it would go to waste? Successful activation means successful evolution? That so-called probability, is perhaps decided by the total number and quality of the gene fragments. Failed activation would remove these gene fragments. In that case, how are the standards for success and failure decided?"

Garen fell into deep thought.

The activation mechanism for these potential points seemed to be all murky, as though there were some complicated calculations and rhythms to it.

"It’d be all clear if I explained it like this. Activation and evolution were always meant to choose the best direction from all the countless genes. And in order to evolve these certain genes, we would certainly need a certain amount of activation energy. These two aspects decide how the potential points evolve the totem."

"Firstly, there are the potential points needed to perform the lowest level of evolution. Just like how so many points were stuffed into the Black-Striped White Tiger before it finally started the first activation. The potential points before that weren’t evolving, they were accumulating the energy required for the first evolution. I will probably need some techniques to figure out if it’s evolving or accumulating."

"Secondly, there are the probabilities. After achieving the required number of potential points, it will start attempting evolution. If successful, the points will be utterly used up. If unsuccessful, some of the points will be returned, just like with the Black-Striped White Tiger. In that case, the primitive totems and Silver Totems should be using different evolution mechanisms."

Garen was beginning to understand.

Chapter 327: Thoughts 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

He had only evolved silver totems before this, never attempting it on a primitive totem, which was why he had absolutely no idea what the situation was. Now, it’s finally as clear as day what was going on.

Primitive totems are living organisms, which means their bodies naturally accumulate a certain amount of energy. Not only that, an increase of energy happens whenever food is consumed. This was the reason why evolution through potential points only needed one step – activation.

When it came to silver totems[1], it was completely different. They do not need to consume food, which also means that they are unable to accumulate energy. Everything is provided by the totem user. Which is also why evolution then takes two steps – accumulation and activation.

"It’s no wonder why Reylan and said that silver totems will sooner or later surpass primitive totems."Garen suddenly understood the biggest advantage when it came to silver totems. It was not the derivator, or control of the numbers. It was in regards to the difficulty of what was required to evolve.

His cheapskate dad from this world was into biochemical studies. Garen could not wait to reach there a little earlier, as he yearned to increase the level of his knowledge with those books.

"Striped crystal was something I used as to play with, in a way you would with a potted plant at dad’s when I was younger…I’d have never thought that black striped white tiger would need this as an evolution core."Garen was slightly emotional. "To think of it , there were a lot of rare items and resources over at dad’s…he sure lives up to his name as a scholar employed by royalty.

In Acacia’s memories, resources of this level were treated lightly, as they could be played with at random. The house was full of them.

As these were rare alternative sources and not mainstream evolution resources, when Garen first gained knowledge from Emin, it had never occurred to him the value of these items.

He only understood now that he used to live in a house full of treasures without knowing it.

Striped crystal is a type of strange, fascinating crystal that grows continuously when planted. As long as he returned home, he could have as many of them as he wanted.

Besides, black striped white tigers needed more than a hundred potential points before undergoing an evolution activation. Once the evolution succeeds, there is no telling how strong it will turn out to be.

Garen was filled with expectation.

He examined himself carefully.

"If we were to assess in detail, Silver totems are always placed in the outside world as they can’t be kept in storage. At this rate, the silver totem light will always be present. This is equivalent to the use of a core totem. If the trouble caused by the derivator was non-existent, I would have been equivalent to a third form totem user."

After Garen’s self-evaluation, his mind became absolutely clear.

"Now the biggest problem would be the derivator. As long as the problem posed by the derivator is resolved early, I would not have to worry about the silver totems going out of control. The core totem should be capable of an upgrade as long as I head back.

His vision finally swept across the black striped white tiger’s icon, the data above changed slightly.

"Core- black striped white tiger: First form totem, can be upgraded. Probability of successful evolution: 11%. Potential points needed to activate gene fragment: 700%. An accumulation of 145 potential points is needed to achieve a chain activation. Striped crystal is needed as a core resource.

Ability: Tail whip, Puncturing Crunch"

The talent and power data displayed was in line with Garen’s own understanding, which is why he was not surprised.

Even though there were still a lot of grey areas when it came to understanding the evolution of a primitive totem, Garen had decided to put probing further on hold.

As he returned to reality, he came down from the carriage.

Outside, the hunting group crowded around a bonfire cooking something; the mixture of white smoke and water vapour carried a pleasant smell.

Surrounded by a vast expanse of deep green plains, there were occasional clusters of dense woods.

A few Unihorn lizards circulated the skies, but were afraid to swoop down and attack the crowd; they reduced to only squawking.

Nearing late noon, soft rays of sunlight shone from the rear, casting long slim shadows against the crowd.

Garen and Reylan walked aside privately, discussing difficult questions on the 3 subjects in low voices.

Angel brought Lala, who was still coughing, and joined the circle of the hunting group, talking about anything under the sun.

The surroundings were not filled with the roars of monsters, which intrigued the people. Although, they boiled it down to the mystery behind Garen. When it came to facing the rest of the journey, they began to relax a little.

Only Garen, who was in the midst of discussion with Reylan, saw that right below his field of vision, his potential points that were fluctuating like crazy. It meant that the silver totems under his command were on a wild hunt, targeting large groups of monsters in the area.

"We are almost exiting the area of Iron Tank City, next will be a desolate no-man’s land. According to the slow rate that we are moving, even the nearest city would require 2 or 3 days. Reylan stared at Garen with a little confusion,"What are your plans brother? Your current theory lacks concrete steps, I hope to get my hands on better research tools as soon as possible."

Of course, Garen would never reveal that the reason they were moving at this speed was to increase his potential points. "You should be able to find a temporary set of research tools right? The stuff that you are teaching me now belongs to the forgers?"

"Indeed, forgers are luminarists that specialize in researching totems, but our direction is more towards researching living totems." Reylan nodded her head.

"Then, you should know if there is a way to empower humans without being controlled?" Garen finally asked the question he had been yearning to ask.

"Empowering humans is our main area of research. Empowering a body itself is nothing new; the technique required is nothing difficult, but there is not much use for it either. No matter how strong a body is, it is impossible to evolve more powerfully than carefully selected living totems. Over at the headquarters, a significant number of people chose to be empowered in order to extend their lives." Reylan confirmed what Garen had in mind. "Although so, I do not recommend you to do that, brother."

She paused, "Top level primitive totem users have encountered a weird phenomenon. The totem light brought by their totems would bring changes to their own bodies, making it stronger and healthier, as well as extending their life. There were even totem users that merged themselves with their totems, becoming a collective body. This was the highest power imaginable achieved, which was also signified the birth of empowerment."

"Elemental totems, Plant totems, Animal totems. In actuality, these 3 types of totems would definitely reach that stage. The main body and the totem will merge to become one, transforming into an inhuman being that exhibits the terror of a totem. This is Obscuro Society’s main goal. Brother, if you want to walk this path, the requirements are of high difficulty. When it comes to technical abilities, even I myself would not be able to help. This type of technical ability requires too much, even if I were to research for more than ten years, it would not guarantee any success." Reylan rejected Garen’s train of thought, "Obscuro society had researched for so many years, and only reaped a small area of technical success. Let’s not even consider the possibility if I were to do this alone."

Garen smiled, changing the topic. "So how do totem users define their abilities?

"Usually evolution is divided according to Form; the first form is definitely incapable of beating second form, and a form 2 definitely incapable of beating third form and so on. Besides that, there are tactics and precious heirlooms that will affect the level of strength. Of course, there is also the manipulator’s strategy and natural talent. Let’s put everything aside and talking about totems alone. Of the totems, the strongest is The Ultimate totem. This means that the totem has reached the highest level imaginable for evolution. Ultimate represents the end of possible evolution. Although such, when it comes to which ultimate totem is stronger than the other, it boils down to the nature of the body itself. The better the nature of the body, the harder it is to evolve, but the stronger it is after evolution. If the nature of the body is good and the number of evolution undergone is high, when and if the totem has finally evolved into its final form, it would be horrifying. Just like the black striped white tiger that you have brother, if it evolved into the fourth form, the power it holds is unimaginable." Reylan explained carefully.

"But no one even knows if there is a third form; no one has been able to evolve this thing." Garen shrugged his shoulders.

"That’s because its foundation is too strong, the difficulty of evolving it is extremely high."Reylan shaked her head."I suggest you to look for a new core totem when you can."

"We’ll see."Garen has not given up yet.

Garen and Reylan talked a lot when they were together. This helped him to have a deeper understanding of totem users.

In the evening, the hunting group made potato and meat broth, served with stale bread, and an apple per person. They ate as if it were a feast.

A group of people sat around the bonfire barbecuing, their bodies and hearts were warm.

The temperature dropped in the late evening; everyone was freezing. Lala, an ordinary person, felt the same way and wrapped herself with blankets near the fire, her face still red. Obviously the sickness hasn’t left her body.

"Further forward is Ferrochrome. Ferrochrome is a small town at the borders of Tilan City and Aisley City. I went there for a holiday when I was younger, and the red tea biscuits there are amazing. I am not sure how it’s like now…" Amongst the hunting group, a petite young lady spoke in a soft voice, she seemed a little down.

"In this kind of environment, I would think there is but a few human habitations."

"Tilan City and Aisley City?"Garen was not familiar with these two places,"These two cities, which are richer in resources? Anyone knows?"

"Chief, Aisley City is very rich in resources, are you lacking any evolution resource ?" That petite lady said softly towards Garen. She and her companions have always called Garen and his sister Chief. Reprimand in them for this didn’t work, and after a couple of times, Garen just gave up and allowed them to called him whatever their heart desired.

"I want some striped crystals." Garen thought of attempting to look for the item along the way. As everything now was pretty chaotic, and deaths were prevalent, resources have been left unused. Who knows if he will be able to get his hands on it ahead of time. If he could find it along the way, he wouldn’t have to speed up the journey anymore; going at a slower rate to increase his potential points would be the wiser move.

"When it comes to striped crystals, I know which place has them." A black shirt guy who didn’t really like to talk much from the hunting group voiced out.

Seeing that everyone is the crowd turned to look at him, the guy fiddled with his collar.

"There are striped crystals in Aisley City, I have seen it in the city museum. It is embedded into a crown that is being kept as a relic."

"You are talking about the Prime Crown right? I have heard of that crown, never have thought it to be in Ailey City’s museum."A man from the back of the group whispered.

Angel nodded her head and looked to Garen, he was already deep in thought.

After thinking for a moment, Garen spoke out again."From here, if we were to turn into Aisley City, how long would we need? Anybody knows?"

The petite lady was most familiar with the geographical area, and answered after some calculations.

"It is similar to our route now, just in the opposite direction. Our time would not be delayed. We will need to cross two paths, Aisley City and Tilan City. According to our current direction, we move towards Tilan."

"Vicky, how can you be so sure without a map?" The black shirt guy said in puzzlement.

"My family was from Tilan, I have explored the surrounding areas." Petite Vicky said. "So what now? Do we head towards Tilan City? Chief." Her gaze fell on Garen. She was always intrigued by this powerful and mysterious man. His relationship with Miss Angel had seemed a little unusual.

"Since it does not affect the distance, let’s change it." Garen nodded his head. "Do you guys have any opinion?"He looked towards Reylan and Angel.

Both of them shook their heads, signaling that they did not have any opinion.

Translator's Thoughts

J_Squared J_Squared

1. Author mistakenly wrote primitive totem

Chapter 328: Thoughts 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

"Wasn’t our departure from Iron Tank City according to your wishes anyways?" Angel said. "If it is possible, do you wish take a short visit to your hometown, Daer and Vicky?" She looked towards Vicky and the guy in black.

The petite lady and the black shirt guy were silent at the same time.

"Thank you Miss." Vicky said softly and lowered her head, silent again.

Garen said calmly.

"If it is possible, I hope that we could take along everything we need during the journey. The resources in Aisley City should be abundant. We will arrange our affairs later according to the threat of the situation.

"Alright." Angel nodded her head.

After dinner, some fed their horses while most returned to their carriages. 3 horse-drawn carriages were tied to a cluster of trees by the side of the road. It was covered with some branches and hay in an attempt to keep it hidden.

Garen returned to his carriage and took a glance at his potential points.

It was now at 248 points.

He looked out from the window and saw Reylan and Angel exchanging a few sentences here and there. He had no idea what they were talking about. Both of them sat near the fire; the atmosphere was strangely harmonious.

He retracted his gaze.

"Since I am unable to upgrade silver totems, let’s just upgrade another primitive totem."

He held out his forefinger. Behind him a blue light glimmered and a blue laser shot out. The blue laser landed on Garen’s fingertips, suddenly transforming into a neon butterfly.

The neon butterfly the size of a face basin lightly battered it’s wings, emitting a soft blue glow around it.

Garen let out a white gold aura, covering his surroundings to prevent anyone else from walking in on him without him knowing.

Then, his line of gaze fell unto the Totem column below his field of vision.

"Neon butterfly: First form totem, can be upgraded. Probability of successful evolution: 21%. Probability points needed for gene fragment activation: 500%. Non-chain activation.

Ability: Poison pollen attack (Dispersed in the form of poisonous pollen, only up to 3 times in a day. Effect: paralysis, death.

"This was the totem given to me by my teacher, which was also my first totem. Let’s see how my luck is. If my potential power is sufficient…"

Garen did not continue his thoughts, focusing instead on the icon.

After 3 seconds, "Buzz…"The icon blurred for a while and quickly became clear again. It failed.

The second time – the icon blurred and became clear again; it has failed yet again.

The third time – the icon blurred, this time it did not become clear right away, but stayed in that state for some time, and its whole body started to turn transparent quickly.

In less than 10 minutes, the entire neon butterfly the size of a face basin disappeared directly in front of Garen’s eyes. Only through the touch of his fingertips, Garen was clear that the neon butterfly was still at the same place it was before.

His face was filled with astonishment. "I remember when it came to neon butterflies, according the information teacher gave me, wasn’t the evolution supposed to turn it into a poisonous white butterfly instead of this?" Right before he left he had received some information from Emin; it was in relation to the neon butterfly. Amongst the info, there was a section that stated one of the evolution paths this butterfly could take: poisonous white butterfly.

But right now it was obvious his evolved butterfly was not a poisonous white butterfly, which was stated in the recorded data.

Garen looked carefully and could barely see the neon butterfly on his fingertips. There was only a small outline; if he were to use his 5 senses he wouldn’t be able to detect it at all.

He couldn’t help but looked towards the icon description under the totem pane.

"Color changing butterfly: Neon butterfly’s level two evolution, second form primitive totem. Can’t be upgraded, Ultimate totem.

Ability: Invisibility through discoloration (Senses and adapts to the subtle colors of the environment’s light rays, in purpose of achieving invisibility).

Reproducing offspring (The color changing moths reproduced can be used as a spying or investigative tool. Once every day.)

Poison pollen attack (Poisonous pollen can cause dizziness, hallucinations and paralysis. Effect upon contact.)

Garen wrinkled his brows.

Color changing butterfly’s abilities disappointed him a little.

When it came to sleuthing, he already had the beetle. In this very moment, hundreds of beetles are all around, ready to return with danger reports if it ever came to that. This ability was sort of redundant. However, the invisibility sounds good.

"Not all totem evolutions go according to our wishes."Garen shook his head. As he flung his fingers lightly, he thought he remembered something.

An idea came to him.

The color changing butterfly at the tip of his fingers flew up abruptly, its invisible abdomen laid a large amount of brown eggs; it fell unto the table.

These eggs were individually as large as the size of a fingernail, oval in shape.

Garen realized that the description on the color changing butterfly did not mention that there was limit on the number of offspring at all.

As he watched, the brown oval eggs began to rip apart; out of it wriggled transparent moths one by one.

He counted carefully, there were 25 moths.

These small moths soundlessly flew out from the window; under the control of Garen’s consciousness, they flew into the surrounding four directions.

As the days passed, Garen kept on increasing the number of moths; the numbers reached a hundred quickly.

The team has passed through a few empty villages, replenishing some of their basic resources. During this time, Garen’s moths slowly began to grow larger.

The only downside was, color changing butterfly’s offspring consumed silver pieces. It was a good thing Garen brought some silver pieces in preparation.

More than a hundred moths consumed 3 silver pieces in total.

But he had realized the advantage in having these moths.

There was no need for feeding, the only thing they fed on was the power of the totem light. Every time the color changing moths were let out, they could only be controlled up to 2 hours. A rest is needed after that.

These color changing moths were extremely covert. As they scattered around the surrounding areas, none of the monsters had ever managed to detect them.

Although finally, two of the parasitic beetles that were sleuthing from before disappeared. This cut off all contact with Garen’s deep swamp croc.

The group finally ceased their progress; Garen had given directions for them to stop. They will only move forward after he had investigated what had happened.

　　****************

At night, Garen stood at the edge of the carriage, looking into the faraway fortress of the hills above.

The fortress was built with stone bricks, a tall tower stood in the middle of it. There seemed to be minimal damage as the structures still looked as they should.

The fortress was accompanied with silence; no lights, no torches, nothing. Just pitch black.

Garen furrowed his brows.

"My sleuthing bugs disappeared in the area near this fortress." He turned back and looked at Reylan, who was traveling next to him, speaking in a low voice.

Three carriages circled around a bonfire, waves of faint heat emanated from that area.

Besides a man from the hunting group who was standing guard for Lala, the rest crowded near Garen.

"If my memory serves me right, this fortress may be dangerous. Although the areas nearby are paths we will have to go through. Both sides are terrain and lakes that are way more complicated and difficult to cross. If we were to make a detour, we would need at least 5 days to close in the great distance." Garen explained

"So we should try and see whether it is possible to go through here. If the monsters turn out to be too powerful, we will just leave immediately, correct?" Angel added on,

"Leila."

"Watch me, miss." A guy wearing a red cap nodded his head and lifted up his right arm. Immediately, a silver light shot out from the protective sleeve on his forearm.

The silver light landed on the ground in front and turned into a golden lioness right away.

Roarrrr…

The lioness growled and bent over to look at its owner. The tail was a living yellow snake. The head of the snake continuously hissed, coiling around and around while staring intently with its blood red eyes.

The guy with the red cap mounted the lioness and disappeared into the night, heading towards the direction of the fortress. Not a single sound was made.

Garen sensed the troops under his command: the deep swamp croc has already reached a number of 20, the beetles a number of 200. The dual headed salamander was just like a weapon generating war machine; it continuously produced a steady stream of deep swamp crocs, creating a massive army of second form totems. All she needed was time, and she’ll be able to produce large amounts of parasites.

Garen was confident; there was definitely not one third form totem in Obscuro Society that was as scary as this. Their evolutional direction only had a few definite types, which differed from his direction in relying on potential points for evolution; theirs was a controlled evolution with a clear direction.

Mostly importantly, till date, parasitic typed totems were unheard of. The most bizarre totem was the reproductive nest type totem, which was a specialty of the Obscuro society.

The legitimacy of this fact was confirmed by Rylan, who knew Obscuro Society best. Garen learned all this by prompting the answer out of her in an indirect way.

His evolution through potential points was seemingly different from Obscuro.

As he watched the guy in the red cap vanish into the darkness, he had an idea.

More than ten beetles followed Leila and crawled into the fortress.

The people from the hunting group knew that he was mysterious, and had at least 7 or 8 totems under his command. Private and secretive as he was, he always managed to do things none could imagine.

When they left Iron Tank City, everyone, including Angel, was rather anxious and insecure; it was the mysterious and unknown Garen that gave them the biggest sense of security and support. This was the reason why everyone unconsciously turned their eyes to Garen.

"Let’s wait a moment and see what happens. If Leila is able to return safely and verify the situation, I will give him a little reward." He smiled and said calmly.

He already had a vague idea in mind.

At this moment the number of deep swamp crocs produced by the dual headed salamander was way too many; it was an impossible feat to manage all of them in a way that maximized the purpose of creating parasitic beetles. Just feeding and planning alone took up too much effort.

But if he were to distribute it to other people and allow a portion of the beetles to follow the orders of others, this would strengthen the rest and allow them to invest their energy into feeding these beetles, ultimately reaching the larger goal in greater speed.

Using these beetles as rewards for the underlings, as long as they don’t backstab him, he’d be able to achieve the goal of upgrading his abilities safely. The beetles’ abilities will be used at a greater rate; the situation will not be out of grasp either.

All of a sudden Garen thought of something – What if Obscuro’s initial thoughts were similar to his? To issue the derivators out in order to increase their own power and overall strength, at the same time keeping the situation within the palm of their hands?

The excitement that bubbled up shortly before suppressed down again.

"It seems like I have to solve the derivator’s control issue..."

Chapter 329: The Nest 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

A group of people silently waited in the forest. Vicky lighted a few torches and distributed them throughout the group. The crackling of the flames could be clearly heard.

The croaking of frogs one after another could be heard in the distance.

Croak, croak..

Garen fixated his gaze in the direction of the fortress. He abruptly stretched out his fingers and gestured in the air. Black flames emerged as a dot from his finger tips, leaving black strands in the air.

Very quickly with the formation of the gestures, his eyes dilated and lost its focus.

"Sight sharing tactic?!" Angel was slightly startled. "So fast…" She stared at Garen in disbelief. Her complexion was complicated, seeming like she had thought of something.

After a whole ten minutes, a light roar came from the direction of the fortress. It seemed like the roar of a lion, but from a long way away.

"Let’s go. There is a problem here." Garen took the first step and moved towards the fortress. He seemed slow but was actually quick and had a rhythm to his steps.

The rest of the party followed behind him, but only Reylan could keep up with him. Angel and the rest had difficulty in keeping up, and had to summon primitive totems to carry them.

In the dark night, the group cut through the vast plains from the dark forest, and quickly headed towards the fortress. Only three swiftly moving orange flames could be seen in the dark, whereas their shadows were completely not visible.

Garen took the lead, following the pathway of the fort to directly arrive at the main entrance. The iron-clad wooden door was wide open, and the keyhole had obvious traces of damage.

The roar of a lion could be continuously heard from behind the door.

Garen went straight into the entrance.

There was a wide stone plaza within. As the faint moonlight shone on the plaza, it seemed like it was plated with a white-greyish layer.

In the middle of the plaza, Leila was commanding his serpent-tailed lioness in a battle with two black shadows..

Whenever the lioness let out a fierce howl, she would emit a circle of expanding pale yellow light, which would only disappear after expanding three metres. Every single time, the light would send the two black shadows flying and rolling on the ground.

The black shadows would then persistently get back on their feet and continued their assault.

Garen walked closer, trying to see the true forms of the two shadows with the aid of the moonlight.

It was two black panthers with bull horns on their heads.

They bowed their heads and pawed on the ground with their hooves like a bull. Air was coming out from their nostrils and their eyes were glowing red.

"They are not silver totems?" Garen carefully identified. Suddenly there was a flash of light in his eyes. "They are not totems, but mutated creatures who were infected. "

"Chief! They are not powerful, just very resistant." Leila shouted towards him. "Their speed is too fast. Although they have weak attacks, but because I’m totally unable catch them, I can only passively counter attack." A dejected expression could be seen on his face.

Moo!!!

One of the black bull panthers let out a roar, and directly dashed at the serpent-tailed lioness.

A dash like that might have been effective towards normal creatures, but not at all towards the serpent-tailed lioness with totem light.

The serpent-tailed lioness stood its ground and howled fiercely, emitting a circle of yellow light from its body, which immediately sent the black bull panther flying again.

With a bang, the black bull panther was savagely sent flying a long distance. Its four hooves left long black marks on the ground.

"Let me do it." Angel finally arrived behind Garen and dismounted from her black panther. Looking at the two black bull panthers, there was some mild covetousness in her eyes.

"These are living mutated creatures, if only the unit factory could be used to replicate them as totems.."

Reylan laughed without saying a word.

Vicky from the hunting group stood out.

"Do we need miss to act for mere speedy types? Let me do it!"

Before she finished her sentence, a yellow line leapt out from behind her and headed directly towards the two black bull panthers.

After two light hisses, the yellow line flashed across the two black bull panthers, and flew back towards Vicky’s shoulder. It was a fully gold mink. It obediently crouched on its owner’s shoulder and continuously licked its blood-stained claw. Its two eyes had a wolf-like dark green glow, giving off a dark malevolent aura.

Both the two black-bull panther were wounded by their side abdomens. After wobbling for a few more steps, they couldn’t support themselves and fell to the ground.

"Be careful! There are more of them around us!" Reylan yelled loudly.

Their surroundings were full of black shadows. The shadows of black bull panthers kept flashing by, carrying a heavy aura of silver totems.

Garen’s countenance changed slightly.

Among the totem auras, he could even feel second form totems, and it wasn’t just one. To be able to gather so many second form totems together, there might even be third form creatures.

"Retreat for now." Garen ordered in a low voice.

The few of them slowly exited the fortress gate, constantly on their guards against any ambush.

"There is certainly a nest here." Reylan muttered as she walked towards Garen’s side. Only Garen could hear her voice. "A nest is the Obscuro Society’s biological weapon plant, if only we could conquer one…"

"Weren’t these kinds of nest invented by the Obscuro Society?" Garen frowned.

"Of course not. They initially also found a special creature’s nest, then imitated it after that. But many of them were unrefined, and it was impossible to control the nests." Reylan explained. "There should be a black bull panther’s nest here. According to the Obscuro Society’s records, it is an agility type, and is decent among first form totems. Big brother, there are two ways for you to come in contact with the derivator’s control method. The first method is to find a derivator not owned by the Obscuro Society to shift your silver totems. The second method is to directly make adjustments to the original derivator."

"A derivator that is not owned by the Obscuro Society? Besides the Obscuro Society, are there others who have derivators like this?" Garen curiously asked.

"Actually, the derivator crystal was discovered by the Obscuro Society in the outside world. It only achieved this form through unique modifications." Reylan explained softly.

Garen immediately came to a halt.

Angel and the rest in front noticed it, and stopped as well.

"All of you stay on guard around the fortress. If you meet something you’re unable to fight against, immediately send signals through the fire bombs." Garen ordered. "Reylan and I have something to handle."

Angel frowned as she gave Reylan a glance. She didn’t say anything but nodded her head.

"Then we shall go back and wait."

Garen nodded.

As he looked at Angel and the others quickly leaving the fortress, he turned towards the black bull panther herd on the plaza, which was growing by the minute.

"How do we conquer the nest?"

"The first step is to clear up these black bull panthers, get rid of all the guards. The nature of a nest is like a plant. The roots are rooted in the ground to absorb nutrients. These black bull panthers are like the fruits. They are like vassals and guards who are being controlled." Reylan calmly said. "A black bull panther’s nest should only be a first form nest. There are minimal second form creatures. The black bull panthers gathered here should be all of them."

Garen heaved a sigh of relief.

"As long as there aren't any third form creatures. There are strong and weak third form creatures, but their abilities are troublesome. If we are unfamiliar with their abilities, it might lead to injuries or even death if we are not careful."

Both of them faced off against all the black bull panthers on the plaza.

Garen stepped forward. A few deep swamp crocs[1] crawled out from the shade behind him, while a resonance hawk was circling in the air above him .

He pointed at the tens of black bull panthers on the plaza.

The resonance hawk dived, letting out a horrendous cry. At that same time, there were sounds of resonant heartbeats.

Pok Pok!

Two black bull panthers leapt forward a few steps and crashed to the ground. There was blood on the side of their jaws as they laid there motionless.

Five deep swamp crocs armed with their long tails and pitch black hides crawled towards the black bull panthers. They darted forward time to time, grabbing the black bull panthers beside them with their jaws. They snapped the panthers into two and then flung them away.

The sharp claws of the black bull panthers could only leave minor scratches on the body of the crocs.

A few of the second form black bull panthers took on the deep swamp crocs. They were exceedingly swift, and their bodies were covered with black bone armor, like artificial abnormalities.

Owww!!!

As the second form black bull panthers bowed their heads, blue lightning arcs formed in between their horns.

Sheesh! The lightning arcs discharged a blue line and savagely landed on the body of a deep swamp croc. The electric current left a black burnt mark on its hide.

The deep swamp croc was knocked back by the current and retreated a few steps as it let out a roar signalling its injury.

"Electric current?" Garen instantly looked surprised. As he spread out his right palm, lines of black flames quickly erupted from his five fingers. Another tactic gesture was formed in the midst of the shadows.

Reylan was stunned at Garen’s feat. "Five...five sight sharing tactics!"

There has never been someone as crazy as this. Even among the countless elites in the Obscuro Headquarters, she has never met someone who could draw five tactics at once. Can a human’s hand be as agile as this?!

Garen wasn’t in the mood to notice Reylan’s reactions. His vision had split into five. Four of them were with the deep swamp crocs, while one of it was with the resonance hawk in the air.

The five different visions were monitoring the second form black panthers from different angles and directions.

The secret ideas that he had finally had a glimmer of hope of being realized.

"Electric current with totem light…..For me, doesn’t it have the same properties as the legendary dragon blood?" His eyes narrowed as he had a definite objective in his heart.

Through the sight sharing, Garen’s powerful martial arts body could finally reveal its strength.

He simultaneously controlled five totems, forming a defensive semi-circle around Reylan and himself. Every black bull panther that attacked was repelled with immense accuracy, or immediately bitten to death.

Every electrical attack from the second form black bull panthers would be blocked by Garen with the deep swamp crocs. The powerful electric attacks could only leave minor burn marks on the black hide, not causing significant damage to the giant crocs.

Garen’s gaze was still. His pupils faintly separated into five fan shapes, every fan presenting images from a different angle.

A second form black bull panther quietly crept towards to the back of Garen and Reylan. It lurked and hid its body in the dark, and took steps towards Garen’s rear.

Suddenly, it swooped quietly to grab the back of Garen’s head. There were traces of blue electric current on its claws.

As the sharp claws were about to touch Garen, from the right came a big black jaw.

Crack!

As the deep swamp croc’s jaw landed on the black bull panther’s abdomen, bone crackling sounds continuously came from its jaw. The croc brought its prey to the ground with a thud. Then immediately started to roll on the ground.

In a moment, after a few flashes of lightning arcs in its jaw, everything became still. The second form black bull panther’s corpse broke into two parts and fell out from the side of the deep swamp croc’s jaw.

The five totems were like meat grinders, annihilating every black bull panther on the plaza. Very quickly, the numbers of the black bull panthers gradually decreased. Finally, the two or three remaining looked at Garen in fear, as if they could run away any time.

Garen brought his tactic and control to a stop. As he looked at the black bull panther corpses all over the plaza, there was no hint of expression on his face.

"Let’s go to see the nest. How do we conquer it?"

Reylan retracted her surprise expression. She adjusted her wind-swept hood to cover her dry, ugly face.

"To control a nest is difficult indeed. But the core material to create the derivator could be obtained from a nest. It is called the Resonance Stone and has wonderful effects. After a splitting a resonance stone into two, one of the pieces could be transmitted through resonance to the other piece regardless of distance. Although there is a certain loss, but the frequency will be the same. Because of this, the Obscuro Society used it as a core for long distance communication. After complicating the simple resonance, then going through informationization, then coding, it will then have the communication function of the derivator in your hand."

"Then how do we concretely control the nest? With the Resonance Stone?" Garen asked.

Translator's Thoughts

J_Squared J_Squared

1. Author incorrectly wrote deep swamp lizards 深泽巨蜥

Chapter 330: The Nest 2

Translator:EndlessFantasy Translation

Editor:EndlessFantasy Translation

"Right." Reylan’s knowledge was indeed profound, as she talked about these secrets like household matters. "A nest has only one resonance stone. It is its core, and its heart. Without the stone, although they wouldn’t die, they would gradually wilt and become a normal plant. Two things have to be done to control a nest."

"What are the two?" Garen looked at the remnants of black bull panthers after the massacre by the deep swamp croc, then walked towards the tower in the middle of the fortress.

Reylan followed closely behind.

"The first step is to segment the resonance stone. Hold one half in your hand and leave the other half in the nest. You will be able to control the nest’s life with the resonance stone. As the plant as no intelligence, survival is their basic nature. With the resonance stone in your hand, you will gradually be filled with their aura. Naturally, you will be the master of the beings it creates."

"The second step is to remember the vibration frequency of the nest. It is like the password to a code. Only by remembering this you would be able to truly control the beings of the nest with the password. This is difficult, exceptionally difficult."

"How can we say no without giving it a shot?" Garen smiled.

The two of them followed the steps to the door of the tower.　

Garen stretched out his hands and pushed open the door.

With a deep groan, the door slowly creaked open. A large amount of dust continuously cascaded in the wind.

As they entered the tower, a dark hall instantly appeared in their vision.

In the magnificent hall, everything, including the walls, floors, fireplaces, oil paintings, sculptures, were covered in a dark green mucous membrane-like flesh.

Hanging on the wall opposite the door was a golden sun ornament. The golden ornament was covered in green flesh, and a water basin-sized ferocious eyeball was popping out in the middle.

The surface of the white eyeball was full of blood strands, with a black pupil in the middle. It constantly adjusted its focus as it kept a close eye on Garen and Reylan.

In the red lines of the eyeball, blood was clearly flowing into the inner part of the eyeball. The flow of blood in the translucent blood vessels was like delicate red sand, faintly emitting the sound of moving sand.

Garen looked around the hall.

To the left and right of the eyeball were multiple black bull horns. The horns were arranged in the formation of a saw. They seemed to sense danger as they slowly protracted and covered the eyeball like a big mouth with black, sharp teeth, completely protecting the eyeball.

"Disgusting. There’s a sour smell in the air." Garen frowned and covered his nose. "What do we do now?"

Reylan also took out a scarf and covered her nose.

"Every nest has a different internal form. You have to look for the resonance stone on your own, which is one of the difficulties of taking a nest. Take note that once the nest dies, the resonance stone will melt instantly, even if it has been retrieved."

Garen nodded. He paced around the hall as he observed the surroundings.

A white-gold aura slowly emanated from his body. The peculiar thing was the eyeball of the nest shrunk back slightly, as if it felt the great aura.

Garen realized it and looked interestedly at the eyeball. After he came to this world, this was the first time meeting a being that could sense his white gold aura.

"The nest will assimilate into the first building or area that it comes into contact with. This tower was also a structure that was assimilated by it." Reylan was explaining to one side.

Garen nodded, showing that he understood.

He stepped on the flesh-like surface on the hall, feeling its softness. It was like stepping on a rubber surface. There was even white slime sticking on his leg as he lifted it up, forming white filaments.

The white gold aura expanded incessantly. Garen, with complete concentration, shrouded the whole area of the tower with his aura.

Very quickly, he could thoroughly sense the blood flow of the black bull panther’s nest.

He grinned as he walked towards the wall on the left. He stretched out his hand and pressed it on an oil painting on the wall.

A deep swamp croc crawled out from behind him. It opened its large jaw and slowly extended its tongue armed with ferocious needles, aiming at where Garen’s palm was.

Garen stepped aside.

Chiiii!

The giant croc’s tongue shot out like a sharp arrow and pierced into the art on the wall. Very quickly, an oval-shaped red piece of flesh was retrieved as it retracted its tongue.

Its tongue held the piece of meat and slowly put it in Garen’s wide open palms.

"This should be the resonance stone," Garen said confidently. This was the largest focal point of the blood flow in the eyeball’s nest. It should be what Reylan was saying.

Reylan looked at Garen with surprise. He couldn’t comprehend how Garen could locate the resonance stone in such a short time. It looked like he had unimaginable methods.

"Next is to segment it. As the resonance stone is not considered as hard, it is easy to do. Big brother, you can carefully study the control mechanism of the nest. The Obscuro Society’s derivator also imitates this mechanism. Once you understand it, you can quickly resolve the concerns regarding the derivator."

Consequently, the two of them cut the resonance stone into two pieces, a big one and a small one. The small piece was then replugged into the hole in the wall.

After Garen’s aura expanded, he thoroughly memorized the blood flow of the nest according to Reylan’s explanations. It was tremendously fruitful.

As for the frequency of the resonance stone, Garen could feel that this oval piece of meat was indeed like a heart. It was beating lightly, but its frequency was messy and randomized. Even after holding it in his hand for a while, he couldn’t sense any repetition.

The two of them exited the nest tower. The black bull panther corpses all over the plaza had disappeared completely, leaving not even a trace of blood.

"Absorbed by the nest." Reylan wasn’t surprised.

"Let’s rendezvous with the others." Garen shrugged and took huge steps towards the door.

As they exited the deserted fortress, Angel and the rest were starting a bonfire nearby. They were scattered around the fortress as guards.

Angel and Vicky were trying to pry open snail shells with a twig. Leila and the remaining person from the hunting party were huddled together. They seemed to be recording something.

Garen took a glance at the group of people.

"Leila."

"Boss!" Leila instantly noticed Garen and Reylan coming out and quickly ran towards them.

A thought flashed through Garen’s mind.

Five black beetles crawl out from behind the group. The beetles had full-black bodies and were half the height of a grown man. Their jaws were full with sharp teeth, looking abnormally ferocious.

"Many totems users have their own way of sleuthing. However, the five black beetles here will be my reward to you to do that. They will fully obey you, but only simple commands can be used to convey your orders. Each of these beetles have power equivalent to a first form totem."

At his last sentence, Angel who seemed unapproving started to be slightly moved.

"First form totem? Impossible!" Angel couldn’t help herself. "Without totem light, no matter how strong the beasts are, they wouldn’t be able to stand against totems!"

"Who said that they do not have totem light?" Garen smiled and pointed at the beetles with his finger.

At that instant, there was faint black light glowing on the surface of the beetles.

Psssttt...

Angel, Vicky and the other two people from the hunting group had chills from the scene before them.

"Giving five level one totems to an outsider in one go!" Vicky couldn’t believe it. She fixated her gaze on Garen’s face, trying to find a trace of pain in his expression. But regretfully, she failed.

Garen’s expression was like deadwood, without any change.

In fact, the truth fit his expression.

The five beetles were only a tiny part of his army. By giving it away, he no longer had to worry about feeding them, and the deep swamp croc could very quickly breed a few more.

Moreover giving them away did not mean that they were free from his command. He was already in control of these beetles.

This was also a good way to recruit a team. With the benefits of totem strengthening, and having creature totems to order around, a team like this had overwhelming advantages. Of course, there was only one solidifying totem currently, but very quickly they would be able to increase the number.

It was Garen that looked down on the solidifying totems that were too weak.

This was the first time he encountered a nest. There used to be multiple nest appearances in Iron Tank City, but the Grand Duke penetrated the enemy lines and destroyed all of them, temporarily relieving the city from danger. This stopped Garen from really seeing a nest.

There was no way Garen would give up on the derivator at the moment. A large majority of his strength came from the derivator. Furthermore, he couldn’t stay in this state of lag for long. Once the elemental generals realized something was wrong, that would spell trouble for them.

According to Reylan’s description, the elemental generals had at least the ultimate form of elemental totems. They had incredible power, only second to the marshals with precious heirlooms. They were at least on the level of the former Grand Duke, considered to be on the level of fourth form aberration totems.

Although totems can be classified into animals, plants, and elementals, They were in fact of a unified division.

Such was the internal levels of the Obscuro Society.

After Garen obtained this information from Reylan, he used it as a standard to gauge his enemies.

The Obscuro Society categorizes all the totems under them into six levels.

First form, Second form, Third form, then Spiritualization, Fourth form, Fifth form.

Only the strongest two marshals have achieved the fifth form. Their exact strength was an unknown, but definitely not something an average person can match. In fact, this path was the path of the elemental totems and spiritualization was the beginning of elementalization.

　　所以凡是元素图腾,都至少是第三型灵光化阶段.哥德的父亲大公爵也是这个阶段,并没有达到第四型层次,只是手中的秘宝龙影之心对他有着提升.可惜,龙影之心也没了.所以才被数头三型灵光怪物逼得最终自爆.

All elemental totems were at least at the third form of spiritualization. Goth’s dad, the Grand Duke, was at this level. He couldn’t progress to the fourth form, but the Heart of the Dragonshadow increased his power level. Pitifully, the Heart of the Dragonshadow was gone, and he was forced to self-destruct by the third form spiritualized creatures.

In addition, Goth was currently at fourth form, after almost completely elementalizing his core totem, the King of the skies[1]. His precious heirloom also elevated his strength. But the most frightening fact was, this guy was improving every single day.

Vanderman, the father of his host body, Acacia, was considered a second form, while Aquarius was a third form, but evidently did not reach spiritualization. Angel was a second form, but for the elemental generals, they were at least at the stage of third form spiritualization. All generals had at least a third form totem. The only difference was whether it has undergone spiritualization, and the number of third form totems they controlled.

The truth was, with Garen’s current strength, he should not be afraid of any single elemental general. His two third form totems, the petrifying white dragon and dual headed salamander, were both incredibly strong. The petrifying white dragon was at third form spiritualization, but it was a pity it could no longer be evolved. Although the dual headed salamander wasn’t spiritualized, it was a relentless war machine.

According to Reylan’s judgment, spiritualization is obtained naturally through the evolution process. If they had poor innate talent or bad cultivating resources, the evolved totem will not have spiritualization. This is the difference between the quality of evolution.

Even the same type of totem will have differing strength with different cultivations.

Initially, Garen planned to follow this path steadily to the end.

However, with the emergence of the nests, and his increased understanding towards creature totems, Garen had some new thoughts.

Even though that was the case, he could only thoroughly pursue these thoughts after resolving the control issues of the derivator.

Chapter 331: Change 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

The wheels on the carriage turned round and round.

Garen turned sideways to look at the scenery outside the carriage window.

Up in the blue sky, a few enormous black dots were circling in the air slowly, making chirping noises in the distance.

The green grassy plains seemed limitless, and the continuous stretches of hills stood up high as a few black sheep the size of little cows lowered their heads and chomped on grass. They occasionally looked up in curiosity at the three carriages that passed by.

The early morning fresh air blew into the carriage window.

Garen lowered his head to look at the Resonance Stone in his hand, before playing with it gently.

The index finger on his left hand lit up suddenly with a black flame, and left a Tactic gesture in the air. His right hand continued to turn the Resonance Stone over in his palm.

Garen put his left hand down and picked up a pen on the table and dipped it in ink, before jotting all this down in his notebook.

Once he had finished his notes, he began to turn the Resonance Stone over again.

"How is it? Are they any results?" Reylan sat up from the opposite seat, which was also the bed area, and asked while yawning softly.

Garen nodded.

"Still alright for now. But it’s very difficult. This Detection Tactic that you gave me is quite good, it can be used to increase these kinds of frequencies within specific degrees, as well as detect them. The only downside is that it requires a lot of Silver Energy."

"Silver Energy is used to sustain Totems, and is also the basis of operating Sustain Tactics. I did not expect that Brother would have such an abundance of Silver Energy to be used for Tactics," Reylan shook her head. "According to our research, this type of Silver Energy is probably determined by the state of mind of the Luminarist. The better their state of mind, the higher their Silver Energy."

Garen nodded.

"My body has been healthy all along, and I’ve always been in a positive state of mind. We don’t have to worry about this aspect."

He picked the pen up again and began to write down a new set of data in his notebook.

"It’s been two days since we left that fortress nearby Ferrochrome Town. We should almost be reaching Aisley City by now, right?"

Reylan grabbed the glass of plain water on the table and gulped it down in one mouth, exhaled, and began putting on her coat.

"Since we sped up we should almost there," she moved to sit next to the window on the other side, and looked outside.

Cough cough…

The sound of Lala’s coughing echoed from the carriage in front again. She sounded as if she were about to cough out her internal organs.

"Stop the carriage! Stop the carriage!" A young man alighted from the front of the carriage. He was the totem user from the Hunting Group that had guarded Lala earlier. His had a grim expression on his face as he ran towards Garen’s carriage, waving his hands frantically.

The three carriages began to slow down to a stop.

Garen pulled the carriage door open and got off, before walking towards the man.

"What’s wrong? What happened?"

"Lala just coughed out blood! We need to think of a way to help her!" The man replied solemnly. "I can’t bear to look at this anymore. She’s just a regular person. She doesn’t deserve this kind of punishment."

"I’ll go and take a look," said Garen, furrowing his brows.

He followed the man into the first carriage, and suddenly noticed the shockingly large pool of fresh blood on the floor of the carriage.

Lala lay on her side on the carriage floor, her face as white as a blank sheet of paper.

Garen’s expression darkened, and his eyes glanced past the others. Angel shrugged her shoulders immediately, showing that she was powerless.

Vicky furrowed her eyebrows and said softly: "I’ve seen this type of illness in Sitcher County. It seems to be Miya tuberculosis, and may be contagious."

At once, a forced expression appeared on the faces of everyone in the carriage.

"I’ll do it," said Garen indifferently as he stepped forward and carried Lala in his arms. He turned around and walked towards the third carriage.

Lala’s weight had decreased severely. He estimated that she weighed less than eighty pounds, and was now skinnier than a person should be.

Garen took the opportunity to look at her face.

Both of her cheeks were sunken and her eyes were listless. All that was left of her were skin and bones.

"No medicine, no specialized doctors. I’m sorry, I caused all of this to happen to you," said Garen softly, as he placed her on the seats of the third carriage, against a barrel of beef jerky.

"This was my own decision," Lala’s voice was very weak now, and most people would have to place their ears right next to her before they were able to vaguely hear what she was saying. "I… wanted to follow you…"

Garen looked at the girl who had taken such good care of him all this while, and felt a sense of uncertainty inside his heart. Without a suitable treatment method, Lala would surely die. Garen himself had unconsciously neglected her during this period of time, which resulted in her deteriorating to this degree.

He reached his hand outwards and touched Lala’ wrist to feel her pulse, before realising that it was extremely weak, almost non existent by now.

"Right now, there’s a way to save you, but I can’t assure you that it will be successful, because everything depends on luck. It is only a possibility."

Lala’s eyes jolted open immediately. "I could still… live?"

"But you’ll have to give up your freedom in exchange," Garen nodded as he answered her question.

Frankly, both of them knew deep in their hearts that if it was really tuberculosis, it was only a matter of time before it became a death sentence.

There was not the slightest bit of hesitation in Lala’s eyes.

"Please, I’ll leave it up to you then. I’m just a regular person, and to be honest in a world and era like this, I don’t have much freedom to talk about." She was someone who was well-versed in the law, and could see everything clearly. She understood that Garen’s treatment of her could already be considered excellent. If she had any other master, she would have been dead a long time ago.

Garen was in awe of her rationality and intelligence. The ability to put everything into perspective, and the knowledge on whether to advance or to step back were Lala’s greatest virtues. As for her pretty face, it was only secondary to everything else. In this world, those who were beautiful but shallow could be found anywhere. However, girls as gorgeous and wise as herself were truly rare.

"You should get ready then," Garen turned to look at the Hunting Group members outside who were looking in their direction.

"All of you should wait outside first. I’m going to see if I can save Lala."

Angel rushed towards him and nodded, as a playful smile appeared on her face.

"Up to you, as long as your ‘cute’ little sister doesn’t get jealous."

Garen was too tired for her nonsense. He pulled the carriage door and shut it, before closing the curtains.

He looked at Lala in her white sleeping gown, and crouched down beside her.

"Just rest for awhile. When you wake up in a few moments, you’ll feel better."

Lala nodded slightly.

"I’m in your hands, Lord Garen."

"Yes." Garen’s hand shot out as quick as electricity, before quickly hitting the side of Lala’s neck.

Both of Lala’s eyes closed immediately, as she fell into a state of unconsciousness.

Garen spared no time in taking out the red crystal ball from his inner shirt pocket, before placing it on the side of Lala’s head gently.

The red crystal ball suddenly began to emit a soft light. A row of small words began to float upwards near the top.

‘A creature has been found nearby, would you like to empower the creature?’

"This is an experiment. If it succeeds, you live. But if it fails, you’ll die. We’ll see what your fate holds." Garen glanced at the words in the crystal ball, and stretched his hand out slowly, clicking on the part that said ‘yes’.

Abruptly, the crystal ball begin to emit a silver light, as the colour of its entire body began to turn from pink to silver. A ray of silver light shot out of its core and landed straight on the right side of Lala’s temple.

Shh…

Suddenly, white gas began to form near Lala’s head, appearing to be water vapour.

Garen looked at the crystal Derivator frantically. This experiment was the key to finding out whether he could successfully empower a human body. After Jessica was first empowered, she went missing without a trace, and there had been no news about her even until now. However, humans could definitely be empowered to a certain degree, because the option to choose humans existed. Deep inside he felt that this was not completely right, but it was worth trying.

This was its final quota, the tenth item that the Derivator would be able to control. Now it was time to see if it would succeed or not.

The silver ray shot out for a full ten minutes, before it faded slowly, and finally became dark.

Garen waited until the silver light had disappeared fully before he kept the crystal ball quickly, and then began to check on Lala’s condition.

Everything seemed normal. She looked the same as she did before the empowerment process, even her body looked as weak as it was before.

"Did it fail?" Garen glanced at the crystal ball, and noticed that it clearly stated on top that the empowerment had been a success.

He looked at the bottom part of his field of vision. If he had succeeded, there would surely be an totem icon here.

Sure enough, an unknown icon had appeared in the silver totem pane. The icon was a three-dimensional full-body image of Lala.

‘Lala Pearson: First form living totem, upgradable. Probability of successful evolution: 89% (The weaker its body, the higher the success rate). Potential point cost: 300%.

Abilities: Housework, studying.’

"She really became a totem." Garen was somewhat shocked. He peered at Lala who was still lying down. The girl was opening her eyes slowly now, and looking at him with a slightly confused expression.

Garen began to use his Will. "Lala, can you hear me?" He passed his message mentally without having to say a word.

Lala opened her mouth in shock, but understood immediately, as an alarmed expression appeared on her face.

"This…?!" She looked at Garen and felt as if his emotions could now decide whether she lived or died. However, the original feeling of weakness from the tuberculosis that was once entangled around her was completely gone.

She felt as if her heartbeats had gotten stronger.

"Don’t feel doubtful, I’m using my thoughts to communicate with you now. Currently, you’ve become my exclusive creature, in a certain sense. Your life and death is in my hands," Garen explained carefully. "Do you feel something different about yourself now?"

Lala nodded, but her response was somewhat delayed. She was also just expressing her thoughts internally.

"My illness seems to be cured…"

"That’s good," Garen nodded in satisfaction. "This experiment counts as a success, so you should try and get used to your body now. It should be much safer for you now than before."

The greatest benefit of becoming a totem was that it was less likely for them to succumb to harm that was not caused by their own species, such as illnesses, accidents, or disasters.

Garen pulled the door open and alighted the carriage, before looking at the grim face of Reylan who had been waiting outside. Her wizened, shrivelled face was lightly painted with an unwilling and jealous expression.

"Brother, it looks like you’ve decided not to listen to my warnings," she said in a very solemn voice. "Do you know what happens when you don’t listen to me?"

Garen could tell that she was masking a stern threat behind her words. He squinted his eyes.

"I don’t remember what you said to me?"

Reylan sneered. She said nothing as she turned away and returned to the carriage.

Garen watched the figure of her back, as he felt for the first time that it might be a wrong decision for him to let this person stay by his side, even though she had given him an abundance of other-worldly knowledge.

"Be careful, your sister looks slightly abnormal."

Angel walked beside Garen and said the words softly. Her voice was hardly audible, but the both of them noticed when Reylan, who was now in front and had walked quite a distance away, turned around suddenly. Her pupils glared directly at Angel.

Angel huffed coldly, and brought her people towards the first carriage.

Garen looked at Reylan, unsure of how to solve the problem for now. He waited awhile before getting on to the carriage, before noticing that Reylan had her back facing towards him now, and was currently asleep under her blanket.

This continued until lunchtime at noon, when Reylan woke up and ate quickly, before going back to sleep again.

Garen felt that something was strange, but decided to leave this thought at the back of his mind for the time being. Whenever he came across a problem, it was better for him to solve it on his own. With his basic knowledge, as long as he knew the foundation of the situation, he only needed to investigate it deeper, and this was not something that would be too difficult for him.

Up until night time, they managed to take care of a herd of more than ten white cats. These white cats were almost the size of horses, and had extremely sharp claws, but were not totems. One of the men in black in Angel’s group took care of them on his own, and left the meat to be made into jerky, while the fur would be used to make clothes.

After dinner, Garen continued to research biological engineering for awhile, before going to sleep as well.

Suddenly, he felt that something was off. While still in a daze, he began to feel an uncomfortable feeling.

Garen hazily opened his eyes with all his might. He saw Reylan standing at his side, and looking down at him. Her eyes were glowing red, and she was emitting light in the darkness.

"Reylan? What’s wrong?" Garen had yet to wake up, and was just looking at Reylan who was standing beside him.

Reylan did not say a word, but turned around and returned to her own area. She went back to sleep again, completely ignoring Garen’s question.

Garen rubbed his head and sat up straight, before noticing that something was not right with his cup.

He grabbed the cup on the table as a little black thing crawled out and attempted to fly out through the carriage window.

Pop!

Garen pinched the little black thing in one swift moment. When he opened his hands to look, he saw a little black cockroach-like insect, that was almost the size of his fingernail.

Chapter 332: Change 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

Suddenly, he heard the quiet creeping sound of insects crawling.

He lowered his head to look, and noticed that his entire bed was filled with a large number of these insects crawling everywhere. There were so many of them tightly packed together that it was impossible to count.

Some of the insects were climbing up his arms, some were crawling on his thighs, while others were attempting to crawl up his chest and head.

The large clusters of insects looked like a pool of black mucus that covered the entire bed. A rotting smell that compelled people to vomit also permeated in the air.

"Damn it!!" Garen’s totem light flashed across his whole body as all the insects were shaken off. He felt a tingling sensation on his scalp, and got up frantically.

Immediately, the insects on his seat slid downwards like flowing water, and scuttled into the bottom of the carriage, disappearing quickly.

Garen picked his cup up to drink some water, but suddenly remembered the little insect that had crawled out of there.

He looked inside the cup and saw a fat white maggot soaking inside the water. The maggot’s body was covered in layers of folds and was curled at the bottom of the cup. It was as thick as two fingers and was still turning around and wriggling.

Many white insect eggs were floating on the surface of the water as well.

Bang!

Garen threw the cup on the carriage floor. A wave of unprecedented anger burst out of him.

"Reylan!!!"

He pointed a finger angrily at Reylan who was still asleep.

What’s wrong, Brother?" Reylan turned over and looked at Garen calmly.

Both of them met each other’s eyes, but neither of them was willing to give in to the other.

Some time passed before Garen calmed his emotions.

"Are you using your methods to threaten me?" Garen felt that this was the first time he truly understood this girl from the Obscuro Society that he picked up.

"What methods? I don’t know what you’re talking about, Brother," said Reylan with a strange expression on her face.

Garen began to feel slightly suspicious that Lala’s illness may have been caused by Reylan. After witnessing the scene with these strange insects tonight, he had now started to suspect this possibility even more.

"What are you trying to do?!"

Reylan’s mouth stretched into an ugly smile.

"Brother, you like beautiful women, don’t you? Unfortunately, my face has disappointed you greatly. Isn’t that right?"

Her smile disappeared, and she seemed to be reminiscing something.

"Frankly… I knew earlier on that you weren’t my real brother."

Garen’s heart stopped for a moment and he paused his speech, as he waited for her next words.

"I just wanted to continue to bask in the feeling of being cared for by someone else, Brother," Reylan’s eyes grew wider, and her red eyes grew more bloodshot. "Of course, it would have been better if that little servant who was prettier than me actually died. That’s what I thought, so I decided to induce her slightly," she said. "You know as well, that some illnesses only require certain specialized environments, and that’s all that is needed to induce them."

"So it was you," Garen said calmly.

"Hehe…" Reylan laughed, and stood up suddenly. "Oh Brother looks like we have no choice but to be separated now. However, all this will only be temporary."

As she smiled, her face began to melt suddenly, as if it was a candle, and the wax-like liquid dripped downwards and turned into countless little black winged insects.

Immediately, Reylan’s entire body turned into a cluster of black winged insects that flew out of the carriage noisily, and buzzed towards the faraway sky.

The winged insects formed into a black human figure in the sky and waved at Garen from a distance.

A sullen expression appeared on Garen’s face as he watched Reylan leave instantly. He had no intention of making any moves right now, as both he and Reylan were individuals that the Obscuro Society wanted to get rid of, and there was no need for him to have any conflict with her now.

This incident with Lala had severed the mutual affection between them completely.

As for how Reylan felt, he had no idea about that, and did not plan on finding out.

"It’s good that she left," Garen huffed coldly as he scattered the Platinum Aura around his body everywhere, using it to check the condition of the three carriages. Once there were no more little insects, he returned it to himself slowly.

"Just like Jess. Nothing but another extreme madman."

There was not a sliver of regret in Garen’s heart.

Even though Reylan could have aided him greatly, a person like herself, who would hurt anyone by his side at any moment for the sake of lust, was definitely unstable. At a time like this where he was unable to grasp the situation, distancing himself was the best option.

"What happened?" Angel and the others got down from the carriage after they were woken up. They put on their coats as they stood beside the carriage window.

"Nothing. Reylan left. She fought with me," Garen forced a smile and said softly.

Angel’s expression had clearly relaxed as well.

"She left? I’ve always thought that there was something abnormal about your sister. It’s good that she left."

"You’re being honest for once," Garen smiled bitterly.

"We should be able to reach Aisley City by tomorrow. You should sleep early and get some rest. The Striped Crystal you’re looking for, and the other crystals, they have them all there," said Angel as she shook her head, and turned to leave the window.

Garen tried to detect his totem creatures.

The Dual Headed Salamander was sleeping in a hole that it had dug for itself at the back. The Resonance Hawk was on the left side within a seven hundred meter radius, hunting down an Aberration White Deer. The Petrifying White Dragon was in a different hole, cleaning the scales on its body.

The Deep Swamp Croc and the Beetles were scattered in different areas, and most of them were already asleep.

Angel, upon finding out that Reylan had left, did not seem shocked at all. She had noticed the complexities of Reylan from much earlier on.

Garen did not want to think about it any longer, and decided to lie down once again. But when he closed his eyes, he will still unable to fall asleep for some reason.

On the second day at noon, they reached the end of the plains in front, and a metal-grey colored hexagon-shaped city finally appeared in sight.

Aisley City looked like a hexagonal coin that had been embedded in the ground, it was abnormally neat. Each of its six sides had a watchtower built there.

Garen poked his head out of the window and looked at the city in front of him.

One of the watchtowers near the road had already collapsed. It looked like a broken pencil from the way that it had snapped in the middle. Half of it had fallen in the middle of the road, blocking the road that the carriage was using to pass through.

There were broken pieces of carriage tyres on the right side of the road, and some of the blood stains on the ground had begun to oxidize and turn black already. A few red-eyed rats were crawling around in the grass.

Once Garen’s carriage arrived, the little guys became frightened and ran away in all directions.

"Aisley City was an industrial city that was rich in mineral resources. It was also one of the two largest headquarters of the southern War Guild. Who knows if they are still any survivors from the guild?" Angel and Garen were sitting in the same carriage, as she chatted to him leisurely while sitting opposite him.

"Maybe there are or maybe there aren’t, but what does that have to do with us?" Garen joked. "In this kind of environment, other than our living essentials, everything else is unimportant."

"That’s also true," Angel smiled as well. "Get down first, the road in front is blocked."

She flung the door open and jumped off.

Garen followed closely behind.

Both of them walked towards the watchtower that was blocking the road in front.

Their surroundings were completely quiet, except for a few rats that crawled below the watchtower quickly, making soft noises as they went.

Weeds were growing on the surface of ashen roads, and dark green vines had begun creeping around the fallen watchtower. Bright daylight vaguely illuminated the interior of the watchtower.

The watchtower had a diameter of five to six meters, and had caused a blockade in front of all the carriages that attempted to move forward.

Garen walked to the side of the watchtower and looked in front, before realizing that the city gates was right there.

The city gates were opened, and there was a row of ruined little houses on the left, which appeared to be sites where merchant stalls once stood. The air was completely silent, and there was not a hint of rotten blood scent anywhere.

"So quiet…" Angel stood beside Garen and said softly as she furrowed her brows.

"It’s too quiet," Garen nodded. "To think that there wouldn’t even be one monster to be seen." Garen detected his Beetles and commanded them to look out, but they did not find even one monster. Everything felt strange.

"Let’s go. We’ll talk a look before we decide," Garen turned around and jumped over the watchtower, landing on the ground on the other side.

"If you’re looking for the Striped Crystal, I’d suggest that you go to the storehouse at the Governor's residence right away, because there should be more there," Angel said loudly.

"We don’t need to do that. The museum one of your members was talking about last time, we’ll go there instead," Garen turned his head upwards and looked at the Resonance Hawk that was circling over his head.

The large grey hawk was looking downwards at the entire city.

Garen drew a tactic gesture quickly. Suddenly his senses were dulled, before instantly becoming clear again.

He was now in the midst of the cold air, looking downwards at the entire Aisley City.

The interior of this hexagonal city was a mess of multicolored broken stones that had been muddled together. Most of the buildings had collapsed. Some areas were continuous sections of charred wreckage, making it obvious that a fire had occurred there. Other places were unharmed and still in perfect condition, as a protective barrier-like wall had been built around it. It was supported by heavy metal buckets, a sign that it was a man-made stronghold. However, there were still no movements there.

"What were the special features of the museum?" Garen asked directly.

"Eight pillars, all black, and a triangular fountain at the door. There were four brass statues in the surroundings, which were all statues of Fedilipa. The roof was rectangular and extremely long, resembling a street," explained Vicky with detailed descriptions, as she stood next to Angel.

"Very good," Garen locked down their destination quickly. "We’ll go there right away. We’ll enter through the city gates and passed through three straight streets, turn right, cross an arched bridge, turn left again and cross another two streets, before finally reaching the museum."

"It’s pretty far. All the streets in Aisley City are very long," Vicky said softly.

"Doesn’t matter. We’ll get our things, divide them amongst ourselves, and leave immediately. If you need anything, list them down and give the list to me," Garen said in a straightforward manner.

"The list was ready a long time ago. Here!" Vicky passed him a piece of white paper that was filled with materials and supplies.

Garen took it and glanced at it, before his brows began to furrow slightly.

"Some of these things are unnecessary, such as these historical books that can only be found on the other side of the city. Kardo fruit jam? This is not the time to be enjoying yourselves. And all these rare metals…"

"We should split up then. In this area, it seems that there aren’t that many monsters anymore," Angel shrugged. She passed him a black stick that was only the size of her palm. "This is a smoke signal used to alert others. If you’re facing trouble, just use this signal, and all of us will come over to assist you."

Garen took the smoke signal. "Do I need to light it up before using it?"

"Just rubbing it quickly against a rough surface will do."

"Alright. However, since there’s nothing wrong here, we should wait until we’re completely sure that there are no monsters before we split up and move."

Chapter 333: Secretive 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

White rays of sunlight fell inside the hexagonal city, and basked most of the wreckage in a layer of white.

Inside the empty city, on the abandoned streets, a blonde man dressed in a grey robe walked forward slowly. He surveyed his surroundings from left to right occasionally as his feet stepped over littered building debris and rubbish. There were also some mysterious deep pits on the ground that looked like white dots, and could be seen everywhere on the city streets.

Both sides of the street were filled with ashen shophouses and the occasional multi-levelled hotel building, and there were broken stone sculptures on the roofs of the buildings.

All of the doors and windows of the buildings were now empty black holes that allowed the cold wind to blow in endlessly.

The blonde man stepped on the ground with his leather shoes, crushing some of the broken stones and making crunching noises as he walked.

He walked on the streets alone while his eyes scanned the area from both ends quickly without giving his pupils enough time to focus.

After walking for a distance, the man passed through two neighbourhoods and walked unto an ashen stone arched bridge.

The right side of the bridge had been damaged by an unknown object and only left than half of it was left. Below it was a dried out river bed, where an abundance of fine green grass was growing in the black river bottom.

"To think that I wouldn’t be able to find a single survivor?" The man walked across the arched bridge slowly, as a doubtful expression appeared on his face.

After he had separated from the others, he decided to go to the museum alone to obtain the item that he was looking for-- the Striped Crystal. Initially, he thought that he would have encountered at least a few monsters, he certainly did not expect that he would not even see one.

"Garen! En… En… Oh…" Suddenly, the sound of Angel yelling and its echoes could be heard in the distance.

Garen looked towards his left near the further parts of the river, and saw Angel and Vicky walking further away in the direction of the river. Both of them were dressed in bright red leather armor, and resembled sharp, little red dots.

The yelling noises sounded throughout the empty city endlessly, and formed echoes.

"Did you find any… ni… ni… ni…?" Angel’s voice echoed from a distance.

Garen raised a hand and shook it from left to right, signalling that he did not.

Angel soon realised that her loud yells would easily attract monsters, so she shut her mouth and stopped shouting. Instead, she used her hand movements to point in the direction of the furthest part of the river to signal that she was walking over there.

Garen understood her actions and walked forward to point out his own direction as well.

Both of them waved at each other before they separated and continued walking forward.

After crossing the stone bridge, a street shaded by trees lay ahead, and when the cold wind blew, the fallen leaves on the ground would roll past and made soft noises as they brushed against the ground.

On the side of this street, a row of wilted buttonwood trees were planted there. There were almost no leaves on the trees, as most of them had become dried leaves that littered the ground.

Garen walked forward calmly at a seemingly slow pace, when in actual fact every step he took covered a great distance, and was actually an average person’s running speed.

He surveyed the environment of his surroundings and noticed that a majority of the shops on both sides of the street were clothing stores and accessory shops. There were shelves of women’s clothes and jewelry displayed inside, and some of the clothing racks had already collapsed while thick layers of dust had accumulated on top of the expensive fabric.

In the middle of the road in front, a brass statue was built there. It was a statue of a little boy in a urinating position which was connected to a round pool below. The pool had dried up completely and a pile of wilted buttonwood leaves had accumulated at the bottom of the dried out ashen coloured pool.

Garen walked to the side of the pool and stretched his hand out to pick up a buttonwood leaf. The wilted leaf resembled a yellow claw that had curled upwards at the edges.

He pinched it gently and the leaf instantly let out a crunchy noise, before it broke into many paper-like pieces.

Garen brought his hand up towards his nose and sniffed it, as a dry scent entered his nostrils immediately.

"What caused so many people in this city to leave this place? There isn’t a single trace of monsters. However, the fallen watchtower outside clearly shows that a war had broken out."

Still uncertain, he threw away the leaf pieces in his hands, and crossed over the decorative pool.

After crossing this neighbourhood, up ahead on the right side, a plaza that was filled with wilted leaves appeared before Garen.

The plaza was oval shaped with three different stone sculptures in the middle that depicted three different single-horned beasts that were posed in a neighing position with a single hoof raised. Their snow-white bodies had began to show thin crack lines.

On the sides of the plaza, long strips of flower beds had been erected to line the borders, but only black soil remained inside, as the colourful flowers had disappeared a long time ago.

Garen’s gaze scanned across the plaza before he looked in front and noticed a foggy rectangular building there.

It looked like a simple white rectangular box. The perimeter of this building was propped up by black stone pillars that were spread out at equal distances from each other, with unknown patterns engraved at the top.

Garen quickened his footsteps and walked towards this building.

Once he had reached the front of the building, he saw a triangular fountain at the main door that had dried up a long time ago. The road leading inside had been split in the middle with one end leading towards the right and the other to the left, forming the shape of an eye. On the outer area of the road stood two bronze statues of people. They were both identical statues of a young man raising a book in one hand. Garen felt as if he was leading something along with him, so he turned his head and looked behind as he walked forward and took long strides.

Garen came from the left side and walked around the fountain before standing in front of the sculpture and stroking the human sculpture gently.

The temperature was extremely low and the air was as cold as ice. The texture of the ground was also rough, and very hard.

He looked down at his fingers and noticed that a thin layer of black dust had appeared there.

He arched his head upwards and looked at the sunlight. Garen suddenly noticed that the sky had started to turn dark. The rays that had warmed his body earlier had now disappeared. Instead, it was substituted by a cold breeze.

Garen furrowed his brows and took his pocket watch out of his pocket. Inside the brass watch face, the hour hand stood straight at the ‘1’ position.

"One-twenty in the afternoon, who would have thought that it would be cold at this hour?" He kept his pocket watch carefully and wrapped his grey robe tighter around his body. He took long strides and walked towards the main door of the museum.

There was a large metal-framed wooden door outside the museum. The large door was as tall as two people, and the golden keyhole in the middle seemed to be of an expensive grade. Two silver chains hung outside the main door, and were probably used to tie it up.

Garen lifted the chain and twisted it lightly with his fingers.

Clang!

A crisp noise sounded before the chain broke into two.

Once the chain had been opened, Garen pressed his palm lightly against the keyhole. There was no sound, so he pushed again lightly.

The entire keyhole was pushed inwards and fell on the ground with a ‘clang’.

The main door was pushed open slowly and the doors faced the outside areas in both directions.

The interior was completely empty and the floor was filled with black dust. The walls were also stained with traces of smoke and most areas had been burnt and melted by fire, causing some of the metal cupboards and burnt coal to stick together, blackened to the point where they were indistinguishable.

"This is going to be troublesome…" Garen knitted his eyebrows together closely.

He walked forward and looked straight ahead.

The whole museum could be seen straight ahead. Up in front, the middle section was completely burnt black, and the only undamaged exhibition counters were situated in the back. All of these counters were shaped like spheres, and were protected by a piece of transparent crystal glass. The surrounding floors were covered with scattered pieces of broken glass, causing the place to be in a state of disorder.

Garen crossed the charred section hurriedly and walked towards the last exhibition counter.

The sound of his own footsteps could be heard continuously throughout the empty museum, and as the noise echoed throughout the emptiness, it seemed as if another person was following Garen from behind.

He narrowed his eyes when he suddenly thought of the issue with Reylan last night, and his emotions turned gloomy all of a sudden. The echoes made it seem like there were more footsteps in the distance that were softer than his own, stalking him from behind. They seemed nearby, following him closely from behind.

Garen turned around suddenly and stopped in his tracks.

There was nothing behind him, and the sound of the footsteps stopped immediately as well.

"Was it an illusion?" He tried to silence his footsteps, not allowing himself to make any noise.

Suddenly, the hair-raising sensation from before finally ceased.

When he reached the front of the counter, Garen began to examine the exhibits inside one by one.

Extravagantly priced jewels, some exquisite copperware, ancient metal boxes, and the latest silver pocket watch. All kinds of mysterious exhibits were displayed inside the counters.

Garen walked passed the expensive but unimportant items right away, as his gaze scanned across the room, before finally noticing that there were lists of the exhibits placed on the wall a fixed distance from each other.

The lists contained clearly-written records of various treasures and the numbers of the counters where they were kept.

Garen’s eyes scanned across the lists before finally finding the counter where the Prime Crown was kept: Number 28.

He walked in front of the undamaged counters and looked at the numbers on top, noticing that were between numbers 270 to 350.

"28…"

Garen followed the direction of the counters and walked forward towards them.

He quickly found counter 28 where most parts of it had already melted.

The crystal glass had been stained black by the smoke. He placed five fingers on the surface of the counter and pushed it lightly, before his fingernail suddenly penetrated it deeply.

A cracking noise could be heard as a large lump of coal and something else was instantly dug out by Garen.

The inside of it was empty, and seemed like it had not been burnt completely.

Garen reached inside and felt around, before grabbing a crown-like object, and pulling it out immediately.

A pure silver crown was now in his hands. The crown was completely spotless, a pure silver colour, except for the red diamond-shaped crystal embedded in the middle. The crown was simple, but also delicate and neat.

The jewel was the size of a fingernail, crystal clear, and pure beyond comparison. There was not a single defect or impurity to be seen.

Garen picked up the crown and examined the red crystal in the middle carefully.

"The Striped Crystal. It’s main characteristic is that when it faces external oppression, thin stripes will naturally appear inside it."

Garen’s finger pressed against the red crystal gently.

Suddenly, thin web-like lines floated upwards like countless stripes, and could be seen clearly.

"This is it."

He kept the crown in his clothes pocket immediately.

After that, he began to refer to the list again, before searching the other counters for the exhibits he might require.

In many of the burnt counters, the majority of the exhibits inside were unburnt, but the exterior of the counters had melted because of the fire, which made removing them more troublesome. The ones that had truly been burnt to a crisp, were but a few.

To prevent the exhibits inside from being damaged, Garen’s every move was executed extremely carefully, which proved to be unnecessarily tiring.

Seconds and minutes ticked away. The sky outside began to darken.

Garen reached his hand inside one of the burnt counters.

Bang! Bang!

Suddenly a loud noise echoed from the outside and the ground began to shake violently. It sounded like the footsteps of a large creature.

"What was that?"

Garen kept his hands to himself and placed the black crystal inside his pocket.

Bang bang! Bang bang bang!!

The footsteps echoed once again and the ground quaked violently as large amounts of dust began to fall down from the ceiling of the museum.

Chapter 334: Secretive 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

Garen’s expression had changed slightly. In the blink of an eye, he felt twenty of his Parasitic Beetles disappear.

Suddenly, a whine sounded in his Will, and his connection from the Resonance Hawk was cut off instantly.

"Fuck! I knew there would be a problem!!" Panic rose in Garen’s heart, as he grabbed his pockets and ran out of the doorway of the museum quickly, exiting the main door. Suddenly, he was frozen in shock in his position.

In the city on the left side of the museum, an incomparably large fatso carried an unbelievably huge mace as he walked through the interior of the city one step at a time.

This monster’s body was covered from head to toe in dark green, and it had rough skin that resembled the bark of an old tree. He also had a large protruding belly. His height was apparently much taller than most of the buildings in the surroundings. The mace on his shoulder was completely black, and its size was beyond comparison.

He strolled through the city one step at a time, as if he was patrolling his own territory.

Garen swallowed his saliva.

This monster’s height was already almost fifty meters high! As he walked through the city, the houses and buildings on both sides seemed like his wooden block playthings that would be destroyed easily with one gentle push.

Around his neck hung a round tooth chain, and two large horns grew out of each of his shoulders, as black as cow’s horns.

Garen had seen large monster totems, but had never seen a monster this big.

The Petrifying White Dragon and Dual Headed Salamander were large enough, but compared to the giant monster in front of his eyes, their size difference was equivalent to the difference between an adult and a baby. Without even trying, Garen already knew that he would not be able to defeat him.

For a troll that was over fifty meters tall, every time his feet stomped against the ground, a five or six meter deep imprint would be left behind.

Garen executed his commands hurriedly through his Will, and allowed all of his silver totems to escape the place quickly.

The troll seemed as if it had discovered Garen his presence. His dark green head bent down slightly as it looked over at Garen curiously.

Suddenly, he raised the mace above his shoulder.

"Uh… No way…"

Garen began to feel uneasy. He picked up this things as his feet stomped on the ground violently. A few strides later, he had already dashed more than ten meters away.

Boom!!!

An ear piercing roar echoed behind him.

He turned around to look, and saw that the museum had been fully destroyed. A large mace lay on top of the collapsed wreckage, and just like a smashed paper box, it had was no obstruction to the weapon.

"Woah woah woah!!!" yelled the fatso as he raised his mace and made loud incomprehensible noises. It was unknown if he was laughing or just roaring.

The noise sounded like thunder, and the quakes that it caused made Garen’s whole body numb.

He noticed that even the little stones on the ground in front were beginning to jump from the quakes.

Suddenly, another black shadow covered him.

Without enough time to think, Garen used all the strength in his body, as he stomped the ground with his feet powerfully.

Boom!!!

A large amount of gravel crashed against his body violently, and the impact caused a burning pain throughout his entire body.

His Totem Light had apparently broken in the blink of an eye!! Right now, he could not even feel a sliver of its existence!

"Which fucking form of a monster are you?!" Garen could not help himself from cursing. He turned around began to shamefully run away.

The fatso began to roar loudly again. He held the mace in both of his hands.

Boom boom boom boom!!!

He began to swing it around violently. He moved his big feet and chased Garen from behind quickly, with unusually fast speed. One step was enough for him to move thirty to forty meters forward.

Countless buildings were smashed until dust filled the air, and as they collapsed, bits of stone would fly everywhere, and some of the larger rocks even destroyed a few houses.

The black mace moved constantly in a quick flurry, and within a few hits, all of the buildings surrounding the fatso were smashed to debris.

Garen ran away frantically. He was too afraid to turn back as the fatso was incredibly fast, and could reach the distance he hastily ran with just one step. If the fatso was a totem user, he would have easily smashed Garen with one step. His speed-based secret technique was truly frightening.

He was too afraid to call upon the totems in his hands for assistance because when the monstrous fatso had attempted to hit him earlier, the gravel had broken through the totem light on his body. It was important to note that the totem light of a totem user was much stronger than the totem itself.

In that moment earlier, if a totem itself had been hit, there was a chance that it would have been destroyed instantly.

He had painstakingly nurtured and evolved a Form Three silver totem, and if it was destroyed here for nothing, he would not know what to do but cry.

The fatso chased after Garen quickly, looking as if he was extremely happy.

"Woah woah woah…!! Ansai! Lucan… Mokeya…!!" he roared loudly once again.

Garen ran frantically and suddenly felt his whole body shiver.

Suddenly, he leapt towards the left, breaking proper posture, as he used all of his strength to evade the mace that came smashing down behind him.

Bang!!

A white mansion that once stood upright was instantly smashed to bits. In the garden, a large tree broke off at the middle, and let out a crisp whooshing noise as it fell.

"Endor language!! Apparently it’s the Endor language!" A layer of haziness began to form in Garen’s mind. Initially, he assumed that he had seen almost everything clearly, but now he had apparently discovered new mysteries and strange things.

"Nusija! Anboer! Kasiduor!!" Suddenly, he turned around and used his secret technique to gather his voice in one place, before directing it towards the troll’s ear.

He was also using the Endor language!

Suddenly, the fatso stopped in his tracks. He lifted the mace back towards his shoulder while his face became expressionless.

"Ansai… Lucan… Mokeya… (Flesh and blood… Fresh… Want to eat…)"

Garen simultaneously translated all the other sounds into meanings he could understand. He was not extremely fluent in the Endor language, as he had not used it enough.

Standing in the middle of the street, he arched his head upwards and looked at the troll, afraid that he would suddenly become mad again, which would cause his mace to come crashing down once more. Once his strength took a hit, it mattered not whether he was a totem user or a secret technique possessor, he would get smashed flat all the same.

This tall building-sized monster had a body that was large enough to cast a huge black shadow that enveloped Garen completely.

A man and a monster, one large and one small , stood facing each other unnaturally, as if they were engaging in a conversation.

"Ansai… Lucan… Mokeya…!! (Flesh and blood… Fresh… Want to eat!!)" repeated the troll again. It seemed like he was unable to say anything else, except for this one sentence.

"Ruo… Xifeidela? (You… what type of meat do you want?)" Garen attempted to form a chain of Endor words to ask the troll a question.

"Ansai… Lucan… Mokeya…" The troll continued to say the same sentence, repeating it over and over again. Sticky saliva began to drip from the two fangs at the corner of its mouth, before falling unto the debris below, and drenching a huge area instantly.

Garen tried other questions but the troll did not respond in the slightest. It seemed to only know this particular sentence and repeated it continuously. Fortunately, it was no longer attacking Garen.

Garen tried again, but did not get the desired effect. Finally, he gave up on his plan to communicate with the troll. He thought for a moment. Before ordering his next command with his Will.

Instantly, a swarm of black Parasitic Beetles crawl in from outside the city, looking like a colony of black ants as they moved in the direction of the troll.

The troll did not move away, but reached downwards with its large hands and grabbed a huge handful of black insects before shoving them into its mouth. It began to chew them loudly. A large amount of sticky white liquid began to drip out of the corner’s of its mouth.

It ate two handfuls consecutively while Garen’s face remained expressionless, as he watched the troll quietly. All of his Beetles were here, and out of the two hundred of them, the troll had already eaten over thirty in just two handfuls.

Seconds and minutes ticked by as the troll continued to grab handfuls of beetles before chewing them thoroughly.

Soon, the last beetle was finally devoured by it.

"Woah woah woah…!!!" The troll patted his protruding tummy as he roared loudly once again. It sounded as loud as lightning, and was much louder than before.

Garen felt a slight aching sensation in his heart as his whole body became numb, and his blood began to pump furiously. His field of vision became blurry, and soon he was unable to see anything.

He wanted to release his aura, but was currently being suppressed by a large pressure, and was unable to release it.

His field of vision became a blurry mess. Suddenly, Garen felt his surroundings light up.

All noise disappeared instantly.

He opened his eyes frantically. He was standing in the middle of the street while sunlight outside was shining on the ground, leaving no trace of darkness.

"Troll? What happened to that troll fatso?" Garen turned his head upwards and scanned his eyes around his surroundings, but was unable to find any trace of the troll.

He turned towards the road he came from, and saw that the museum had already become a pile of wreckage.

Traces left behind by the troll were still here, but the fifty over meter in height, almost seventeen storey tall troll itself, had now disappeared completely.

His surroundings were completely quiet, as if nothing had happened.

Still in a state of disbelief, Garen jumped on top of a building and surveyed his surroundings. The entire city was pin-drop silent, and there was not a single trace of the troll.

"Endor again…." he said before sighing in relief.

Looking at himself closely, he could see physical proof that his grey robe had been torn full of holes. His arms, abdomen, and thighs, all of them were full of dark red bruises, all of which were caused by the gravel hitting him.

Suddenly, his expression was tinged with a sliver of shock.

On his own right hand, he was unsure when exactly it happened, but a new dark green ring had appeared on his ring finger.

Garen tried to remove the ring gently, but this little thing seemed as if it was growing from his finger, and was completely impossible to remove.

The entire ring was smooth and glossy, and had the colour of a dark green jade. The surface of the ring was engraved with a thin line of words in a square.

Garen tried to recognize the words carefully and soon realised that it was obvious, that those words were written in the Endor language as well.

"The city troll will only accept the first life that gives it a gift…"

Garen looked upwards. A confused expression flashed in his eyes.

"City troll? Is it referring to the monster from earlier?"

He suddenly thought of the recorded legends and myths that he had seen in the previous world. His expression became serious all of a sudden.

"If it really was the city troll… Then this ring…"

He quickly looked at the attribution pane at the bottom of his field of vision.

In the bottom of the attribution pane, a little dark green glyph had appeared. This was the first time Garen’s ability had displayed a color other than red.

The meaning of the glyph was: Troll Grip. (In the ruined city, if one successfully encounters the nomadic city troll without dying, but manages to communicate with it instead, once it is satisfied with the first gift it receives, it will then repay you with another present. According to the myth, the city troll’s gift will increase one’s strength to a great degree.)

"An increase in strength!" Garen’s eyes lit up when he noticed that there was a huge change in his strength attributes.

His initial strength was at 2.66, but had now unconsciously increased to 6.66, which meant that it had increased by another 4 whole points!!

Chapter 335: Strength 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

He held his palm gently. Garen used his enhanced physical control to detect changes, but did not feel as if his strength had increased.

Garen looked at his attribution pane again doubtfully, and sure enough, his strength had already reached the 6.66 mark. There were no further changes to the number, and it remained firmly at that point.

He reached his arm outwards and leaned against a long ashen coloured bench on the roadside, grasping it tightly.

Suddenly, he felt a hot sensation travelling quickly throughout his right arm from ring finger. His entire right arm began to warm up, as if he was soaking himself in a hot spring.

Crunch!

A cracking noise sounded in the air even though he did not lean heavily on the bench, as the wood broke and turned into dust in a blink of an eye, and dispersed in the wind.

Garen narrowed his eyes in disbelief, as he truly was not using a great amount of strength, He merely pressed the bench innocently for a moment. It felt as if the sturdy wood was completely non existent when he touched it.

"What great strength!" Slight fear trembled in his heart.

After hesitating for a moment, he lifted his right arm, straightened it into an offensive position, and swung it forward suddenly.

Tch!

A shapeless air fluctuation flew out immediately.

Crash!

A bronze statue far away was cut into two halves instantly. The top half of the human statue slid down slowly, and was abnormally smooth.

After that, a loud crashing noise could be heard.

No one knew how many things and walls these air fluctuations had passed through to cause such fine layer of white dust to form in the distance. It happened so fast that the number of things it passed through was unknown.

"Tch tch…" Garen himself was feeling an uncontrollable sense of shock.

He suddenly thought of the troll’s mace, and realised that both of these things possessed almost the same degree of monstrous strength.

"Such powerful strength, who knows what the effect will be if it’s used against totem light." Remembering the troll’s strength, Garen began to feel slightly hesitant.

The troll did not consume all of his totem light. Its attacks also brought its own type of unique strength, and was not held off completely by the totem light. In other words, it was a type of power that possessed a similar nature to the totem light.

He really wanted to call the Deep Swamp Croc over to test out the new strength he had on hand, but before that, a series of footsteps began echoing from the far end of the messy, damaged streets. Leila, the man in the red hat from the Hunting Group ran towards him and arrived here quicky.

Behind him was Angel, who was holding a girl and lagging behind slightly.

The three of them were looking towards here from far away, with panicked and alarme expressions clearly displayed on their faces.

Garen hesitated for a moment and relaxed his right arm downwards temporarily, afraid of the slightest movement. This arm was weird because it could release an unbelievable amount of strength without its reactionary force springing back. The slightest accident could cause him to injure others. He was not ready to use his right hand for the moment.

He dashed towards the direction of the three other people quickly.

"What’s the matter?" he asked softly as he looked at the girl Angel carried, who was actually Vicky who was now unconscious. "What happened?"

Angel furrowed her eyebrows and scanned the surrounding area.

"I feel like something isn’t right with this city. Earlier, some of the houses in the area collapsed without reason, not to mention that I think I heard a giant monster’s footsteps, and I’m not sure if it’s an illusion or not. Before I knew it, I heard Vicky collapse and faint. She seemed like she was hit by something, as her totem light was penetrated suddenly, and her core totem was heavily damaged!"

Hearing her say this made Garen suddenly think of his own core totem, the Black Striped White Tiger, and how it was almost wrecked as well. Once the totem light was completely broken, the core totem would also suffer similar damage.

He could not help but glance at Vicky. This girl was also a form two totem user, but her complexion was completely pale, an obvious sign that she was gravely injured.

"Has it been five full years already?" he asked.

"It’s already the sixth year," Angel replied quickly.

Garen nodded his head.

"That’s fine. Get this girl a new core totem immediately. If a totem user is protected by their totem light for too long, their immunity becomes extremely weak, and when they’re exposed to air and other external substances for extended periods, I’m afraid she may face more problems later on. I assume she has more than one totem, right?"

Seeing Angel nod her head made Garen relax.

"We should leave this place. I don’t think it’s safe here anymore." Garen examined all of the streets around him.

All the streets were filled with smash marks left by a heavy object, showing that the traces left by the city troll still remained.

"But we haven’t finished collecting our things? Are we really just going to leave like this?" Leila wavered.

"Are you things more important than our safety?" Angel glared at him.

"Uhh… Both are important…" Leila shook his head warily.

"Move!" Angel kicked his buttocks.

"My limited edition ‘43 out of print fashion!!" Leila wailed, but was pulled away on his ear by Angel nonetheless, as she dragged him away immediately.

Garen took the items he had collected and returned to the carriage on the city outskirts with Angel’s trio. Ansa, the black clothed man in the Hunting Group that had stayed back to keep watch, was now crouching beside the carriage, and checking some of the dead rat corpses. He noticed that everyone had returned, and were carrying large and small bags of items. He stood up hurriedly and came forward to help carry some of the stuff.

Lala, who was inside the carriage earlier, also got down to help arrange the various goods.

Basic cooking essentials, flour, tissue, a change of clothes, new cups, and cutlery. There were also some tools that Luminarists used for conducting experiments.

Everything was immediately moved into the third carriage.

Leila, the bastard had the audacity to command his Black Beetles to drag a brand new, gorgeous, large silver carriage outside.

"Using form one totem insects to pull a carriage. Haha. Only a brilliant totem user like myself would have the right to enjoy special privileges like this."

Garen did not say anything. Four members of the Hunting Group in one tiny carriage was truly a tight squeeze. Meanwhile, this large carriage had six wheels and was over six meters long and four meters wide. It was almost the size of a small house. Four of them inside this carriage would definitely be more spacious for them.

The black clothed man Ansa was very attentive. He found various spare parts for the carriage, and also a lot of nails and a hammer that could be used for repair work.

Both Angel and Vicky found a myriad of tools used by Luminarists and Forgers, such as an incubator, petri dish, thermometer, conical flask, and a centrifuge, among others.

"It’s a shame we couldn’t find a unit factory, but the things that we did manage to find aren’t too bad. Unit factories were involved in the deep secrets of the Forgers and Luminarists, hence, even if we didn’t take them with us, they would still be destroyed in the end. It’s very likely that others would be able to uncover the techniques of creature units from there."

"These are already pretty good," Garen nodded in satisfaction. "With these tools, I can conduct new and deeper research. Thank you very much."

Angel’s mouth twitched.

"We don’t need meaningless rewards or gratitude. Some for you, some for Ansa. Ansa’s equipment is specially used for totem repairs. Melting machine, repair instruments and separators, and the precision instruments are all specialized. Meanwhile, yours is mainly used for creature research, so both of you can exchange equipment if needed."

"I know," smiled Garen. Although Leila had left, the basic equipment that he left behind was sufficient. With these tools, Garen could start from the most basic experiments and quickly progress towards his plans.

Once everyone had retrieved their own items, it was nearly evening, and the sky had began to darken slightly.

Everyone returned to their own carriages, and by evening, Aisley City began to look even more gloomy. There was not a shadow of a person to be seen and barely any light. Every inch of the city was dark and empty.

Standing outside the city, one could definitely feel the endless cold and chills coming from inside.

Garen reversed the order of the carriages. His own carriage was the first in front, while Lala’s goods carriage was in the middle, and the Hunting Group’s two carriages were the last ones at the end.

He clapped his hands and lined the four carriages in a row, before they left Aisley City slowly.

Sitting next to the carriage window, Garen took the map out and began looking at the road carefully.

The yellowish map depicted a little red dot, and beside the dot a line of words read: Lush Forest district, Vanderman mansion.

Garen stretched his index finger outwards and placed it on top of the red dot on the map lightly. They would pass through a large forest, a river, and a stretch of mountains. Finally, the would stop at the position on the map with the city symbol.

"Aisley City is here, so we still need to pass over a stretch of mountains, cross the Naserweiya river, pass through the Red Rat forest, before we can finally enter the Lush Forest district. I’m just unsure about what this place looks like now."

When he thought of the abnormally huge city troll, an uneasy feeling bubbled up inside him. It felt as if everything had deviated from its initial course. The experimental aberrations and various germs and viruses released by the Obscuro Society had caused various unfathomable changes.

It seemed like the world had become more mysterious day by day.

Tch…

His index finger had accidentally torn through the map. The map fell on the table, and Garen unknowingly pierced a hole through the table as well.

Garen immediately realised what had happened and retracted his right index finger frantically, as a panicked expression appeared on his face.

He looked at the Troll Grip he wore on his finger, the insignificant dark green ring that was tightly wrapped around his ring finger.

"Was this also the Obscuro Society’s intended change?" he pondered quietly.

He turned around and took a leather suitcase from below his seat and opened it to rummage the clean clothes inside, before finally taking out a black leather glove, and wearing it on his right hand.

After moving his palm and feeling that nothing was amiss, then only did Garen stuff the box back into its place below his seat.

Right now, he was unable to estimate the true strength of his right arm. He only knew that it felt extremely powerful, because at 2.6 it was already at the pinnacle of human strength, and with just one hand, he was already as powerful as a Deep Swamp Croc. This was something that Garen had tested out once before with his own eyes.

But now it had increased to 6.66 at one time, and this number meant more than just two or three times of his initial strength. The higher the numbers, the effect of the strength generated would also become more obvious.

He had investigated and found out that the enhanced strength from the Troll Grip did not mean that he had exceeded the limit of his attributes. Instead, it meant that his other attributes would not be able to increase in the future after some time.

Daa…

The sound of the carriage wheels could be heard softly, as the carriages began to move slowly.

The grassy hills outside the window looked as if they were moving backwards slowly. The carriage shook slightly when it rolled over some gravel. Next, the carriage turned in a semi circle motion before speeding up gradually.

Garen sat up straight and held the Resonance Stone in his left hand again, as he began to feel the frequency carefully again.

His brain possessed calculation and analytical skills that were far superior to an average person. It was the effect of intelligence levels that had reached 2.5, which also caused him to have an increase in physique-based secret techniques. The progress in which he grasped frequencies wildly exceeded Reylan’s expectations.

From his initial stage of weakness and inability to sense them, to his current stage of improved clarity, it now felt as if he was holding a beating heart in his hand. Before this, he had wasted a duration of a few days.

Holding the Resonance Stone gently, Garen continued to bury his head in the process of researching frequencies.

As long as he could synchronize his own frequency and reach the Resonance Stone’s level, he would be able to restore the Crystal Derivator to its initial stage at the right degree.

Regardless of the Troll Grip or the nest revenue brought on by the Resonance Stone, the thing that he truly wanted was neither of them. Instead, his goal was to fully grasp the Crystal Derivator.

To him, the Crystal Derivator, regardless of its current strength or his future plans, still possessed utmost importance for him. He could not lose it!

Chapter 336: Strength 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

Two days later…

Sunlight was shining brightly, and the air was warm, as everything was basked in a layer of golden light.

The rapidly gushing river looked like a glittering golden river. Beside the river, a few Deep Swamp Crocs had bitten a large black water anaconda and had dragged it up the river bed, and were now tearing it to pieces and eating it.

Garen sat inside the carriage and nodded his head in satisfaction, as the carriage passed the shallow water bed slowly, and travelled forward in the direction of the railway bridge. In front, a thick and densely-packed forest could be seen.

******

One day later

Under the light drizzle, the entire forest was covered in a layer of rainy mist.

An elegant, snow white coloured large flying dragon flapped its large wings gently and dived downwards.

Whoosh!

A large gust of ashen air landed directly on the backs of two large black bears. There were lots of blue-coloured bone shards growing out of the black bear’s back, and when it crawled on the ground it looked like a stegosaurus.

When it felt the ashen breath blowing against its back, the Thorny Back Black Bear let out a roar and all of the spikes on its back sprung forward. At once, they petrified themselves into two stone statues.

As the thorns rained down, a few white imprints soon appeared on the White Dragon’s hard scales.

The White Dragon dived downwards again, and grabbed both of the Thorny Black Black Bear statues with its claws, with one in each claw, and immediately flew towards the faraway sky.

An hour later, a troop of carriages passed by the area slowly, and travelled across the road in the forest that headed towards the Kovitan Empire. Three of the carriages were black, while the last one was silver. In the first carriage, the windows and curtains had been opened. Garen looked at the White Dragon flying in the distance with a blank expression on his face, and pulled the curtains closed again.

*****************

Kovitan Lush Forest district

Vanderman mansion

Vanderman sat on the sofa in the hall on the first floor and chewed on a black pipe that had run out of cut tobacco a long time ago. His eyes were glued to a piece of paper in his hand.

Opposite him sat his two loyal subordinates, Edney and Maxilan. Both of them were clad in strange black-purple armors that looked sturdy and majestic, except for the dark red crystal lines that were embedded on top. The lines looked like blood vessels and contained red liquid that flowed through it endlessly, which also caused bubbles to float around in the liquid occasionally.

"What is Aquarius planning to do now? Seems like I forgot to beat her up properly the last time. Lost two form two totem users but still unrepentant…" Vanderman’s expression darkened as he tore the piece of white paper up slowly. "Right now, Her Highness the Twelfth Princess is planning to arrive in person immediately, and no matter how much she struggles she won’t be able to pull anymore tricks out of her sleeve anymore. Except…"

"Except what, my Lord?" Edney stroked the small knife in her hand gently. "You just need to wait for Her Highness the Twelfth Princess to arrive, before you ask Master Masuya to lend you his strength, and then you’ll definitely be able to get rid of that disgusting, ugly woman. If two form three totem users go up against her, she can struggle with all her might, but that will still be useless."

Vanderman lay face up on the sofa.

"It’s just that this letter arrived in such a timely manner, a sign that Aquarius’ side is well-informed…" he said as his face began to contort.

"That’s true, her messengers are too well-informed," Maxilan nodded as a slightly disturbed expression appeared on his face. "We too only received the news this afternoon."

"Why should we trouble ourselves with all this? As long as our power is strong enough, we can just get rid of any situations we face immediately!" said Edney, unfazed.

Vanderman nodded, his complexion had improved slightly.

"Right now the main war is there, and I’ve heard that they’ve started using Spiritualized totem users. Once this kind of war weapons that can greatly influence the outcome of battle have been released, it clearly shows that it has come to the White Heat degree already. We’re still alright here, so I’d assume that the main force has been sent to other places already."

"I’m worried that the Obscuro Society has deployed a Spiritualization totem user to Aquarius, which would be troublesome for us. Aquarius can single-handedly control one form three and five form twos. Meanwhile, these Spiritualized totem users are all war weapons, and the pressure they exert upon their enemies through their Spiritualization is too strong, and will also be too strong for us to handle as well!" said Maxilan as he furrowed his brows. He had followed Vanderman for so many years, but this was the first time he had encountered such a difficult situation.

"What’s done is done, it won’t make any difference even if we spend more time thinking about it," Vanderman waved his hand. "You should go and rest first. My old friend is looking after the mansion, so there won’t be any problems there."

"Yes, sir."

Both of them stood up to open the door and leave, while the maid closed the door carefully and left the hall herself, to avoid disturbing Vanderman.

Vanderman stood up and only then did he notice that his pipe was already out of tobacco, and the fire had extinguished long ago. He mashed his lips together to get the pipe. He walked towards the front of the fireplace unconsciously and looked at the dazzling fire, before noticing the black and white photo that was hanging above the fireplace.

A sea of green grass, himself sitting on a chair, Acacia standing behind him with a small smile on his face and a joyful expression.

He looked at the photograph quietly for a good while, before exhaling a deep breath, and reaching his arm outwards to take the box of tobacco under the photo frame.

******************

Lush Forest district

Inside the secret underground room in the Aquarius mansion

"Right now most places have been cut from all contact for a long time already, and we won’t be able to support everyone on our own for much longer. We need to make up our minds soon," Aquarius furrowed her brows as she looked at the crystal ball in front of her. The white crystal ball began to give off a dim red light from the inside. It caused the entire secret underground glow to light up dimly.

"You need to stabilize that area first, this division here is also facing difficulties. The interior of the main section defected a few of its members, and the frontlines of the war have barely made any progress either. Daniela is facing rebounds, but those were the messages from a few months back, we don’t know what the current situation is like over there. The areas here where I require support troops are far too many," said an old man’s voice as it sounded through the crystal ball.

"I don’t care. Anyway, you still need to make the necessary arrangements here for me quickly, because I cannot bear to stay here any longer!" Aquarius said furiously. "This goddamn, disgusting, rotten to the point where he should be used to feed the dogs Vanderman has nurtured a final form, and last time it almost broke my left arm off! Out of the eighteen other mountainous spots, you could send me to any one of them and I’d be fine with that!"

"Don’t be anxious, I’m merely a Brigadier General, I don’t know anything about the arrangements made by the higher ups. The Kovitan higher command center is located in the Kovitan capital and Iron Tank City. They’re too lazy to even care about our message reports," said the old voice impatiently.

"Anyway, just do as you see fit. I’ve already given Vanderman the letter already." Aquarius turned the crystal ball off angrily at once. Regarding these new toys, she had yet to understand them fully yet, but that did not hinder her from using it to increase her power.

The crystal ball was kept properly, and she walked towards the right side of the secret room, pulled out a secret drawer, and took out a black envelope.

Aquarius then tore open the envelope , took the letter out, before she began to carefully translate the words one by one using the secret language.

As the translated contents increased, the expression on her face improved as well.

"This thing is still happening?" Finally, when she put the letter down, her facial expression had become much better by then. The corners of her mouth were also curling up into a strange smile.

**************

"Ooh… Erm… Oh…!!!!" Leila pulled Garen’s arm with all his might and used his entire body weight, causing his face to turn red.

"Could you not let out these constipated noises?" Angel stood at the side with her hand on her forehead. "If you want to test your arm strength just do that, you don’t have to make these disgusting noises as well…"

"Can you feel the blood flowing through my veins? That’s true strength! Oh oh oh~~~ My strength is burning!!" Leila roared as he furiously push Garen’s arm downwards again.

Garen looked at the other man wordlessly and used his left arm to arm wrestle with Leila. Due to Vicky’s broken totem light, because she was exposed to air, she now had a fever, an obvious sign that her physique was lacking. As they got bored during the journey, everyone decided to squeeze into the biggest carriage to engage in some entertainment for training purposes.

The current event was arm wrestling, and the unfortunate part was that Garen was single-handedly beating everyone without any competition.

After Garen had defeated the three women and Ansa, his thin body suddenly gained the interest of Leila. This bastard assumed that this was a good opportunity for himself, so he stepped forward as the last person who would conclude the legend of Garen’s undefeatable account.

Leila used of his might, and now a leopard’s paw was hidden behind his left shoulder. The paw belonged his totem beast, and suddenly a surge of powerful strength rushed forward.

"Haha, bet you didn’t expect that I’d still have this final skill!" He was giddily happy, as his leopard totem possessed exceptional concealment, especially his secondary totem the Shadow Leopard, and currently no one had realised that he was cheating.

Suddenly, he noticed that Garen had been distracted by something that Big Sis was saying.

"And now!"

The man and the leopard attacked, and he pushed its paw downwards and pressed hard.

"Ah!! Your legend!! Will be ended by me!!" "Roar!"

Bang!!

The hand and the paw smashed downwards violently, and pressed against Garen’s left hand.

After that…

There was nothing after that.

"What did you say just now?" Garen turned around ignorantly and looked at Leila. "I think I heard you saying something about my legend?"

Leila stared at Garen’s unmoved arm blankly, before turning his head upwards, and looking at his opponent.

"Nothing… I didn’t say anything…"

"Oh…" Garen turned away and continued the discussion on the previous topic with Angel.

Lala and Vicky who were standing on the sidelines both covered their mouths and laughed secretly. Ansa stood on another side and checked the slots in the carriage, and shook his head wordlessly.

Frankly, everyone had known about Leila’s cheating, and recognized his signal, but this guy was still the clown of the group, and no one had seen through him yet.

The carriage travelled forward slowly at a fixed pace. After a fixed interval, everyone would take turns releasing their totems outside to monitor the situation, but there were still no form two monsters to be seen. Everyone felt that this was extremely strange.

"It’s unbelievably calm," Angel shrugged, and looked at Garen. "Do you have some sort of good method to avoid them?"

"That’s a secret," smiled Garen mysteriously. "If I tell you it won’t be worth any money anymore. I’m still planning to use this to get something good from the Kovitan capital, you know."

"Always hiding something. But recently, why have you been wearing a glove on your right hand?"

Angel looked at the black leather glove on Garen’s right hand. This guy had one ungloved hand, while the other hand was gloved, hmm… It as unsaid that he ended up looking really cool. At a glance, he looked like powerful boxing champion.

As a totem user, she had always been in awe of physically fit professionals.

"This is because my right hand got injured, and I didn’t want you guys to see it, so I decided to hide it under a glove," Garen explained calmly. He was looking for an opportunity to test out the true strength of his right hand.

He placed his Black Striped White Tiger core totem with Ansa, to allow the other man to help him repair it. In Aisley City, due to the totem light on his body breaking completely, his totems either suffered light or serious injuries. The core totem suffered the most, and had almost half of its body destroyed. This made Garen, who had painstakingly searched for the Striped Crystal, extremely furious. He faced a lot of difficulties evolving it, and never expected to encounter this problem as well.

The difficulty in fixing the core totem, as well as the difficulty in evolving it, drew Garen in the direction of creature totems. According to his plan, these creature totems were the only ones that could help him reach his goal.

After chatting to the others in the carriage for a while, he got off soon after that.

At night, it was completely quiet, except for a mooing noise that could vaguely be heard from the distance, that came from an unknown monster.

On the top of the largest silver carriage stood a silver owl that had a pair of light yellow eyes that were giving off a soft blue light in the darkness. They were like two large light bulbs.

The owl stood on the roof of the carriage but did not move, as if it was just a sculpture.

Garen glanced at it before turning around and walking towards the back of the carriage troop, disappearing into the darkness quickly.

He stretched his right hand gently. This time, he wanted to test out his arm strength with the strongest Dual Headed Salamander, and see the true strength and upgrades that the Troll Grip had given him.

Chapter 337: The Return 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

After travelling with the convoy for a few minutes, Garen found a silent, pitch-black forest.

Standing in the middle of the woodlands, he waited silently for a moment.

Very quickly, from deep within the forest as black as ink, came the sound of heavy footsteps. The sound came in bursts, carrying a rhythm.

A giant creature, almost eight meters in height spanning no shorter than ten meters, was squeezing between the trees as it headed here. It was a dual headed salamander. It raised its two heads in mid-air, and continuously protruded its black tongue.

The dual headed salamander stopped in front of Garen, with a distance of less than 10 meters between them.

"Let’s begin." Garen signaled his intention.

The pitch black dual headed salamander let out a soft growl, then suddenly thrusted its head fiercely at Garen.

Garen took off his gloves, slowly extended his left palm, then placed it on the salamander’s forehead.

Bang!!

As his palm met its forehead, a circle of air shock waves blasted out suddenly from the impact.

Both the man and the salamander were blown several meters back abruptly. Their bodies were left with numerous scratches from severe friction.

Garen widened his eyes. He had a sense of irresistible delight.

"Sure enough...Sure enough… hehehe.." He could not help but let out a faint laugh. In the midst of the dark forest, his eyes seemed unprecedentedly bright.

"That’s right, looking at the time, this is about it. I even came back a little earlier." He looked at the dual-headed salamander who was quickly digging a hole to leave. Its body disappeared in the distance, becoming a blur, as it headed towards the horse carriage.

　　********************

Hwaaa...

Waves of sounds could be heard in the broad, dark green forest. Leaves formed layers of waves as they were blown in the strong wind. From time to time, there were some dark green creatures flying out from the forest, while occasionally, a few strange birds came down from the sky to perch in the trees.

The midday sun was covered by grey clouds, only revealing a circle of golden light near the edges.

In the distant sky, three giant grey hawks were flapping their wings as they headed towards the depths of the vast forest.

Each grey hawk had a six to seven meters wingspan. On their backs, sat two men and a woman in grey robes.

Among the two men, one of them had a strong body. Beneath his grey robe was shimmering silver armor, while at the waist was a heavy broadsword. His most prominent attribute was the black beard on his chin.

The other man had a pale complexion, and seemingly lacked training. He had a pair of calm eyes, while beneath his grey robe was a tight black gown. The most eye-catching attribute was his pair of eyes, which had exceedingly rare silver-black pupils. His white retina with silver pupils left a cold, strange impression on others.

The only girl had flaming red leather armor beneath her grey robe, clearly revealing her slender waist. She had a beautiful face with a youthful aura. Her bust was abundant, but not excessive, and her legs were long and slender. It was evident she was showing off her proud assets. At one glance, she was not more than eighteen years of age. The wind ruffled her short, flaming red hair, revealing a dark-gold earing on her right ear.

"Darian! How long more until we arrive at Lush Forest District?" The girl yelled. She rode her grey hawk parallel to the strong man, and turned to look at both men.

"I don’t know. I only went there for a vacation many years ago. I know nothing other than that." The strong bearded man stroked his chin. "Ask Beckstone about these, he definitely knows."

The girl silently gazed at the man on a greyhawk in front of her. The pale-faced man in grey robes bowed his head, as he seemed to be focused on some calculations. Uncertain, silver flames continuously erupted from his fingertips.

"We still need half a day’s time to reach Trejon’s Territory. Viscount Vanderman hates people breaking his laws. At this time, his territory should have been armed with various air defense mechanisms. As courtesy, we have to land one kilometer away and journey by foot." The black-gowned man seemingly heard the girl’s question and answered without turning his head.

"Hopefully we can gather sufficient information this time. So happen Barr and Baphje, the two professors from the Royal Alliance will be there. I’ve read their thesis on Silver Glitter, and it was enlightening for the cultivation of Nias’ second evolution. This time we can meet them in person." The black-gowned man said, seemingly speaking to himself.

"Our trail previously ended at Vanderman’s Manor. Maybe Leanna came to Trejon’s Territory before. As we need Vanderman’s help to search, do not be rude Darian, to avoid leaving a bad impression. It would be troublesome if they refused to help." The red-armored girl reminded in advance.

"Yes yes…" The bearded man lifelessly leaned on the back of his giant hawk. "It’s so boring. Adiss, you no longer chat with me after your Spiritualization. I wonder why…" He murmured as he helplessly tugged at the hawk’s feathers.

"A male riding on another male, what do you want me to say to you?" The hawk looked stupefied.

"I have goosebumps at the thought of a male riding on me. You better not have wishful thinking, otherwise, there are many things I will do. Of course, if you are Berlina, I would be glad to discuss reproduction with you."

"Why would you think this way?" The bearded-man loudly refuted, "Am I like that?"

"Very alike."

"Okay then.."

Berlina, who was beside them, instantly let out a shy laugh.

"Being looked down upon by his own core totem, Darian you can be considered the first in history."

"If i knew it earlier, I wouldn’t have Spiritualized him.." Garen uttered in dissatisfaction.

"Look out, there’s a creature in front." The black-gowned man closed his eyes, accurately reporting the numbers. "A second form acid bird and three first form black-billed geese entering attack range in one minute."

"Let me do it this time!" The red-armored woman was excited. "My flame sparks is the best for group combat."

　　*******************

In the distant jungle, a thick, brown, giant tree lifted its branches to the sky. Its diameter was tens of meters long, sustaining a huge shade of a few kilometers.

The lush leaves were like a blue blanket, growing furrily on the top of the tree. As the sunlight directly shot through the shade, only a glimmer of the golden rays remained.

At the bottom of the trunk, in the gaps of the roots, was a tree hole. The tree hole was about the height of three men, its width the length of two.

Inside the tree hole, there was a spacious brown wooden hall.

On both sides of the hall were three flower pots, with two flower pots directly above.

Hizzzz!

After a light sound, there was activity in six out of the eight pots. In the basin-sized circle, there was a green seed quickly emerging from the soil. After sprouting and emerging, small black flowers blossomed. Black fruits soon formed and dropped into the pot. The fruit then decayed and, once again, became growing and sprouting seeds..

Within 10 seconds, the pot was saturated with dense, green vines. The vines intertwined and grew upwards, forming a dark-green pillar of plants of about a man’s height.

There was a total of six flower pots forming six dark green pillars of plant material.

The vines constantly twisted and entangled.

On the top of pillar on the utmost left, a wrinkled old face was coming to sight. The face was actually formed by a dense combination of leaves and twigs; it had a nose, eyes and complete facial features.

"Two have yet to arrive?" The old face spoke with a dry, hoarse voice.

Different leafy faces emerged on the remaining five pillars.

"Davis, you are always the first." The second face from the right whispered.

"You are not too bad yourself, Leena." Davis didn’t utter much.

The other faces did not say a word but fixated their gaze on the two pots on the top.

Soon, a red seed emerged from the pot on the left, quickly growing into a red plant pillar.

A bearded, old face then appeared from the pillar.

"My apologies for the wait." The bearded man coughed twice. "I’ve already sent Beckstone off. According to the information he obtained and his current position, he should be quickly reaching Kovitan’s Lush forest District.

"Royal Luminarist Zikhar’s territory? One of my sons has a good relationship with him. Do you need a referral?" One of the elders asked.

"There is no need." Davis, the one who spoke first, muttered. "Let it be a test for Beckstone. If he can successfully activate his innate talent, we can find out the extent of his talent."

"This is just the first beginning… Vanderman’s ultimate totem - Green Vine Sphere, is the first key to perfecting Beckstone’s talent. Has the second been selected?" Leena asked.

"Count Eiskan of Bernarius. I will make the arrangements. His valor will be in display as Beckstone arrives." Davis answered.

"We have to grasp the opportunity. As Hellgate will be awakening soon, we do not have much time left." Leena nodded

"Beckstone will become the most perfect, strongest Luminarist in history. There will be no exception!" The bearded old man spoke in a low voice. "Currently he has already entered Spiritualization, but the Obscuro Society has also started making moves."

He swept his gaze across the hall.

"Friendship, family, love, despair, anger, sacrifice, glory...once Beckstone understands everything, his talent would develop thoroughly. When that day arrives, it would be the time to face the Obscuro Society head-on.

　　********************

Garen quietly focused on the vase of fresh flowers before him.

Red and white little flowers fully covered the branches of a rust-colored tree.

The white and red flower petals brought a sense of freshness towards the carriage. There was also a faint fragrance from the flowers in the air.

Piak!

Garen naturally plucked a pink flower and placed on the side of his plate.

He was using his right hand.

Piak!

It was another flower.

Lala who was sitting across him twitched her eyes, revealing a trace of frustration in her expression.

"The bonzai that I chose and pruned with much effort, can’t you let them be for a while more?" She said lightly.

After recovering from her illness, she wore a dark purple, one-piece short skirt, with a thick black belt at her waist. She wore pitch-black stockings, putting her slender legs on exhibit. She tied her blonde hair to her left side, allowing it to drape over.

After being empowered, she seemed to have healed completely. Her lips appeared to have a touch of pink, while her skin turned soft and fair, slightly glowing with pink.

Garen plucked another flower and raised his head to look at her. "Your dress is beautiful." He let out a satisfying smile.

Lala blushed at his smile.

"Leila got the clothes for me.." She whispered. "This, or even those that are more, and also many…"

Chapter 338: The Return 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

"I wonder why that fellow wanted to take so many things so adamantly." Garen lost his cool.

"How do you feel after being empowered?"

"It feels great," Lala answered after some thought. "I feel more healthy and energetic. Plus the sickness I’ve had since young has disappeared. I only need six hours of sleep a day to fully recover. It’s as if my body is in its best condition."

Garen nodded.

"I will take this incident as a lesson for myself. You should stay by my side in the future."

"Okay!" Lala relaxed. She had been relying on Garen no matter what, as she didn’t feel at home when she was with anybody else.

Her parents died when she was young. Her aunt, her only relative she had, died during the battle. Hence, the only person she could only rely on now was Garen. Recently, she was sent to take care of Reylan, but had fallen seriously ill afterwards. This thrust her into a serious existential crisis, she wasn’t a totem user and therefore couldn’t control totems at the front lines during the war. As a commoner, she had to make herself useful for the team, or risk feeling useless and unwanted after a period of time.

Lala’s biggest wish was to return to Garen’s side, and take care of his livelihood, just as she had always done.

"Alright, you can leave now," Garen said calmly, as he placed the flower pot on the table.

"Sir Garen, regarding your personal news, I had not said a single word to Lady Reylan or Angel and the team from the Hunting Group"

She turned around and left the carriage after finishing her sentence. Garen was both surprised and satisfied.

The group of carriages stopped as they were having a barbeque just outside. With a small harp in her hands, Ansa played and sang to the music. The tunes and hymns slowly traveled into the carriages.

Garen listened to the music and he had a strange feeling written all over his face.

"This music… sounds rather similar to the Green Grass by The River." Garen recalled the drama series that he had watched on Earth. It was as if his memory had traveled through the space time continuum and went back to the drama series where he used to watch with his mother.

"How nostalgic…"

He closed his eyes and had left all of his thoughts behind opened his eyes.

He slightly moved his right hand to stand up and walked to one corner of the carriage where all the experimental instruments were placed. The experiment conducted yesterday had yet to be concluded.

It was shameful behavior for him, who possessed special abilities, to casually waste his time during this period of war.

It only required one to two days for him to get back to the Trejons’ territory.

**********

Vanderman sat quietly and reviewed the three youngsters sitting in front of him.

The leader was obviously the one in the black robes. He didn’t look very well and was rarely exposed to the sun. His eyes were silver which gave off an emotionless vibe. He seemed to be in his twenties.

He claimed to be Beckstone, a traveler from a far away place. Due to the sudden events, he had been traveling all over the place to investigate the root cause. Although this reason was rather orthodox, ten out of five totem users would have the same reason. It was a reason that could be used in all situations.

Another person was a girl in red armor. She was about eighteen or nineteen years old and sat closely to Beckstone. She would occasionally stare at the person beside her; it was obvious that she fancied him to some extent. She looked very beautiful, and one could immediately tell that she was naive, with a mind devoid of schemes and plots.

The last person was muscular and seemed very interested in Maxilan’s Creature Armor, as he kept closing the distance between him and Maxilan. This youngster obviously was the type who couldn’t cover up his emotions.

Vanderman maintained a courteous smile the entire time.

"As a member of the Royal Alliance of Luminarists, I feel a deep regret for the current chaos. However, please forgive my investigation into your every move; we have a powerful enemy lurking in the dark."

"Viscount’s actions makes absolute sense. I feel very grateful that you have allowed us to rest temporarily during the chaos. Please do not hesitate if you require my assistance." Beckstone, too, maintained a courteous smile. Naturally, he wouldn’t reveal to anyone that he was currently investigating the disappearance of Leanna. It wouldn’t be too late for him to request for assistance after probing for information during his investigation. This was especially true, when the leader of this territory was under suspicion as well.

"For you to lend us a helping hand, I thank you for your generous support, on behalf of the citizens’ within the Trejons’ territory." Vanderman thanked the trio with the highest regard.

"You’re welcome." The three of them immediately replied.

"This is what we do."

"Then, I shall take my leave as I still have matters to attend to. The servants are available, shall you have any needs." Vanderman stood up. "Also, my territory is currently in the front line of attacks, and I have essentially taken care of all the creatures that would appear from behind. You will arrive at the human defense area if you walk from here, and if you wish to leave during this period, I will send someone to escort you to the other cities."

"Thank you, Sir Viscount." Beckstone stood up and bowed at him.

"No problem. Take a good rest. Someone will escort you to your rooms." Vanderman nodded and walked out of the living hall.

Beckstone looked at Viscount and Maxilan, who followed behind, leaving the living hall. He sat back down as could no longer hear their footsteps.

"What’s wrong? What’s on your mind?" Berlina came closer from the back and asked gently. Her body fragrance found its way into Beckstone’s nose.

He frowned.

"It’s nothing."

He took out a small delicate box and gently rubbed at the texture of the box.

"The clue points towards Trejons and stops here. We better investigate this manor thoroughly and we may find something."

"Leader, I sense something is off," Darian whispered.

"What’s wrong?"

"Viscount Vanderman," Darian answered in all seriousness. "I smell something bad from his body."

"A bad odor?" Beckstone frowned. "Is he a Phantom Light?"

Darian nodded slightly.

"There are disagreements within the Royal Alliance of Luminarists so this is to be expected. Perhaps Viscount Vanderman comes from a rather extreme faction." Beckstone thought for a while before he answered.

"In any case, I have a bad feeling about this." Darian shook his head as he said.

**********

Aquarius’s manor.

"Hehe… two Spiritualised Totem Users? Where do these two powerful characters come from?" Aquarius, who was in a beautiful red dress was holding the report given by her subordinate. She was stunned as she looked at the report regarding the totem users.

The girl in green looked serious from the start till the end.

"According to the intel, they’re currently tracking the whereabout of a girl named Leanna. This girl seemed to be rather important to the leader, Beckstone."

"Leanna…" Aquarius’s face was filled with joy. "Luck is truly on my side. Vanderman… Leanna… Leanna? What a joke. What are the current losses of the Green Shade?"

"It’s still alright and we have confidence in our disguise so there shouldn’t be any problem in investigating more. It feels weird that there are a lot of creatures appearing that didn’t appear onto the intel’s report." The girl in green skirt said.

"It’s fine. I believe it’s just a mutation from the bacteria and it’s not up to us to meddle in this situation to begin with. When will the elites that we hired from the superior arrive? Vanderman does possess something valuable after all." Aquarius asked.

"The fastest duration is about two days." The girl in green skirt answered softly.

"Let’s find a good time to tell the youngster the truth…"

************

Beckstone gently took out the message at the black pigeon’s leg and placed a tiny black stick on its leg. He then jerked his hand and released it.

The pigeon flew out of the window and with a sudden acceleration in speed, the pigeon left a trail of black feathers and disappeared.

Beckstone squinted his eyes.

This pigeon arrived in a strange manner and suddenly appeared outside of his bedroom’s window.

He tucked his head out of the window to look around and did not discover any suspicious trace.

After closing the window, he opened the message and scanned the words written on it slowly.

His pupil shrunk as he read the letters and as he finished reading everything, he gently crumbled the message into a pile of white dust with his right hand.

He stood by the window and was lost in thought for quite some time.

"Whether if it’s real or not, I will investigate this matter myself…" His eyes were filled with resolve.

***************

With a complicated look on Garen’s face, he was looking at the sea of trees in front of him. It had been a long time since he returned.

He was in the driver’s seat in the carriage with a notebook that he always carried along in his hand. Suddenly, he gently closed the notebook and jumped off the carriage as he frowned.

The whole carriage team was gradually put to a stop.

Garen took a few steps forward as four Deep Swarm Crocs went forward slowly in all directions. These ambush type predators were able to leap in a tenth of a second and wouldn’t let go of their prey once they had bitten them. With the combination of their incredible strength and huge bite, they could tear their prey into pieces within a very short time.

These four Deep Swarm Crocs were the strength that he revealed to the public. He had his remaining strength hidden as the Crystal Derivator’s strength was not meant to be showed off to the public.

"What’s wrong?" Angel came from behind and asked.

Garen raised his hand, telling her that there’s nothing to panic about.

He walked towards a big tree and touched its root. There were droplets of black liquid on it and seemed to be corroding the root as white smokes were coming out from it.

Garen’s face changed as he had seen this special liquid in the creature’s information from the Obscuro Society. It was a secretion from a creature that was used to mark their territory.

He squinted his eyes as he stood still on the ground.

"If it’s that creature, perhaps…"

As he recovered from his thought, he turned around and walked towards the carriages.

Angel and the others had come down from the carriage for some time. Everyone was looking at him in confusion as all of them had released their totem, preparing for war.

"What exactly is going on?" Angela asked as she frowned.

"A ridiculously strong creature had just passed by. We’re lucky we didn’t encounter it as we’re passing through its territory." Garen smiled.

"It definitely sounds strong if you even considered it to be so… It’s best not to fight it." Angel nodded her head. "How much longer before we arrive your manor?"

"If we’re quick, we will reach there by tonight," Garen answered with confidence.

Chapter 339: Suspicion 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

The carriages headed towards the manor at the top of the mountain, traveling along the Black Swan Lake.

The sky was slightly cloudy and gloomy during the afternoon and it seemed like it was going to rain soon.

Garen placed his left hand by the window and stared out at the familiar white manor in silence. He could see the faint white buildings around the manor.

A transparent force field which resembled an egg shell covered the whole manor. The security seemed to be very strict as groups of soldiers could be seen patrolling at all times.

"This is my home…" Garen muttered. This world’s home, he said inside his heart.

"It’s a beautiful place." Angel, who was sitting opposite of him, complimented, as Lala poured her a cup of coffee. "Are we going to stay here from now on?"

"There’s no rush for that. I’m afraid other problems have arisen. We should take extreme precaution, as we are currently in the chaotic era. I will enter first to confirm my identity, before bringing you guys in to prevent them from separating us, since our group is quite large."

Garen started frowning as he thought of something.

"What’s there to worry about?" Angel casually whistled. "Everyone would welcome us because of our strength, right?"

Garen shook his head.

"I’ll go and make the arrangement."

"Whatever floats your boat. Just send the signal if anything happens." Angel nodded.

Garen finished his cup of coffee in an instant.

"Then, I shall take my leave."

"I’ll wait for your good news."

Garen got down from the carriage, tidied up his grey robe and looked at the manor.

"It’s… been awhile since I’ve seen this manor…" He sighed softly as he walked towards the manor through the lake.

As he walked across the wooden bridge of the Black Swan Lake that was strangely devoid of Black Swans. What was left behind were a few mere black feathers, by the pond. Weeds were everywhere, and the water was murky.

It looked so different, compared to the clear and beautiful Black Swan Lake from his memories.

Garen shook his head and tightened his black robe.

Splash!

A big silver fish jumped out of the water and attacked Garen, who was on the wooden bridge.

Without even looking at it, Garen flicked his finger at it.

Bam!

The big fish was sent back into the water. Traces of blood floated onto the surface.

Garen increased his pace, and crossed the wooden bridge, and as he walked along the small route between the forest by the hill, he realized that the fence on both sides were ragged. Grey tombs were strewn across his left, all of them looked very recent.

As he finished glancing at it, he continued moving forward with a pair of red eyes filled with resolve.

As he arrived the entrance of the manor, he could see a woman in red armor having a conversation with the guards from afar.

As the opponent had yet to notice his presence, he jumped to the side and hid behind a big tree.

Soon, people started to gather by the manor as if a team was about to depart.

"Quick! Where’s Charles? Did he slack off again? It's supposed to be his shift! Call him out this instance!"

Loud voices could be heard from outside.

A faint voice could be heard from afar as well.

"...Confirm the identity of those people by the lake… They better…" "Garlock! Where’s Sir Maxilan? Is there any new command?"

Looks like they had discovered the location of the carriage team.

Garen was relieved that the people from the manor were preparing to confirm the identity of the carriage once they noticed their presence. In this kind of situation, they need to confirm whether they were friendly or hostile since they were in such close proximity.

After some thought, Garen turned into a grey figure as he rushed out.

While he was on his way back to the carriage team, he knew that Beckstone and the team had most likely arrived at the manor, as he saw the girl in red armor. There was a beautiful girl in red armor among them, from his memory.

Since they have arrived earlier than they were supposed to, the best route to enter the manor was to enter together with the team.

Garen understood very well that Beckstone was the future star of the Terraflor Society, who aimed to be as strong as the Hellgate to fight against the Obscuro Society. Unfortunately, they had underestimated the Hellgate and overestimated Beckstone. They thought that they could reach the pinnacle this world in terms of strength, but they didn’t know that there were always stronger opponents, out in this vast world.

Beckstone couldn’t possibly face every powerful character that appeared during the Chaotic Era.

The three heroes had the support of two Overlords and three Emperors, which was the reason why they could even last for so long. The ambitions, the resolve to change and the crazy ideals towards the Obscuro Society of the emperors were pushing the future towards an unknown direction.

"Good timing. I would like to witness the potential of the future pillars of the Terraflor Society." Garen smirked as he sped up.

**************

Half an hour later…

Angel led the carriages into the manor slowly.

All the carriage curtains were wound up, and everyone was relieved, yet tired, as they arrived at a place among human beings. They no longer needed to worry about a sudden ambush from an unknown creature, which brought everyone mental reprieve.

When Vanderman found out that his son had returned safely, he rushed out of his experiment room as fast as he could and welcomed the carriages personally. Maxilan and Edney were guarding him tightly by his side.

Although his expression didn’t change at all as he looked at the silver carriages approaching, his shivering lips exposed his uneasy emotion. He held his hands tightly as his nails sunk into his palms. No matter how hard he tried to control himself, anxiousness and fear lingered in his brown eyes.

Vanderman lost his cool, as he saw his son, Acacia sitting beside the woman leading the carriages.

He took a few steps forward.

"Cia." He tried his best to prevent his voice from shivering.

Garen got down of the carriages and looked at his old man who was resisting himself with a complicated emotion. He felt distant and unease as he looked at his emotional expression.

"Father… I have returned…" He said softly.

He was then gently hugged by the Viscount.

"As long as you’re safe." Viscount whispered. He immediately let go of him after a gently hug and examined his son to see if he was hurt or healthy.

Edney followed up and said happily: " Cia, Viscount hasn’t been sleeping well since your disappearance. We have spent a lot of manpower to track you down and lost a lot of them since the chaos. But these things aren’t important anymore...you have returned! The most important thing is that you’ve returned safely."

"The most important thing is that you’re safe." Maxilan nodded from one side. He was looking at Acacia in front of him, who turned from an immature youngster into a mature adult, with a golden beard under his chin.

Garen gave Maxilan and Edney each a hug. These people would stand by his side and support him no matter what happened. Garen couldn’t help himself but to feel safe around them.

"This is Angel. Her team, the Hunting Group, saved me when I was in the Iron Tank City. I hired them to send me back here." Garen introduced.

He then introduced the remaining Hunting Group members to Viscount and Maxilan.

Beckstone’s team, and two of the totem users, Barr and Baphje, who were guarding the manor came out to see the commotion. Both parties were happy for the Viscount. Whether they liked it or not, the return of a family member would always be a happy scenario.

Beckstone recalled his farewell with his teacher when he left his village.

Barr and Baphje, too, recalled the days they left their hometown. They had been friends with Vanderman for a long time, and were invited here to protect the manor.

After the greetings, Garen was surprised that Angel was behaving properly, and every action was well mannered.

This good-looking girl in red shirt conversed with Vanderman with respect, and explained the fake story, which Garen had discussed with her beforehand, to Vanderman.

As Garen was looking at the people in the area, he could immediately recognize Backstone. This guy’s characteristics were obvious; he always put on an emotionless expression on his face, and had a unique silver colored pupils.

There were a lot of unfamiliar faces in the manor, they seemed to be Vanderman’s underlings. There were less familiar faces too, such as the housekeeper Duqian.

He had a better understanding of the situation in manor after enquiring of Maxilan.

The Vanderman Manor was currently safe, as it was being protected by two major powerhouses. One of them were Vanderman’s two trusty subordinates, along with at least ten form two totem users, supported by the Royal Alliance due to the relationship between them and Vanderman. The other powerhouse were the Royal Luminarists, Barr and Baphje. The both of them not only had strong knowledge in battles and tactics, they were also very knowledgeable in servicing, maintaining and executing Tactical Formations. Both of them had a few students who followed them everywhere, and were either form one totem users or form two totem users.

Although Maxilan didn’t reveal which form of totem user Vanderman was, Garen know that his father Vanderman had an ultimate weapon. On the surface, he was just a mere form one totem user, but he definitely had a strength that could possibly match a form three totem user. He was currently the strongest man in the manor.

Soon, he placed all of his attention on Beckstone and his team.

This young man in the black robe always had a smile on his face, but it gave off a sense of coldness. It’s as if he looked down on everyone from a pedestal.

He did have the power to feel arrogant. He was very talented, had an ancient inheritance, a mysterious teacher and the strength of a form three spiritualizations. These were the foundations of his arrogant behaviour.

As he noticed Garen’s gaze, he smiled at him politely and showed no interest in interacting with hi. He gave off a cold and distant vibe.

Perhaps, deep down, a form one totem user wasn’t worth his attention, as he was just small fry.

"They’re the Beckstone team, and they arrived here two days ago. I heard that they came from very far away, and were trying to find a place to stay where there would be people around so they could avoid the creatures." Maxilan stood beside Garen as he explained.

They walked towards the main building, where a faint fragrance of meat came out from the main hall as two servants opened the door to welcome everyone.

"Beckstone? He looks very strong." Garen nodded his head.

Chapter 340: Suspicion 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

"They’re very strong. According to Master Barr, there are at least two among them who are stronger than him!" Maxilan said emotionally. "To have such a powerful strength at such a young age. I wonder what kind of teacher is able to nurture such a talented man." He looked at Garen as he thought. "You must have suffered outside, right? I guess you can take that as training. Looks like you have become a totem user as well, right?"

Garen nodded.

"My totem is still under repair as it was broken by the creatures a few days ago. I didn’t expect you to notice it, since my totem light has weakened drastically."

"It’s a good thing, since you can share some load of your father’s load." Maxilan patted on Garen’s shoulder.

"Yeah." Garen nodded his head as he looked at Beckstone once again.

After a festive dinner, Viscount gifted Angel and her team a myriad of gifts, even the resources that they needed were provided to them. He had even written them a letter of recommendation to allow them to enrol in the Kovitan’s Royal Totem Academy. It was the most technologically advanced academy in the East Continent.

Future development would be endless if they could learn under some powerful Luminarist, and this made Angel and her team ecstatic. However, they immediately felt a twinge of guilt for Garen, as they teamed up to trick Vanderman after all. In addition, to be called Garen’s savior? It should be the other way round.

Garen didn’t mind it in the very least. He didn’t give much thought about how Angel and her team felt towards this situation, thought what he cared about were two main things. The first one was whether Beckstone had found out the truth, and the second was whether the incredibly strong creature outside would come in this direction.

Both of which could bring problems, no matter what.

In the two days that they stayed in the manor, Garen could feel that Beckstone and his team were investigating in the shadows, and this made him very cautious.

The Deep Swarm Croc totem that he had left outside of the manor was starting to feel more and more threatened, as the giant creature crept closer and closer.

***************

Inside the guest building.

Garen tucked his legs in as he sat on the red wooden chair, smiling at Angel who was sitting opposite of him.

In these two days, Angel had been well fed, even obtained a few good items from Viscount Vanderman. She suddenly felt ashamed, and shied away from Garen’s gaze whenever she noticed Garen’s attention.

"Why are you looking at me?! If you have something to say then spit it out!" She couldn’t resist anymore, and started shouting.

The morning sunlight came in through the window and landed on the floor between the duo, and a faint red light bounced around the room. Dust would occasionally float into the pillar of light, which resembled little worms dancing within.

Garen placed his hands together and said. "Have you been living well for these past two days?"

"I get to eat, drink and obtain free things! I would be lying if I said I’m not living well!" Angel started to show her true nature. "Do you want the things I have taken? Impossible! I don’t have any money, and the only thing I can compensate you with is my body!" She opened her hands wide and closed her eyes. "Whether you want it or not, I’m right here!"

"Alright, stop joking around." Garen shook his head and put his serious face on. "I wanted to talk to you about something serious.

Angel stopped joking around. "Something serious? Aren’t we very safe now? How is there another serious issue?"

Garen shook his head. "Do you remember traces of a black substance before we arrived here?’

"Do you mean to say that… that creature is coming here?" Angel’s eyes widened. "Impossible… Such a coincidence? We have just arrived at a safe zone and something is about to happen?"

It’s troublesome because it’s not a coincidence." Garen said calmly.

"You mean to say… someone is controlling it?" Angel inhaled.

"Keep an eye on Beckstone and his team. I need to go out and examine the surroundings myself." Garen said.

"Can’t you use Sight Sharing? It would be easier to find if you told your father and his subordinates, right?" Angel couldn’t understand his train of thoughts.

"I have my own arrangements." Garen held his calm tone. "Just prepare yourself mentally. Our stable life would be over before you know it."

As angel looked at his serious, grim face, and couldn’t help but turn serious about it as well.

"Whatever. I have managed to survive all the attacks along the way here. This is nothing."

Garen nodded. He stood up and in doing so agitated a lot of dust, which rose into the pillar of light, and he walked passed through it with his grey robe. In a blink of an eye, he walked out of the room, and only his footsteps could be heard as he walked further away.

Angel shook her head as he started to feel that she could never understand him. He had gotten more and more mysterious as trouble escalated.

************

Inside Vanderman’s study room.

Garen and Vanderman were sitting opposite each other.

The maidservant quietly backed out of the room and closed the door behind her, after pouring a cup of red tea for each of the housemasters, leaving both of them alone.

The steam of the red tea rose slowly into the air, dispersing and finally disappearing as the cups were placed on the table between son and father.

A faint fragrance were mixed within the air.

"Your favourite sugar cube has been added into it." Vanderman pointed at the red tea. "Have a drink. The taste made from home can’t be compared to the ones you drink outside." Vanderman revealed his rare gentle smile.

Garen picked up the cup and had a few sips.

"I have become a totem user." He whispered.

"I know, The Black-Striped White Tiger." Vanderman wasn’t surprised. "I’m not surprised that you’ve chosen the path of the totem. With your talent, you had almost no chance of evolving at all, so it’s the best that you choose to become the strongest among the form one totem user. It’s given by the totem user who had saved you last time right? It ain’t bad."

Garen didn’t say a word. He had deactivated all of his totem lights except for the Core Totem and Butterfly Totem’s Totem Light. This was to prevent from his father from discovering them, so that his future plans would not be affected.

"Why did you not let me become a totem user in the past? If I couldn’t become a Luminarist, at least I can control a portion of my fate when I’m a totem user, right?" Garen had wanted to ask this question for a long time.

"Why? I don’t know how you became a totem user. With your skills back then, you must have put in a tremendous amount of effort." Vanderman shrugged his shoulder. "I have originally planned out another path for you. However that doesn’t matter anymore now that you have become a totem user."

"Another path? Is it the same as Maxilan and the others?" Garen recalled the armor that Maxilan wore.

"Yes. It was a new technology that I had developed. I can weaken the totem light so that the requirement to use it is reduced as well, thus allowing a commoner to use it during battles." Vanderman said proudly.

"I have spent a lot of effort in this, and I finally I have solid results. I have been preparing my strongest work just for you; it was specifically tailored to your body’s characteristics. If not for your sudden leave and disappearance, I would have tailored one for you already!"

Garen didn’t say another word, as he didn’t think that this would have happened at all. Based on the original history, this item was destroyed before it could see the light of day, and this was the reason why it had no opportunity to be known to the world.

"You can go to the treasury and get any resources you need for your totem. You can take a rest, as we have a few guests coming." Vanderman patted onto Garen’s shoulder.

Garen stood up, bowed with respect and opened the door.

Master Baphje and Beckstone were already standing outside of the door. Master Baphje had a goatee and a bald shiny head.

"Master Baphje and Sir Beckstone." Garen lowered his head as he greeted them. Currently, his position was the lowest as Baphje and and Beckstone were on equal footing with his father in terms of strength. Regardless of his age, he was a form one totem user; nothing worth noting in the eyes of the two.

"Oh it’s you Cia. I brought Master Stone along. We have some things to discuss with your father." Baphje smiled as he said so.

"Master Stone?" Garen noticed how Baphje addressed Beckstone, suggesting that Baphje respected Beckstone a lot.

Beckstone greeted him with a nod and ignored him afterwards. The door was soon shut as both of them entered the room.

The reason Beckstone came over today was to find out more about Leanna’s details. Coincidentally, he witnessed the return of the Viscount’s son, his impression towards him was typical and vague. If Garen weren’t the Viscount’s son, he would not even bother taking notice of a form one totem user.

He believed that the relationship between father and son was rather good.

However, the most important thing to him was to take note of the Viscount’s reaction. He started to predict the scenarios that could possibly play out, and came up with the best course of action.

Garen stood outside of the door and tried to eavesdrop but he couldn’t hear a thing. He then realized that there was a Tactical Formation set up here to isolate sound, so he left the place immediately. With Baphje around, Beckstone was most likely suspicious of it and hadn’t confirmed the truth yet.

"Good day Master Cia."

"Master Cia."

"Do you want to go for a drink, Master!"

As he walked, the totem users Vanderman hired treated Garen as the same rank.

His position was overlooked in this precarious front line.

As Garen had no plans on making any arrangements, he greeted these totem users with a smile as he left the building. He was fairly similar to how Beckstone treated everyone else.

A few beautiful female totem users were attracted by his handsome figure. Sexual relationships were not looked down upon during such a chaotic period. As long as both of them were attracted to each other, they could get a room and have a one night stand. Perhaps they would still remain as strangers after having a go at each other.

However, Garen had yet gotten used to such a casual lifestyle.

After circling the manor once, he realized that Beckstone’s team members had gotten suspicious of Vanderman. Berlina, the girl in red armor, and Darian, the muscular guy, were asking for information all over the place clumsily.

Garen couldn’t look any further at such a clumsy way of collecting intel, and was sure that his father Vanderman had already realized it. It was just that he had yet to expose them.

Together with Leila, Garen gave an excuse to go to the Black Swan Lake. As he was a form one totem user and a Black-Striped White Tiger Totem user, which was much stronger than the typical form one user, Vanderman’s restriction towards him were very little. Furthermore, there were experimental beings that had yet revealed to the public patrolling the area so it was very safe.

Both of them got out of the manor with ease, and were on their way to the Black Swan Lake. Strangely, the weird fish in the lake stopped attacking Garen. It was very obvious that they were related to Vanderman’s experiment.

Leila didn’t ask Garen of his true intentions and was surprise that Garen was walking leisurely around the manor.

Chapter 341: Anticipation 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

Inside the manor.

Beckstone and his partner, Darian, were cautiously avoiding the guards and soldiers as they walked towards the most deserted part of the manor.

He looked left and right, and occasionally at his watch as he waited patiently.

Soon, a figure with a cold face appeared. It was Beckstone, and he looked like he was in a very bad mood.

"Have you gotten your answers?" Darian whispered.

"It’s been confirmed. The last thing we need to do is find his experiment lab. Those experimental beings outside wouldn’t appear for no reason. He must have hidden building with a core experiment apparatus inside." Beckstone said coldly.

"What are we waiting for? Let’s go find that place!" Darian rubbed his hands as he was getting excited.

"No need to rush. That old man had started to suspect me. He must have known what we are investigating when you two were collecting intel for this past two days. We must proceed with caution."

Beckstone’s tone was very calm.

He took out a small blue crystal from his pocket. It had a diamond shape and it looked crystal clear.

"When we came out, teacher had given me a total of three Time Mists, and now it’s the right time to use one of them. We can use two abilities from each of these, which are Confusion and Bail Out. Naturally, we can use them at a different time."

As he was speaking, the crystal gently floated and rotated silently in the air.

Beckstone swung his hand upward, and gently pushed the crystal upwards. It came to a stop at the right side of his body.

"Alright, we should move. Our immediate area has been mistified, and all probing tactics should be rendered useless. However, we only have 30 minutes."

"You sure have a lot of good items on your hand! Why don’t I have any of them?" Darian felt in envy.

"You need to maintain a certain amount of calculations before using this; its difficulty is on par with solving an advanced physics questions within a time of ten seconds. I still have some of them if you need it." Beckstone replied coldly.

Darian was silent, calculation was not his forte.

Beckstone looked around before bending down and gently pulling up a metal plate that lead to an underground passage. The metal plate was camouflaged as part of a green field, and had a thick layer of dirt caked on top of it. One would never be able to realise that it was an underground entrance.

Beckstone looked down at the entrance. His eyes were glowed silver. However, the light slowly dimmed and calmed.

"Let’s go."

He immediately jumped into the entrance like how someone would jump into a pond, and disappeared into the darkness.

Without any hesitation, Darian slowly placed his lower body into the hole and the metal plate back to its original position, before he fully entering the underground passage.

Both of them were inside the dark tunnel; their only light source the blue crystal on Beckstone’s body. However, its intensity could only illuminate a small area, relative to his surrounding.

The ground was moist, a faint rotten odor was always present.

"How long has this placed been sealed off? It’s so smelly!" Darian complained covering his nose.

"It’s not that it isn’t ventilated, the odor wouldn’t disappear even if there was air coming through." Beckstone said calmly.

"Disgusting. It’s worse than the time we had to pass through that creature’s stomach!" Darian complained.

Two of them moved forward with haste.

Few minutes passed, and Beckstone suddenly felt something was off.

"Something’s not right!" He immediately stopped moving. "We’ve been walking for so long, how could there be no movement from the other side?"

A silver light flashed from his right eye and his vision was covered with layers of silver light.

"It’s a Tactic Maze!" His face suddenly sank. "They had prepared in advance! They even set up such a troublesome Tactic Maze."

"Who cares what maze it is! Let’s just break through it!" Darian started to become impatient.

"He patted his body and a big black creature emerged from his side. It was a humanoid creature with an eagle’s head. Its head and its body were covered with thick, solid feathers, its eyes were gold, and a black rings surrounded its pupils. It had huge, black wings as its hands and goat’s hooves for legs. It’s total height was about 2.5 meters, and was about a head taller than Darian.

"Move forward Night Owl! Pierce through everything!" Darian pointed with his finger.

The eagle head creature screamed spread open its wings.

Kachak!

Within a screeching sound, two white lights shot forward and landed onto the wall in front of them.

Boom!!

Two huge holes were formed in the wall. Stones were sent flying everywhere, some had landed on them but were deflected by their totem light.

In a blink of an eye, the holes recovered back to their original shapes. It was like an animal regenerating a leg after having it severed. Strangely, the stones went through the ground and disappeared.

"It’s useless." Beckstone said calmly. "A Tactic Maze is made out of highly regenerative materials and has the effect of returning attacks. We can only get out of the Maze by following its rules. What you did just now was equal to a person fighting against the whole of the maze’s resources. If its source is geothermal energy, you’ll never solve it, even if you wasted all your strength."

"Then what should we do? You didn’t plan on breaking it through with strength?" Darian was displeased.

If we can find the four main nodes of the maze and destroy them, we can get out." Beckstone’s silver eyes moved. "Let’s spread out and find the nodes."

***********

Inside the underground secret room.

DuQian was standing quietly in front of a giant black crystal. She had been modified by Vanderman, and was no longer a human being.

Her upper body was still resembled a human, with her fair skin and beautiful face as she was wearing personal armor filled with green blood vessels. However, her lower body had been modified into a giant dark green root, which was directly inserted into a square pool. Her lower body was filled with hundreds of roots, and it kept absorbing the green liquid from the pool, as if a huge tree were absorbing nature’s nutrients.

As the housekeeper of the Vanderman household, DuQian was also Vanderman’s lover. She had been by Vanderman’s side since young, and their relationship was that of a husband and wife, father and daughter.

In order to her lover’s plan, she was willing to sacrifice herself and be modified into such a state.

"Someone dares to go through the maze?" He looked up at the map shown on the crystal.

It was shown clearly that there were two red dots moving deeper into the maze from the entrance.

The whole maze was like a giant web, where the edge of the right was the entrance, and the exit was at the other end.

Both of them were moving towards the exit of the maze. All the guards that they had encountered during the journey were easily killed off by them.

DuQian pressed onto the symbol on the master control on her right but nothing happened.

She felt something was off. "Is this… Mist Blockade? I can’t believe they have such an advanced skill! Looks like they have planned beforehand."

She pondered for a while.

"Since I can’t send out the signal, I will come after you guys myself."

She placed her fingers onto the master control once again.

Immediately, the black crystals showed four different screens, each of them had a strange head sculpture within.

They were the clown, blind giant, two-headed wild boar and a beautiful woman with gold hair and red eyes.

"Someone has invaded the maze. Which one of you will go and deal with them? The enemy came prepared." DuQian said coldly.

"Uh huh!!" The two headed wild boar was the first one to voice out. Its voice was rhythmic and it was obvious what it was trying to say something.

Strangely enough, DuQian understood what it was trying to say.

"Alright. You’ll handle them alone Ralph. Don’t let them pass through your territory."

The wild boar oinked two times before the screen was turned off.

"Why didn’t you send me?" The clown licked his long red nails as he said unsatisfactorily.

"I would be a better choice instead of you." The red-eyed beauty was dressing herself up as she comb her hair. "I have used up all my ingredients here. It’s about time to refill them."

"You would throw all of them away before you even finish them. I would have conserved the materials by eating all of them after cooking them." The Blind Giant said unsatisfactorily as well. "Nothing will be left for us once that pig Ralph goes on a frenzy."

DuQian looked at these sore eyes. These four were strongest mutated beings, each of had their own unique strengths and couldn’t be classified by form.

Even she would be in trouble if four of them were to team up.

Although she didn’t know the strength of the intruders, she should be able to kill them off easily in their territory with the support of the elusive maze.

************

Garen was staring at the two carriages coming from afar. The carriages were badly damaged, and were on the verge of breaking down. Two of the horns on top were missing, revealing a giant hole.

The curtain was made out of broken clothes, and the driver was no other than his beautiful cousin sister: Sophie Hathaway.

Hathaway’s cold elegance wasn’t damaged in the least. Her silver armor, on the other hand, was ragged, revealing the blood vessels within the armor. The way the red blood vessels moved in the armor indicated that it was an experimental equipment made by Vanderman.

Although she looked oppressing on the driver seat with her golden ponytail, she had obviously gotten a lot thinner.

As she took a turn from the forest lane, Hathaway saw Garen and Leila standing in the middle of the road.

"Cia!?" She was stunned and happy at the same time. "You’re still alive!!?"

Neigh~~ Neigh~~

She quickly stopped the black horses, got down the carriage and sprinted towards Garen.

She immediately hugged her tightly.

"You damn bastard! Where did you run off to! You had me so worried!" Hathaway was both happy and surprised. She then let go of Garen and pinched his body. "Thank goodness you didn’t lose any part of your body!"

"Stop it cousin sister!" Garen helplessly struggled out from her arms. "I’m already an adult. If you keep touching me I would sue you for sexual harassment!"

"Huh? I can’t believe you learnt these phrases in such a short time!?" Hathaway was angry and pinched Garen’s face. "Tell me! Where have you been all this while!?"

"Can you stop it?" Garen was completely helpless and immediately put some distance between him and her cousins sister. As Leila was in the scene, if this kept on his image as the leader would be lost for good.

He looked at Leila, and behold, she was giggling to herself in a corner.

"Cia! You’re not dead?!" A familiar voice came from the carriages.

Garen look at the carriage and saw a young woman with linen colored shawl hair jump down from the car. She was wearing some sort of white cowboy tight suit and there were holes everywhere on her knees and thighs.

This girl had a well balanced body figure, a rather ugly face and looked delicate. Her cheeks were red and seemed to be ill.

"Andel!?" Garen immediately recognized this girl. He could immediately recognize her thanks to his good memory.

Andel, Marin, Prynne and Acacia were the four of the noble team that were the most eye-catching in the Lush Green district.

He didn’t expect Andel to be alive.

"What happened to you? You look like you’re sick." Garen immediately walked towards her, the girl who had a slight crush on him.

"Where is Prynne and the others? Marin? How is everyone?" He started to reminisce the days the four of them hung out together, when he was enjoying his life.

"Prynne and Marin are together as they were sent to the royal capital by their household members. Marin was attacked by a creature and was severely injured and his injury could only be treated in the Royal Capital. I… I have no where else to go." Andel lowered his head as her mood plunged down.

Hathaway walked towards her and gave her a gentle hug. "When Andel’s family was moving, they were attacked by a creature and everyone was separated. The status of the remaining household members are currently unknown. I met her when I was on my way here. If not for the totem user who was sent by Prynne protected us, I’m afraid…" She didn’t finish her sentence by the meaning was loud and clear.

"Mum and sister will definitely be fine…" Andel whispered.

"Let’s go back to the manor and tell us what you have gone through. Let’s settle down first before we talk about the rest." Garen knew that Prynne’s status was higher than his, and was most likely the strongest noble in the Lush Green district. They had both power and authority, so he wasn’t so worried about him. The fellow’s household had a strong background within the Royal Capital and the Royal Household.

"I need to find a way to contact my uncle in the Royal Capital. He will surely help me, since he pampered me the most when I was young." Andel whispered.

These for households had countless of connections in the Kovitan Empire. Garen or Acacia’s father, Vanderman who was an academic noble had incredible connections with the research academy and the three departments. He was able to pull Barr and Baphje here to assist him during the Chaotic Era thanks to his connections.

Andel and the remaining two household, too had very strong connections of their own. As long as they’re alive, the chances of them from recovering the damage would always be very high.

*************

Buzz…

Silver light came out from Beckstone’s eyes and formed a silver vortex onto the wall.

The shape kept changing and soon formed into a complicated map and two white dot and green dot could be clearly seen on it.

"This is the map of this maze. It’s not really complicated as they are only 322 forks. The construction of this maze is technologically obsolete It looks like they’ve spent some effort in it." Beckstone said coldly.

Darian, who had both of his hands at the back of his head, followed behind him without much interest.

"I’ll just need to follow you and your orders. Stop telling me these complicated things because I will get confused by it."

Bam! Bam ! Bam!!

Heavy footsteps could be heard from the front.

"It’s coming again. It’s so annoying! When will it stop!" Darian started to lost his cool and flung his right hand and the Night Owl appeared once again. "These creatures are too annoying! We need to kill all of them for five times in order for them to stop appearing!"

Chapter 342: Anticipation 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

"There’s no need for you to waste your totem’s energy. We just need some time to deal with them thoroughly." Backstone said coldly. "Listen to my orders."

"Right!"

"Lightning attack on the upper right."

Kaching!!

Two lightning bolts with the thickness of a small arm shot out and landed onto the upper right corner of the dark passage.

"Stomp twice with your legs at the lower right."

Boom Boom!!

The Night Owl followed the orders and stomped twice with all its might.

Suddenly the passage in front of them changed.

"Alright let’s move."

Beckstone walked forward, passing through Darian and his creature.

"Is that it?" Darian was stunned as he looked in front of him. He didn’t even see any trace of humanoid creatures.

The black tall man made out of dirt had completely disappeared. What was left in front was just a pitch black passage, as if the disturbance previously was nothing but an illusion.

"Save some energy because there will be more later." Beckstone’s voice came from the front.

"Where’s our final destination?" Darian quickly followed Beckstone.

"We will go where the maze ends."

***************

"You couldn’t find it?" DuQian was clearly upset.

She looked at the multiple screens on the crystal.

"The clown had been dealt with?" She couldn’t believe that the opponents were this strong. It was as if there were no obstacles as they walked through the clown’s supposed traps.

The clown, who loved to battle, went in front of the wild boar and met the opponents head on. However, he was also killed in front of the wild boar.

His corpse was nowhere to be found.

Inside the screen, the beautiful woman with golden hair and red eyes was upset as well.

"The opponent seems to give off a strange silver light. He managed to capture the clown and is nowhere to be seen in the maze. What should we do?"

"Tell all the guards to come back and defend. No… The news can no longer be spread out." DuQian applied pressure to her forehead. "Three of you gather up, I will be joining you. The end of the maze is the owner’s study room. We must not let them go there! Never!"

"Yes!"

Three of them nodded and the screens were closed instantaneously.

DuQian looked at the tree roots under her lower body and her eyes were filled with rage. She was Viscount’s strongest living weapon, and the opponent was obviously going after the Viscount. If she were to be defeated, then the whole Trejons’ family would be done for!

Alone, Viscount was just a form one totem user and had not much battle strength. His strongest weapon was her!

DuQian picked up the black spear that was placed on the stone. The roots behind her body wound up together and formed one huge tail. She then slowly moved forward and headed towards the control room.

"As long as we can hold on until the mist disappears, the blockade will disappear and Viscount will immediately notice what is going on here!"

**********

Boom!

Beckstone stared coldly at the creature that had fallen in front of him.

The beautiful woman with golden hair and red eyes, who had a pair of antlers on her back, melted in front of him at an alarming pace. She then turned into a stream of silver light and was absorbed into his right eye as she disappeared.

"Let’s move on. The experiment lab should be just right up ahead of this maze."

Darian followed him tightly from behind.

"I can’t fight against beautiful women.. as my heart melted when I saw her… If there are any more seductive traps… Keep it coming at me! Don’t be shy!" He muttered as he looked around at his surroundings.

Both of them then pushed open the sealed stone door in front of them.

Rustle…

Their faces changed the moment they opened the door.

"This… This is!!?" Darian covered his mouth as he tried to resist the strong stench in the air and stared what was in front of him.

It was a room packed with corpses, male and female. They were covered in red stripes and were hung by steel chains pierced through their hands, resembling poultry on display.

The majority of them were youngsters. Some of them were even children, just a few years old.

However, all the corpses had one thing in common; they had been skinned. All of them were covered in blood. Their muscles, red and white, were clearly visible. It was not a sight for the weak.

Some of these corpses had been utterly rotten. Maggots drilled in and out of crevices where missing pieces of flesh had been eaten.

On the other hand, some of the corpses were still fresh; obviously placed here not long ago.

The whole room was spacious and completely filled with hundreds of corpses. These corpses were separated into two rows, end to end, spanning thirty meters long.

Beckstone was traumatized as he slowly put one foot in front of another into the room.

His footsteps echoed off the walls as they fell on the greyish-white stone path that covered the room. On the sides of the stone road were stairs that went under; the bottom of this place was filled with colossal amounts of clotted and wet blood, which painted the whole floor red.

As they walked deeper, the duo saw a few crystallized boxes filled with corpses. The boxes were about as tall as a person, and there were even detailed labels on each box.

Beckstone looked at the label.

‘Sun Calendar Year 3558 of the 4th Month -- Alice: There is only one successful sample. The success rate is too low. My heart softened as I heard the cries of these children. Unforgivable. I am trying to evolve the human species as a whole! I must persevere!’ -- Vanderman Trejons.

There was a small girl, about five to six years old, who was immersed in a transparent liquid in this case. This little girl’s golden hair was spread open like a flower inside the water. Her eyes were wide open, looking out of the glass, as if she were still alive and was placed inside this small glass case, naked.

"Such inhumanity!" Darian scolded out loudly as he hyperventilated. It was clear that he was very angry.

Beckstone’s eyes were filled with murderous intent.

He then started to walk alongside the cases.

His invisible distortive power started to expand from his body. This strong power kept spreading out, like smoke and filled up the room in no time.

Two tall figures appeared at the entrance then.

One of them was a two-headed wild boar humanoid, and the other one was a fair giant, who was a head taller than the wild boar. However, the giant had no eyes, and couldn’t see anything at all.

Behind these two creatures stood a strange woman.

Its upper body was a human, but its lower body was a tail made out of countless roots. On top of that, this lady’s eyes were filled with blood.

"Kill them!!" DuQian ordered without mercy.

Countless Slime Men climbed up from the floor and surrounded Beckstone and Darian in the room.

Beckstone ignored them and kept moving forward quietly, his eyes falling upon the cases one by one.

He finally stopped at one of the many cases that lined the room. What was already a pale face became a shade lighter, as he saw the label on this particular case.

His trembling hands slowly reached for the label.

‘Sun Calendar Year 3357 of the 1st month. Leanna Ross. The quality of the children from this batch is just superb! Five of them had succeeded. This was without a doubt an encouragement to my research. What’s funny is that this kid dared to say that I am pitiful. I will let her know that who’s the pitiful one!’

There was the female corpse of eleven or twelve year-old girl, peacefully immersed inside the transparent liquid within the case.

The girl was naked, straightened from head to toe by a thick, metal bar inserted into her mouth, piercing and running straight through her lower body. She was stabilized by the base of the case and was placed as a standard human specimen.

The girl’s eyes were wide open. Her gaze filled with agony. Her limbs were flush against the wall of the glass as if she was struggling with all her might at an impossible task.

Beckstone gently rubbed the label’s characters as his body shivered. It was as if something in his body was expanding and he was resisting with all his might.

"Leanna…" He stared at the beautiful, familiar face, as he recalled the days he spent with her when he was young.

Beckstone closed his eyes in agony.

"Ah!!! I will kill all of you!!" Darian, who was standing from behind, finally exploded in rage.

Two Night Owls appeared at the same time, along with a giant Grey Hawk as well.

The Grey Hawk was surrounded by a grey light, which was an indicated that it had been spiritualized.

It was at this moment.

A powerful silver distortive power expanded.

Silver light lit up from Beckstone’s right eye, as if something was trying to escape from it. They expanded and contracted sporadically.

A few minutes later.

Beckstone stood at the front of a reddish brown passage, where he could see the wooden door at the other end. That wooden door was the entrance of the study room which bypassed the maze.

He could feel that person’s breath behind the door.

Darian stayed behind to deal with the creature that seemed to be immortal. As the Time Mist was about to expire, he came alone to prevent from the main culprit from noticing, so that he could kill him!

Beckstone restrained the silver light in his eyes and walked towards the wooden door silently. He quickly hid his murderous intent.

************

Vanderman was drinking his red tea in front of the window quietly.

This was the study room of the main building, which was also his favorite study room. It was also one of the maze exits as it was connected to the underground lab as well. His biggest secret was placed inside this very room.

He felt safe here, as long as he knew that this place wasn’t in danger.

He placed down the teacup, took out his black pipe and carefully lighted the tobacco inside and adjusted it.

Click!

As the red fire was lit and immediately burnt the glowing red tobacco. Its fragrance soon permeated the entire room.

"I need to send off those three as soon as possible. The longer they stay here, the higher the probability of them discovering my secret." He pondered for a moment. "Coincidentally, the twelfth princess came to visit. It would be best if I can let her bring these three along when she leaves."

He started to feel guilty recalling his experiments back in the days. He knew that the experiments were inhumane, yet he gave no quarter pursuing his ideals back then. In the end, he had created bloody memories that he didn’t want to recall.

Every time he recalled these memories, he couldn’t help himself but feel agitated.

"This is the price of improving the civilization. They would have thanked me if they still had a soul." He comforted himself so but he could keep the guilt in his heart at bay.

Sigh…

He exhaled a ring of long smoke streams.

Knock Knock KNock.

"Please come in." Vanderman responded calmly.

The door was opened.

Garen came in with a smile.

"Father, since I am free, I decided to come and see you."

Chapter 343: Battle 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

Vanderman froze for a moment and then smiled slightly, feeling as though a little something had filled the hole in his heart.

"Sure. Speaking of which, it seems like a long time since we’ve had a proper talk, as father and son."

He put down his pipe and watched Garen sit down, reminiscence in his eyes.

"Speaking of which, when I was young, I also did many wrong things in order to achieve my ideals. I hurt a lot of innocent lives. Thinking back on it now, my heart aches with the pain of it."

He paused.

"In truth, even now, no matter how much I want to make up for it, the effort I had already sunk in forces me to continue to the end. If it weren’t for you and Du Qian, I’m afraid…"

"In order to achieve their ideals in life, people need to step over countless corpses, isn’t that the principle of life?" Garen leaned onto the sofa, saying calmly. "The weak pay the price for the ideals of the strong. The desires of the strong need to be filled by the weak, that’s why countless people chase after the strong, and idolize them. If the strong are merely a unit that services the weak, nobody would want to reach that pinnacle."

"Where did you hear such theories from?" Vanderman frowned. This was natural selection, plain and simple, the theory of the Phantom Lights. Although Vanderman himself admired the Phantom Lights, not even he was this extreme.

"Isn’t that only natural?" Garen shrugged. "The ladder of the world is decided by strength. While the strong perform their duties by protecting the world, they should also enjoy the service of the weak. Everyone should do what they are supposed to. But some people always think that everything is under their control. Even if the chances of an accident occurring are low, that doesn’t mean there definitely won’t be any accidents."

"What are you saying?" Vanderman’s expression was slightly surprised.

Garen smiled imperceptibly.

"What am I saying? There will always be many accidents in life, some of which can be avoided. But others can’t be avoided no matter what. What we need to do is maintain a calm heart even in the face of accidents, so that we never regret anything. What do you think, am I right?" His gaze went across the room in an instant, penetrating through the door, and focusing on Beckstone, who was outside, in a moment.

Stone had stretched out his hand to grab the doorknob, but stopped. He stood outside the door and clearly felt that intense gaze penetrating everything, landing straight on him.

"Interesting…" His lips curved ever so slightly. He loosened his left hand slowly, his eyes faintly glowing with a silver light. There almost seemed to be a shapeless beast roaring in his pupils.

Grooowl!!

It was almost simultaneous. The roar of the beast, the sparkle of silver light.

A huge black shadow pounced at the door!

The door smashed into pieces in an instant, the black shadow colliding into another with a crash. In that instant, nothing could be seen clearly, and there was only the explosion of silver light, blindingly bright.

Barroom!!!

The whole building collapsed with a boom, large clouds of dust and wood dust scattering everywhere. The smoke and dust floated up, completely obscuring everyone’s vision.

In the center of the estate, the whole main block had come crashing down directly. Huge amounts of white smoke rippled out from the center, and nothing could be seen clearly. Some of the servants and patrolling totem users nearby quickly ducked to avoid the scattering debris of stone and wood.

Slowly, the wind blew the dust off the ground.

Garen’s figure slowly appeared on top of the rubble. He stood on the spot quietly, his gaze looking straight ahead.

There, Beckstone had silver blood leaking from the corners of his mouth. His eyes were like rapidly rotating silver whirlpools, constantly sparkling with blinding silver light.

"I misjudged…" He glared at Garen, squeezing the words out of clenched teeth with a hard expression.

"Cia… You!!" Vanderman stared blankly at the son in front of him. This child, who was once so familiar to him, was suddenly so foreign right now. The strength he displayed in that moment just now was enough to make Vanderman’s body go numb. Such terrifying strength…

"Leave this to me, Father." Garen chuckled lightly, transferring his gaze onto Beckstone. "Let us have a fair duel." He clapped his hands lightly.

Clap-clap.

As he clapped, the earth began to tremble.

Phwah!

The floor next to him immediately bulged out. A huge Dual Headed Salamander suddenly popped out from the ground. It was more than ten meters long, seven or eight meters tall. When it crawled out of the ground like that, it instantly sent the surrounding servants screaming and running in all directions.

Screee!!!

The Dual Headed Salamander settled beside Garen with two tapping sounds. No matter how you looked at it, it was a huge grey-green monster. Even its two heads alone were as tall as a person, and that mouth could swallow an adult in one go.

But Beckstone wasn’t paying attention to that, he was looking instead at one of the creature’s mouths. It was biting an unconscious woman, Berlina. The girl in red armor was being lightly held in the Dual Headed Salamander’s teeth and seemed to have completely lost consciousness. She was covered in wounds, her armor was damaged in many places, and her body was a mess of blood and flesh in several areas as well. Her Totem Light was extremely faint, which meant her totem had been destroyed.

By then, Vanderman had already blocked the others who had come rushing out at the sound and retreated to a distance. Looking at the unbelievably powerful Garen, he didn’t seem to have recovered his senses yet.

He still couldn’t understand what was happening. How did his son suddenly end up so powerful!? His brain was a mess.

Andel and Hathaway ran in from another recreational building and stood at the other side with different expressions. Andel looked like she was seeing Acacia for the first time, her gaze on him filled with surprise and confusion.

"What… what on earth happened? What is that monster!? When did Acacia get so strong!?"

Hathaway opened her little mouth slightly, completely unable to answer. She was herself utterly confused and had no idea what was happening.

"Lord Beckstone is a Form Three Spiritualized totem user! Cia actually… actually…"

The two of them looked at the huge Dual Headed Salamander beside Acacia and felt weak in the knees just looking at that enormous body. Judging by its size, it was at least a Form Three monster!

"Form… Form Three? …" Andel’s eyes looked lost. She had only ever seen the power of Form Two totem users, so even Form Twos were the pinnacle of strength as far as she was concerned. As for the even stronger Form Threes, she could not even conceptualize them, so she just grouped them together with the rumored greats.

Du Qian, who was grievously hurt, hid in the shadows and was surrounded by some strange-looking low-level experiments. Watching the drastic developments in the field, her gaze was complicated, dazed, and comforted.

"My master, you finally have an heir…" Looking at how Acacia’s strength right now, she could almost remember how strong the Viscount was back in the day.

On the other end, Leila, Angel and the rest were hurrying over.

"Wow!! As expected of Big Bro! He still has such an impressive trump card!" It was Leila’s first time seeing the huge Dual Headed Salamander hiding behind Garen. That mountain-like beast was the most striking image on the scene, and so of course was the woman in red armor in its jaws.

Angel glanced at the huge Dual Headed Salamander, a flash of understanding and shock in her eyes. Thinking back to how calm Garen had always been, she instantly had her answer for everything, and she quickly swept her gaze over the other places.

Everything was normal on the Viscount’s side, and it wasn’t the girls who just came either. The focus should be on that young man standing opposite Garen.

"Move aside, all of you, and focus on maintaining the safety and vigilance of the estate." She connected it to what Garen said before. "Vicky! You go outside, and stay aware of the movements outside!"

"Okay, Big Sis!" Vicky received the order and left without hesitation. Hearing Big Sis use this sort of tone for once, she instantly knew that this was no joke, and something big must have happened.

"Leila, you go to the back, outside, and keep watch as well. If there’s anything you can’t handle, send out a signal immediately!"

"Yes yes yes!" Leila left reluctantly. "I wanted to see more of Boss’ cool presence, why you gotta chase me away so fast…"

"Ansa, you stand further back, and take care of your own safety." Angel raised her right hand. Soundlessly, five pitch-black panthers walked out from the shadows. These panthers were sitting or standing, walking around Angel like guards glaring at the surroundings.

Two of the black panthers had limbs made of black mist, as though they were covered by a cloud of black air.

Looking at the two men standing off in the center, Angel’s eyes flashed with calm.

****************

Garen looked at Beckstone, standing opposite him. This unnaturally calm young man was now already pale as death, his eyes filled with unconcealable bloodlust.

"How is it? Anything you want to say?"

Garen could feel the gazes on himself. Like so many moving spotlights, they were all gathered around him and Beckstone opposite him.

He smiled nonchalantly.

"Fight me fair and square, just the two of us one-on-one. Whaddaya think?"

Pitch black Deep Swamp Crocs floated up next to him, and these crocodiles were surrounding Beckstone.

"Fine…" Beckstone squeezed the word out of clenched teeth. His gaze on Garen was getting darker and darker.

"Don’t look at me like that, we just have different stances." Garen smiled. In his past life, too many people looked at him like that, and not one of them didn’t die by his hand.

"Fine. No more chit-chat." Garen waved his hand.

Groooowll!!!

More than ten beasts roared in rage.

The Dual Headed Salamander swallowed the woman in red armor and kept her under its tongue. With heavy stomping steps, it walked up to Garen.

Garen’s feet tapped the ground lightly and floated into the air lightly. Finally, he landed on the Dual Headed Salamander’s back, high up above.

Pssshew!!

The first Deep Swamp Croc turned into a black line, pouncing at Beckstone.

And then the second, the third, the fourth!

All twenty Deep Swamp Crocs were there, attacking and biting from all angles. They fell over Beckstone like so many black threads.

Each black thread brought along a pungent current of foul air.

When the black threads brushed past stone debris, a chunk instantly disappeared from them, as though it vanished into thin air.

"Once Deep Swamp Crocs attack, they’ll burst with instantaneous energy exceeding that of a Form Two totem. They are super fast, and don’t stop until they’ve bitten their prey." Garen said smilingly, "Don’t dodge now, your pretty partner is still in my hands. Let me see your true power."

The Salamander at Garen’s feet revealed Berlina in its maw once more, lying under its sharp teeth.